The stars laid out the show
Stars shining so bright
Watch the secrets unfold
There's magic in her hands
Whisper what the future holds
Dance to the mystery
Yeah, yeah, yeah
So
We are Kangol
how's everybody um i wanted to just come on for maybe i'll do like well let me see
oh yeah well we have let me see kind of my graphic for tonight's show
this is pretty cool i mean this just chat gpt just made that for me it actually made a better
there you go. Hi, how are you, Nancy? Yeah, I picked up, I had a coupon, some coupons for the bagel
store, so I thought, is it a vanilla cream cold brew? But I'm out of tobacco, kind of. And so I'm
Kind of like
Not I'm not doing too good. So I'm gonna be probably return
No, maybe returning the new one I got because it doesn't really like work for me
I might keep it actually because I need a selfie stick
But this this other one it's like it doesn't
Stay in the
Doesn't attach anymore. So I just I just I was gonna get a new one
But I just ordered and then like like refund it and everything but I just I just ordered duct tape
So it will come today that I could uh, I can fix it
How's everybody doing?
But yeah, I had a good night last night, but I just wanted to give a mixture like you know since I'm starting to have the panels sponsored now
You know if you do sponsor a panel in the future if you have anything to advertise, you know, I'll put it on the banner
Your channel to duct tape will always work. Yeah, it's just like see it's like this
You see how it is like it. Are you see the alien?
Hey friend
Yeah, this like it has this like, you know
Or you screwed this part in he screwed this into like this thing
But they're like all war all the they're all worn down just for me for me
He usually gets so much though. It's all over you. So I ordered some gorilla tape
And it will come today kind of pay a few bucks extra to have it come today, but you know, uh-oh
It's worth it for the show. Hi Eva one. How are you?
Yeah, it's cool. Ely the spunky got this for me. Isn't that awesome?
Ely with the kitty cat
Hey, what's up? How is everyone doing? So guys guess what I found out? I found out I was like I was like
Got like a this discord notification or something or something or rumble notification. I got a notification on rumble
And I said it was like oh it had it had my name on it. I was like it was like
Saying like my show psyche awakens tarot. They had my exact title
What is this and I went I looked and someone is someone
Someone streams my show onto rumble and it's on this channel called panelverse
And so it's already on rumble and it's like, you know, I
Tried stream to rumble isn't you too complicated. It's also I can have a minimum thing
I think I can stream to you. You're still evil
Well, yeah, so there's a minimum like a number of like ways to
to stream right now, but I don't think Rumble will be the way to go. I mean, I was getting some views there, but
I don't care if this other person who's called the panel versus streams my every show because actually it's kind of cool because
then I have the archive of my shows without, um,
having to save all of them. I can still delete them on my channel. That's pretty cool.
I don't know, because who cares about if, like, you get poor mom on Rumble.
I don't think Rumble even, like, checks the videos or anything.
Yeah, so let me see how am I gonna hold up my I think I'm gonna put it up in a tissue box
Let me see. Let's kind of a little bit low put it inside
Yeah, it's not like ideal right now, I'll put it like that I
Will I'm getting as soon as the gorilla tape gets here
Okay, that kind of works. Well, not really. That does not work.
Hi. Hi, CB. I'm, uh, Jim.
Hey, oh, you went to link random guy? Okay, hold on. Oh, shit. Yeah, we do have an hour from summer.
I'm carrying over from last night.
I will carry over the hours if I happen to end as soon as I
make sure that.
And also, I'm going to make sure if anybody does sponsor
a panel in the future.
Good morning.
Not only does open the panel, but you get a full advertisement
on the screen on the banner the whole time that it will run.
So that's a pretty good deal, I think.
Maybe I'll lose some other things like have a raffle for the people that have a sponsored panel and for
free gift or something like that, too
so I
Want to make sure everyone has fun up here comes random guy
What I do you're gay right would you would you fucking would you rock that I think sick bro come on?
Would you rock that?
I like the that's like the fucking Marth mobile almost kind of huh?
What should I do drive it? Should I drive it? Should I keep it? What should I do? Come on? What should I do?
I'd you like it. Yeah, look at it like it. It's cute. I mean it's a cute little
Like I don't really see a light blue car nowadays, you know, it's like a that's not that common other color
They're little powder blue or Tiffany. Oh, yeah, does it remind you of Wayne's world?
Um, I don't know. I haven't seen Wayne's world in so long, but you know, I bet if what if I feed it recently
But I don't know what happened your cars being towed away
No, it's I'm telling it fool. Are you're towing it? Are you a tow truck driver? Yeah? Oh
Cool, it's a good little little job. Well gotta go see ya. Bye
You just wanted to show me that little car on the boot
The blue car is booted.
Aw, he wants to keep it.
Where's my really, that kind of car?
I see.
Oh, you gotta go.
I need my glasses.
Okay guys, I'm getting the Jeffrey Dahmer glasses
and I'm returning these ones.
I was gonna just like get them to like,
because these were kind of like expensive.
So.
Every turn I'm gonna Amazon has really good, which I mean I like these but they look like crooked
They look like the crooked on my head first they face first of all
I don't know if it's my nose or something, but they're already I've already sat on them at a time
So they're crooked right and then second of all
you know
Okay, so last night I guess everybody heard the famous page
and Alex song
Has anybody heard that because I bet that was like, okay, I've been the service. So that was like, oh make a AI music video
And so it was like really like fancy. I was like, oh my god. Well, this looks really cool
And so I like I like uh, it was like it does automatically it figures out like the exact like meaning of the song
The story and a bit of the storyboard and it does the graphics and it's like and then it started putting it together
I got a subscribe like $19 a month to get you know, just a subscription on it
And then like halfway through it looks good.
It started looking so it would look so cool.
You guys are gonna love it.
But like halfway through it, it like stops
or like it starts and I wouldn't look
and it said it ran out of credits.
So I spent like $19 on all these credits
and made like over half the video,
maybe probably three quarters of the video.
Oh, Jamie, how are you?
I'm sorry, I didn't see.
Hey, I hope you, yeah, Jamie, Jamie herself.
Oh.
You're really bad. You're alive and rusty in the house. Oh my god. Hope you're hope you're doing good. Jamie
Love you, sweetie
Hi everybody, oh
Yeah, I heard that she had some your teeth your teeth. Oh, I hope you're okay, Jamie your dental or
Needs some dental surgery. I hope you're okay. I'm not in too much pain. You're in the hospital
Jamie's she's not oh, okay. I think that RIP is it. Oh my god. I'm sorry see me. Oh
Oh collapse line. Oh my gosh. That sounds like it painful. I'm so sorry, Jamie
Well, do you want to just want to cheer up? I have something to cheer you up, Jamie
Without further ado
So this is the song that I will have this song this song
Put to a video, but I spent all these credits and after so I say if I if I
Want to finish out that video, which I will do I'll finish the video
They're trying to charge me $15 of credits to make feel like to finish the video I think so or not me
I think I'll have some leftover, but I'll play the Alex. Here's the Alex and Paige song here guys Alex and Paige
This is called
Paige we fought we fall in love with me. I think I felt we fall in love with me Paige
And I've been missing in my sleep, hey
Oh, thank you. Let me have a look. Hold on.
I'm sorry. It looks terrible, Jamie. Oh my gosh. I'm sorry. It looks terrible. Jamie's all bloody
and uh
The hospital bed the cars are wrecked. I mean, it's
So look you survived. Oh
My word is being delivered
out for delivery
I think I'm getting some new cards today guys. It should be an exciting day
Hey, yeah, I'm glad you're okay, Jamie
So I got lunch today. I got uh nova locks and I had a coupon for three dollars off of nova locks and a coffee cold brew
So, oh, am I still muted? Hello. Hello. Do you hear me? I think I think I'm okay
How's everybody doing though, I mean, it's like, you know, just let's be happy. Jamie's alive. We're all live
Your life can be fragile, right?
Oh
My stomach just paced him by CB. Yeah, it's awful. The pictures looks just terrible
She's like it looks like she's she's all a little bit bloody
Yikes, I wish Jamie. I'm sorry
But my stomach is growling
Yeah, but you know what's good about the panel too is like if you now people like since it's monetized now the panel
First of all means my you know, I'll be okay
I think my show will always be okay because you know always people as long as I have you guys there my audience there
You know, I will I will be on YouTube because
Whether monetized or not, the show is monetized, okay?
Second of all, some people just don't like me.
They want to yell at gay people
or get some steam off and it's taken.
So, you know, or just be disrespectful to me and, yeah.
You want to be disrespectful to me.
Just like, when I forget my TTS setup,
people can put very insulting comments in it,
but I don't really care because I'll be kidding.
Every comment, you know, I'll be getting a donation.
So, yeah, money helps sometimes.
So, yeah.
Oh, someone pulled up in front of you.
Oh my gosh, who's driving you or your mom?
Is mom OK?
I heard mom's knees.
So guys yesterday I cleaned my house and it's like so
nice
It's like the you know, the the laundry is all done the dishes are all done
The I have like scrubbed down all the surfaces I went through all this cleaner
I cleaned my table up last night clean my that like the TV area clean every surface
I'm gonna get him back him soon. You don't drive you boat your t-boat at last minute ouchie
Hi, hold on. Hey, I see ya
Yeah
You know what else there you know what else is a good song though guys is the the gaudi song
So but I'll tell me tell me when you went out here. You just never heard the gaudi song
God he actually cried when I played it. He was like so touched. It is a cute song, too
But I've never seen him seen him
Like that that's it was really touching
I'm doing okay the page now. I'm gonna I'm gonna make that page in Alex, but I'm gonna have that finished and that's guys that video is hilarious
It's just that, you know, it's Alex, I don't know how they figure out like what Page and
Alex might look like, but I think it looks like Page and Alex look like the cartoon basically
of like, you know, animating that video. It's so funny.
Y'all, hey, Irby. We're doing good today. Look at my alien saying hello.
Farah, Farah, oh my gosh. I'm so sorry. Healing prayers. Yes
Hey, Irby
I'm sorry, so it's nice to be that I didn't see it. Let me say sweet pea. Hey, JB. Oh, hi JB. I sweet pea
I'm sorry. I was I like just
Get distracted and stuff. I
Love you, sweet pea. You're sweet
Your motto hey mods, okay sweepies a member Jamie's Cowboys member reality Nancy is a mod
I see
Jamie's Cowboys ready Nancy charisma Hernandez was a mod he man is a mod and a member
Yep, hey everybody see a new shout outs for all the members. Yep. I think Jamie's yeah, I think God Jamie's okay
Why don't we wait for people to get here? I'll just play the Gaudi song.
Do you guys want to hear the Gaudi song or no? Hey Jenny girl, what's up?
Aw. I'll play the Gaudi song. I want to animate the Gaudi song too.
I just don't know how expensive it is, but I think I'll do it.
Yeah. Yay Jamie's here guys.
I think I had like the video. I think I had like the lowest settings or whatever for it
But I can't believe we use all my credits for like almost three quarters of the video. Anyway, here's the song. Hey, Jenny
Here's the Goddy song. You guys like Goddy. Here's Goddy. Here's Goddy song
Out of New York, came a storm on wheels
Rollin' in smooth with the mafia feels
Cuban cigar, lit like it's temper
Pizza in one hand, hot dog for dinner
Said psyche, I'm bored, had to switch the scene
Left some poor woman screamin' on live stream
Trolled her down to the void and back
Then crashed my show like a heart attack
Gotti, made man, trol king, mafia soul
Rollin' through panels like he's in control
But they're still my friends
Yeah, love you God
He's still the bitter and we fight
We troll, but we friends
Forever my friend
He thinks he's God
With the lowercase G
In a wheelchair
Still stomping through the live feed
Bout of your king
Laughin' at chaos like it's comic relief brought
Spunky too now that troll's a gem
Mean one sweet ones they all jumped in
Cameras glitchin', chat on fire
Mods beggin' me to cut the wire
But nah, I like my circus, I love this mess
Every troll's just a test of a mess
Got you rude, absurd and free
But deep down you got loyalty
my friend you called me a fraud then defended my clown spam my chat then held
it down you got layers like a deep dish slice under all that shade a heart made
of ice and maybe rice so let's light that cigar raise the mic another night of
Fun and weirdly it feels like you're the one
But we stick together
Playing the song. That's Gotti's song.
But if I have to say so myself, that is a good song. Oh, Gotti's crying. That is a sweet song.
Yeah, Jamie's here, Gotti. Jamie's in the chat.
My favorite, I think my favorite
My favorite part of the song that one of my favorites is is I go this chord are me Amish and Mormon Italian blend
Oh, it's funny
oh guys so yeah i have my unfortunately yeah sending good vibes to jamie yeah guys unfortunately my
tablets uh i won't get this gorilla masking tape for like another couple hours i think it will come
between two and five or something so then i'll be able to fix my uh my tripod but until then i have
to hold my kind of hold my thing but there i am now i can show you like a little bit of my i mean
Okay
Here's my staircase
You can see now see that's my house. Let's see. It's pretty clean. It's like I need it back himself, but
All right, we'll get on this up on this table kitchen is not bad
There we go, look at my house, fair thing.
It's clean, huh?
You heard the voice too?
Yeah, that's, my door's wide open because it's downstairs.
It's just like, it has a screen door.
Oh, hold on.
Oh yeah, a person.
I did that because I unmodded all,
like a lot of the, a lot of the managing mods
because someone turned off my,
My my banned words someone someone like a deleted them. So I will know I'm gonna remod you
I was just I'm on it like a lot of the after charge my phone a little bit
I'll remod you forgot I forgot I just like I just I'm on it like most of the managing mods
But then I just tell me I'll I'll
I'll remod people I just need to like
Both I always go through my list and like sometimes that happens
I know you won't, Purse. I know you won't.
I'm a...
I'll turn on my phone in a minute.
Yeah.
Oh, thank you. Thank you, Christine. Yeah.
It's just like, yeah, I don't know why someone would do that.
But actually, it's better than what happened before.
Like, somebody before deleted, hey, Christine, how are you?
Someone deleted all the words before,
and then they replaced it with my name, Bita's name.
What's Discord?
Discord is kind of an app where we communicate
after the show, or we have a little,
I'll put the link in for you, hold on one second.
The Discord is right here, once again.
What are the bad words?
I don't know, guys, that's top, top.
Are you, you have to be a, you have to be a,
are you a managing mod?
You can only see if you're a managing mod.
I might make you a managing mod.
But what are the bad words?
I don't know, I have the, I put, you know,
some of the swear words, some of the slander words
that people use, you know, this is typical,
some typical stuff that I'd rather not have in the chat.
So have two managing mods, one channel manager,
it'll be easy to figure out who's fucking with me.
I think everybody that I have, oh, it's pretty, let me see, okay, so now I can, now I'll
remodulate you and I'll pin my link too, yeah.
So I want to thank, so last night.
We had Spunky and Summer, both sponsored panels.
And so, yeah, I think that it's going to work better because I like having panels,
but sometimes it gets very, very quiet during them, and it kind of takes away from me,
like, doing readings and stuff like that.
Having them sponsored then I can actually you know, you can I can advertise your channels on the banner
If you'd like to sponsor a channel then you'd say pretty much are the hero for the
The show because you let that everybody can come on panel
It's then it kind of makes it so it's not like $10 person. It's like $10 for everybody and then you know
But okay, so I hope it works out that last night it seems to work out
But I just want to make sure I gave summer this extra time this morning since I did you know, I make sure she gets her money's worth
Okay, and okay, so this okay, that's wrong show
$10 I've been doing I did last night. I did like $10 for like three hours
I was doing like between two and three hours
So I just threw another I threw another hour because I stayed on to like only one o'clock last night
Instead of two I was playing on stage until two
So I think I think I just might be like two twenty dollars a show and I do I'll do a six-hour show or something like that
We've got like that's what I'm thinking and then anything over six hours is like buying now
But you know, but and then else I can split it into two ten dollars
And then it will have also the advertised group.
Okay, so person, I'll make you a managing mod person.
Yeah, well the band words thing is like I think the band words is you click on the chat settings
Pull out is the word
Yeah, I
Don't know but yeah the last time they put like psyche beta
They put like terror reading who what when where how they take out any kind of like quite some people are like very quiet chat, right?
What's going on? So yeah
But everybody I put as a mod this time should have been pretty much like, you know
I'm solid with and so maybe I don't know. There's a mole. So I do apologize if you are
If you let's try I'm trying the regular chat click on the little wheel where you like do the chat settings
And then you go into chat setting that should be on the bottom of that
I guess if it had bad words, but I don't know
I don't know if it's there
Some people apparently can see it
Oh
It might not be on them on a chat one, okay, so let me see
Okay, there you go
It's called it provides oh
Um, I don't think this will not work, will it not work?
No, not really. It's really hard not having like the...
Actually, I can put it like this one.
I have to make this little...
Stop that snack.
Oh, here it is.
OK.
It'll fit in here.
So not much not too good. It's not too good, but I will get that tripod fixed today. So
I was at the Jeffrey Dahmer glasses
You have no way of doing it person. Hmm. I know well
Yeah, it's like really not I mean it's like really not necessary to be to be in there unless you know
You want to add some words, but if you want to add have any words add or suggestions?
It will just you know, it will just when people type the words then the comment will just not come up
It will just be filtered out, right?
It's just made me slanderous comments or like, you know
I have the word biscuit just because you know
Beta and somebody else like we're just there annoying me saying that word all day. That's good day. Where did they do it?
Where do you do it? Where do you wear is it usually it will say at the top of the chattel the little wheel?
It will say chat settings. It's where you can put the chat on
I see it. Let's say chat settings at the top little wheel. It'll say chat
Was a community moderation and then it will say for the channel blocked words and
then
Yeah
I put if it's certain words in there like
It's like threatening words you see
I'm gonna put like the F word just cuz I don't this just keep chat kind of like a
Little bit more like cleaned up
You guys think of words I should put in there. Hey, what's up, money for 20? Yeah, I got I got the Dahmer glasses are
Oh, hold on. You're trying to make us laugh. Oh biscuit. Oh, I know. Yeah, sweetie
I was just kidding with the biscuit. It was funny. Oh, fuck you biscuit
Top cat. Yeah
It says Top Chat and Live, let me see.
It says Live, it says Participant Mode, Message Delay,
it says Blocked Words, Community Defaults.
Okay, so I can hold potentially
an appropriate chat messages for review.
I'll turn that on just because we have so many trolls
right now.
Yeah, I have a,
just doing certain word like,
that people get called and they don't like to be called
or see like, yeah, okay.
I don't know, so if you have suggestions, I'll just make you, I'll make you a managing mod
body, hold on.
Thank you. Can you let me know what words and you'd be happy to just like I know just like words that are like
The slanderous words like you know or is that because people get killed like a you know just like
And like you know just the words we don't like have people have people accused of on the channel, right?
Me Alex the mod I don't think so. Yeah, I don't think so
But if you think of anything like, you know, if people are say, oh, you know, like just like
Overusing a word, I don't know just like bullying with a word or something like that
How many people are managing mods, it's just a few it's not very many just a few
Yeah, there's no there's no like yeah, we do have some time left today for the panel
So thank you summer. I just you guys check out the banner on the on the screen
That's what I'm gonna do for the thank you for the people that sponsor panels
I'm gonna put a thank you message like that and I'm gonna put their channel names and
Mods can put her her channels up in the chat. That'd be great, but uh and then uh
This will be it'll tell the time how long the panel will last and stuff like that
Think it'll work out. I think it'll work out because I do have like a lot of people coming in in here
So I think that you know, it's good to the banner. Well, if you have like, you know
Needs some subscriptions or something like that. I'm sure I'm sure like a lot of people would
Subscribe and it will just be there the whole time. I'll do it the whole time the panel sponsored
I think that will work out right? That's a lot of words
Not too many like you know Emma has like over a hundred downwards. We went through
Why the family names because I don't want people like I don't like people bringing up like people's family members and stuff like that
you know
It's like there's just been like personal like there's just been like, you know
How much to open the panel um, it's open it's open right now. It's open for another another it's open till another like 25 minutes
But oh, okay, so we feel love you, but it's gonna be like I think I think every I think it's gonna be like, you know
Five to six hour show it would probably be the $20. So I would split it split it into two ten dollars two ten dollar segments
Yeah, something like that. Yeah
You can see I you can say it other ways, but it's like, you know, then I then you might be are you talking about ancient Egyptian like my
Mummy, yeah, you have a mummy in ancient Egypt
Ten dollars for three hours of open of the panel being open. It's just like yeah, and but that's for everybody
It's not it's not it means like that will work. I mean that it's just ten dollars for
And it will that covers everybody. It's not ten dollars per person. It's just ten dollars. So who's live? I probably am Kate
I was like, Kate. Yeah. What do you know about 46 and 27? Okay, well, 46. Okay, well, that's
okay. So numerology, first of all, if you look at the numbers, it sounds like different
things. Like, so the word will sound like something, and you have to be kind of creative
207 or 20s even I don't know so kind of like maybe it sounds like something right 46. Yeah
Uh, 20 said, or 46 and two. Okay. No, no, it didn't say 27. It says two 46 and two. Yeah. Number two. Number two is duality
It's like the most evil number because it's the first number after the of the singularity, which is the one, right?
Um, but we did the dual world. So it's male female. It's dose, you know, you know dose DOS
It's or dough DEA UX, right dough in French
Do do
Like this, right? Hey Jan Ann. How are you sweetie?
Jan I've been having so much fun doing these AI songs. I don't know
I want to put you in a you I'll put you in one soon, but I've been making these AI songs and
Hanging out. I hope you're doing good
You got a show doing good. I
Love you Jan. I miss you. Let's see everyone doing
Why sweep you why are you like such a bad mood always why you won't be taking me back? Why what's wrong?
Sure
Yeah guys, okay, I do have I have really cool stuff too like on my I wish chat GPT had the app on
On this Kindle kindled Harley doesn't he have any uh of
The Android apps right and so it's not that great of a tablet unless you hack it
But I can pull it up on the internet
The YouTube's on this tablet really suck which is like sad
Can't have the YouTube app. It's so it makes it really hard to mod on it
Sweet pea sometimes just gets in a bad mood and then she usually comes back though. Let's just hope she comes back
Okay
So let's get into this show script, okay
Okay, so
Show outline plan
Okay
So here's the
You'll never join discord. Okay. It's pretty obvious when you're like not like so
But what sweet to your little bit like paranoid I think remember when you get paranoid sometimes like I don't think so
I think we're all being friendly today. It's actually a good chat, but if this is too much for you
Probably it's gonna be too much for you another time, too. So we love you anywhere. Ah
Here's Janet
Hi, sweet
Girls hi. Hi. How are you? Good. How are you?
Amazing
You know a in our house in our boxes being amazing
Shining bright like a diamond
You look great
Oh, you didn't know you didn't know that mr. Britney's fine, huh? Oh, I
Honey, I will say look look look look hold up. Hold up. We'll go like this. Okay, bring me back though. Okay. Oh
Okay
Whoa, oh my gosh. Oh, she's twerking off camera. Whoa
You don't get to see what I see. Oh my gosh. You don't get to see what I see guys
Yeah, I'll put you back up here you go
Yeah, wow guys the freak ops are back
Well, it was a special VIP for you. Thank you. I'm honored. I'm honored. I'm honored
Yeah, I really appreciate that
It's so ugly and zombie like we want them to keep doing that. You know what I mean?
Well, I think you look you look great and you know people always doctor photos and stuff like that
You know, you never know they've always told me, you know, there's always like an angle
I can go like I can make it itch in my eye
I don't really
I look like an ochre, you know, I always liked you with your beard, you know that right?
Oh, thank you. Pussy face, but it did look sexy and young it made you look 37
Do you like the, uh, the glasses? I mean, I'm, I'm getting the, I'm getting the Dahmer style glasses.
Oh, I'm going to return these and get the Dahmer ones. These are kind of crooked now.
Why do you want the Dahmer? Oh my God. They used to call you that in the beast sector.
Yeah. I got, I got, I got, I got like, they're like kind of like thick black ones,
but then it's like in the aviator style. They look pretty good. I think they'll look pretty good.
They look kind of like the Burberry's. These are Burberry's.
Oh, yeah, I kind of resemble those. Oh, yeah, except for the yeah, they're kind of minor like aviator, but yeah, those are cool
I like those a lot
Because you know you and Cali so you get to wear all types of sunglasses all the time
Sight because you stay sunny out there
We got to have like different ones for like like winter you wear sunglasses when this
Snows like shining off the side now. These is my superstar
Oh
Yeah, I have these I have these conneas. These are these are actually these are called Northwest or something
I think they're called these glasses like oh at their daughter. Yeah
Oh, those are nice on your face. I like that. Thank you. All line. You got a strong all on
You need to get some gel for your hair and like I know it's all dried out right now
80s like you'll see my 80 hair
Yeah
Oh, thank you school of Athens for gifting a membership. How nice of you. Thank you so much. Appreciate that
You're awesome
One member. I've been a member for a month. Yes. I saw you and you got your upgraded emoji
Thank you. Thank you for renewing also. Okay, see she's not gonna be showing her butthole on the show, okay? Oh
Oh
My god
Wow guys, you don't know what I mean. Wow. What are you? Wow. Wow. Wow. I she showed it. She showed it
That's amazing. Yes. I'm 47. It's 47 years old though. Psych. Yeah. Well, you know, it's like we're still we're still
Holding on darling the meat still holding on. Yeah
40s the new 30, I guess, right? So guess what breaking news? Let's gossip a little let's be a little
Okay, okay
Kate was over there streaming and I was over at that groovy Jimmy's and we were having fun and groovy Jimmy went over there and
Right after he got off there because the girls were attacking, you know spin spin sit spin, you know them to
Turtle and little worm. Well
Something happened and all of a sudden Kate started sprigging out and they started jumping her. Yeah, Barry in and Sam
Man trying to say they were trying to bring up a past post on her acting like they don't got sins of their fathers and
Yeah, she just literally said, you know what Sam and you're not welcome here no more
That was a big step for her
For people manipulate. You already know you are
That's why you don't see certain people around, you don't see certain people going live.
You know, and they can only talk about darkness
Yeah, and allow them to come and do what they did and I'm sorry it happened to you honestly
Because I told you if you would have stood with me honey, you'd be the ride just like the Empress I am
How to near mother did shit to nobody? Yeah, well, I mean things it has proved that you're more obsessed with me
That means I can fart in your face and you'll take
God today
Who we talking about the haters they're fan. Yeah, your haters are your fans the ones that tried to attack you
See they couldn't walk in a room and be like psych you're cool
And you had to go through like a bullying and abuse to get to where you're at
How did you feel bro? No, they came in trying to bull you and attack you and you still survive
They didn't and we learn right yeah
A lot of people didn't let you into the sector that I found you in because we found each other in the beef sector
You already were over there and I remember how the black people did you right?
But you stood your ground and you were really good
You were nice to them and you didn't do anything to them
But in return look what happened so all this does happen to you. It's gross you have
Because the hazy, right? It's a hazy. Yes, sir, right and even college they do it, right?
Yeah, they did it middle school. They did it, but these people are actually tragically
projecting their life on to you
So a lot of the stuff that they've said are done. It's because you know, you're very transparent on just being you
You told us you were on drugs. You told us you survived
And you told us you just survived stabbings and all types of crazy stuff
But you still want to help people that says a lot
Because a lot of people that are hurt they hurt other people right and yet you were hurt and still tried to help
Yeah, we'll try to herd and lie on me. You didn't see me out here. I didn't make videos about you. We talked about this
Don't y'all don't talk about me. I didn't let yeah RG on my channel
I didn't stop man's ass that man gave Jimmy over
$600 that man supported him but when he got exiled when you get removed when you tell people to go away and they have nothing
Rejection becomes obsession darling
See these people are in real time. This is all they have
So when you learn then you move accordingly because I wouldn't sit with them in real time
They don't benefit you can't benefit me and you went out and the bill was a hundred and thirty dollars
I would grab that bill you would grab that bill. We'd be up there pulling that bill together. Wouldn't we?
Yeah, for sure. Here's the school bathrooms. Have you met school bathrooms here? There we go
Nice to meet you too. I'm just keeping I'm listening to you. You speak well. I like the way you speak really well
Thank you. You said absence
Becomes obsession or like rejection becomes obsession. I like that. That was good. Well said
Yes, because again, this is all you have in the real world. No one likes you. You don't go outside
You don't engage you're locked in a box
So when then you come out here and you think that we have to accept you that we have to tolerate you and put up with
You but we don't when we're in our own homes. We don't ask you to come knock on our door
So when you come and knock on our door here, then know that you have to bring something
to the table. A lot of people don't have social character personality. They can't walk in a room
and engage with everyone. Some people just don't understand that being socially awkward means that
you can't talk to everyone and you're jealous when others can.
You're here character of a person not the color of their skin and the character of a person means that if you greet me
I'll greet you that means if you say hello nice lady. I'll say hello gentlemen
If you try to touch it you can get smacked
Don't throw a rock to try to hide your hand if you stay behind the screen
Yeah, I'll wait because you want to argue with people but your life is the facts
You can run these people for the facts of their life. They're negative and nasty because that's yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, I like how you said I'll wait to I'll wait, you know because
Waiting right and listening to somebody else. It's it's interesting. That's interesting
Yeah, they thought they were gonna wait and tell me I was ugly and tell me that I wasn't here to help site
I helped site never asked him for nothing still. Yeah, that's the thing because if you help him
I never used anything that we went through against what I loved him for
Yeah, because if we help him he doesn't owe us anything like are you are we helping?
Help him or are we helping him because you know, we want to look good
People you know
I just wanted to say thanks for the membership. Oh, I love it when it goes to like one of my boys, you know
I finally get to watch those members because I get pissed off at psyche
I'll be like, yo, this is a good stream and any membership. I can't watch that shit
Now I can watch it. I appreciate somebody bought me
One I got it like last month and it just ran out so I paid it forward, you know
Some people don't even say thank you for the membership. That was. Yeah. Yeah. That's Athens is a real one, bro. Like, you know, appreciate you kid. Yeah, no doubt, bro. No doubt. His Empress is good too. She's she's speaking truth. You know, you hear her speaking.
that right there likes to be nice.
I think you might want to apologize.
We're going to be able to make some progress today.
Never apologize, psych.
Hey, you try to sleep with a 27-year-old.
I did not, I took him off, I took him off, I took him off.
I took him off, I took him off, I took him off, I took him off.
I will say that Bronsburg and I have fought
and he never went after my children.
He keeps it straight on the Empress.
So I didn't have a problem.
R.G. did that.
I didn't know R.G. did that.
Oh, yeah, he did.
OK, I'm sorry, I didn't know.
My daughter is on OnlyFans when she's a registered nurse.
So again, sir, I don't have no problem with this man,
but he don't talk about my family.
So if he wants to drag Empress or whatever he wants to say,
he is more than welcome to.
But you won't put my children in it.
You keep it on me.
I don't I don't believe in putting kids on it. Janet been talking shit about me about the dumbest shit in the world
And I just ignore it, but I mean at the end I know you don't act like you don't come from where I come like don't act like
I don't act like you weren't on the phone with Brittany like stop. What are you talking about?
Okay, what do you mean? You didn't use to talk to me on the phone back in a day when we were friends?
Which we talk one time, bitch.
Okay, so that's how we know each other. I don't know that other man.
What the fuck are you talking about? You went on a stream y'all, like, twice.
You're a hateful, no reason.
You don't fucking like...
Your hate comes for a reason, though.
What? Hate? I don't fucking hate anybody.
Yes, you do.
You're a goofy and a bozo.
Why are you so mad?
What the fuck are you talking about?
If you only talk to me one time, what do you do then?
Because I curse. Nigga, what the fuck are you talking about? I curse. That's what I do.
I'm from New York. I'm busy sp-
I reject you. What the fuck are you talking about?
He talked to me more than one time.
No, I didn't. I don't know what you're doing.
You're all goofy, bitch.
Projection is obsession.
I rejected you. What the fuck are you talking about?
Bitch, you was the one that was crying.
Would you not be the one that was crying when I came back
when you streamed at it? Let's be real.
I've never missed you.
I didn't miss your eyes either, so it's two for two, bitch.
What the fuck do you want from me?
Wonderland is still going, and we're still empress-ing,
and you're still irrelevant.
How am I irrelevant, you came on my stream, Janet?
How am I irrelevant, you came on my streams, Janet?
What the fuck are you talking about?
I have a recording of you simping for the Empress.
You can't get out.
Simping for who, bitch?
I got the recording.
Bitch, you have a whole song dedicated to me, you goofy bitch.
Remember you dedicated the Kendrick Lamar song to me?
Hey, remember you dedicated to Kendrick Lamar song. What's up? What's song loyalty loyalty?
No, I'm not the loyalty song. It was another song some do listen. Okay. There was some dude. That was what's his name?
He convinced DNA I got I got I got I got argue
I want to speak. I shouldn't have to scream. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. He's a grown-ass man
If he only talked to me one time, why is he so angry?
He used to be in my community
psych I can pull the clip where he simped on my panel
Yeah, I understand because
Regardless of what we don't speak no more hear me out. Okay. I should not have that psyche. I'm sorry
I just want to finish, you guys are really-
Yeah, okay, I'm sorry, I apologize.
I apologize.
I apologize, I apologize.
I'm acting like you rule the world, but can't calm down.
Because again, I'm not angry at Bronzeberg. I just told you Bronzeberg can invent all he wants about how he hates Janet
Talking to me one time on the phone. He's mad that when he ran off with Mona from the UK because I took them over there
He's mad he picked the wrong bitch
Don't be mad at me that you picked the wrong bitch and you lovely nigga. I got friends. I got a man. I'm good
So again hit the like Bronzeberg and watch your mouth
Thank you
Get jumped by no men. I got my fucking Mayweather hands
I'll throw punch the fuck out of these niggas in real-time Pat. Do you understand?
I got energy that
Emasculates these gentlemen their dick gets inverted
So they're kind of respect the Empress if you don't fuck with me then why you got so much energy for me
That's all you know, you're fine. So so literally made up alive about my deaf son
Mocking my deaf son who's 28 years old that has nothing to do with nothing my boyfriend and my friend boy
That's a friend's calling right now. Give me one second
Yep
Hi, hi summer. Thank you so much. Yeah, I you know, I ended a little early last night
So I'm carrying over over your your time today
Today, so you know, I'll keep going for a
Most panel because we have Janet on so Janet, you know, if you don't know the history of Janet and I Janet was on
the show a few months ago when I was just, you know, really starting out the channel.
Okay, and Janet, is it okay? I mean, I don't, because I don't want Janet to leave,
because, uh, you know, she's kind of fighting with you. Here's summer. Hold on one second.
Yeah, summer, of course. Yeah, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on. That's Janet.
It is Jenna, yeah
You let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your pants, you let this bitch take over your
Stop speaking on Mona. Me and Mona don't talk no more. I don't have anything bad to say about that woman
It is all good. I don't want to talk about Mona
She constantly want to bring up Mona because she was jealous of Mona. That's what the fuck happened
Otherwise not this dumb goofy bitch sitting up there talking about I said this I said that I never liked this bitch
This bitch told the whole world. She was in love with me. I wasn't in love with me
Oh my god, she's on me like why the fuck why the fuck is this goofy bitch back here sit up there talking the same bullshit
Then she runs her fucking mouth about me or her bum ass panel talking about oh well
He's irrelevant and blah blah blah this bitch dedicated a whole Kendrick Lamar song to me
What the fuck we talking about this bitch act like I don't have clips this bitch cried when I was on a panel with Mona
And when I sit up there talking about oh why why he did that why did she started shit with Mona?
Mona sent they come back to me like yo, Bronzeberg. What what the fuck is is is Janet talking about you for blah blah blah and lying on me to Mona
Mona even here Mona been gone for like a whole fucking month or a year
This is the shit that I gotta deal with this goofy dumb bitch from Pittsburgh. You think I still feel sorry for this lame-ass bitch?
Oh, she's in Pittsburgh. She gets dragged out from mad people in the beef sector and got the nerve to sit up there and talk shit about
Bronzeberg. I run a way better channel than your goofy ass channel, bitch. I got fucking 20 people that be in my chat on average.
How many people you got in your fucking chat? Five! Motherfucker, who the fuck you talking about?
You ain't shit and fuck you in that jail bird boyfriend you going out with you dumb bitch. Who the fuck you talking to?
Mad cuz you gonna sit up there talk and then this bitch got the nerve to talk about I jerked off to her in a fucking
Streamyard this is bitch dumb this bitch was in a shower with cigarettes
Nigga offered to suck my dick and sit up there and live with her the fuck is she talking about?
I wish this bitch would lie on me, I'ma drag this bitch, this bitch is a goofy, stop fucking
lying on me bitch, and go tinny your fucking jailbird boyfriend motherfucker, fuck outta here.
I'm surprised someone from Pittsburgh wouldn't let me on the panel, I'm from Pittsburgh too
Janet, you said I was, I'm not letting this white boy on, I was like what the fuck?
What is that actually going out with groovy come on Janet you're a desperate bitch from Pennsylvania every fucking man
That pays attention. She wants to go out with y'all don't understand the cycle of this bitch
Fuck you talking about she's a desperate bitch a middle-aged bitch from Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania
So I dodged a bullet. She said yeah mad people dodged a bill bullet
Ever came on to you. That's because she was desperate and she was looking for a man
She's like what she's like wait for it
That's the reason why she said that because she was looking for a man to replace her dead husband
That's not me who said that shit. She said it
So again, this bitch want to lie on me. I got something for that ass. You know why I got clips motherfucker
Fuck you talking about you don't think I got screenshots. Nick has been had screenshots, bro
But my thing about it is you're not gonna lie on me and think I'm gonna take it
And then you want to sit up there and psychologically manipulate psyche into putting me backstage now. We're not doing that
I'm a real one. Don't ever fucking forget that this bitch whole profile is lame. She's a fucking goofy ass bitch
Fuck are we talking about?
And psyche you won't put me backstage for this goofy bitch
There's a stripper backstage
Talk about you at least if I talk about you I talk about you on the fucking chair. I brought you right back, okay?
You really you really need this you really need to realize who you
I think so she apologize, huh? Did she apologize to you? I never I mean
I don't have I never heard particular things about I don't know what was said
Apologize to you psyche. I'm sure she did. I think she did. She did
We made we made up because you ran to her, you know, she likes attention
Well, I don't know what happened
Hey, he's there to say anything. Okay, anything that I don't know. No, no, it's a figure of speech when I say say last
But that's crazy to me that you won't let this goofy bitch Janet talk shit on you
But I'm the fucking problem. I don't I don't care people talk shit about me. Everyone talks shit
Well, how is that how is that crazy when you're gonna sit up there and be friends with someone who's a backstabber?
Well, I think you know, that's who you're dealing with a fucking backstabber by the name of Janet
Okay, well, you know, she I don't think she really ever backs up that she was she was mad
I understand why she was mad at me a certain times. Maybe like, you know, I forgive her
And she doesn't need to apologize I forgive her anyway, okay
You say you say all these different things about how you don't care. You don't care
You don't care, but then you constantly reference it when it happens to you
Yeah
You complained about it psyche
You complained about it. So why is it a different book because this goofy bitch?
Janet is here. Why is it?
You're coming on like attacking Janet the whole time. I really don't want people to talk to Janet
Janet started a bullshit with me and bringing up fucking Mona like she's fucking new news
That's I mean, I don't know anything about that person
But no one knows
Nipulated to narcissists like fucking Janet. That's just crazy. And the thing about it is she really thinks she's getting off by doing this shit
And she's doing the same fucking thing everybody in your chat tells you the same thing about this office
I'll just do is chatting with us
Guess she's trying to control your channel. She's not you like it, bro
I mean, I was letting her be a guest because she's a bit awkward look at lose
I got five people in the chat talking shit about my page explain
She wanna go to groovy jimmy, she's fucking with groovy jimmy cause she wants clout
That's the reason why she's here, man
Pay attention
I don't sit up there and say this shit for no reason
No, I can't stand janet
Cause janet fucking lied on me
And janet sat there and talked about I'm a stalker
And constantly wanted to bring up some old ass girl I don't talk to no more
It's crazy
And then you know when she's on a page
Oh, I got bronzebird upset, blah blah blah
Bitch, you can never
You can suck my dick from the back
and my whole ball sack bitch
cause I know you want to do that anyway you low life bitch
fuck you talking
pull my name out your mouth and suck my dick
yeah
Are you off the phone? Janet's on the I guess she's on the call still a squad anybody here
Hey, is everybody really have something to say I don't think she's trying to control my panel
But I was just like they know letting her like not to use she said she's gonna leave
But I she's been here for a while. I just wanted her to hit what she wanted
And but we can all be on the panel now and talk one at a time
Yeah
I always got you backwards. You know that. Thank you. Thank you summer, but let's let's my fault y'all
I didn't mean to break that shit up. I just don't like bullshit. So what I was cool to add this money in summer
What I'm not much not much I watched the video before summer was nice. No Kings
The
Excellent excellent you spoke really well up on the steps and then I watched it parade to my mom and I watched
I watched with her like a half hour of it and then I was heading home and I hopped on
Really great
Yeah, it's beautiful Saturday here in Los Angeles, I'm a oh there's Moshe my fan Moshe who said everyone like should like join up
And go to war with me. I saw you say that in the other chat Moshe
Why are you calling people to have a war with me? What's wrong with me Moshe like right really?
I am a weirdo on King David. You said I should be killed in the name of King David or something like that or I'm alive
That's all you say that Moshe this guy Moshe said that in in a damn better case chapter out
It was or be yeah, I think it was um Kate's chat
Okay, hey, what's up Janet?
I don't know if you've heard any of that, but, but, uh,
Bronzeberg said, or you want to respond, or...
What? Boy, we're moving right along.
Hi, Summer, and hi, Money420.
Yeah.
So it has been a while like
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to like leave him off so long. I do apologize for my fault my bad. I apologize
Okay, and so yeah, so money for 20. Do you know Janet?
Yeah, it was moving right along for the fact
I don't give a fuck what you're talking about you dirty ass fucking bitch
What else do you both want from me now bitch?
What else do you want from me now bitch?
Your face looks like an asshole bitch
You weird looking motherfucker
Fuck the fuck up bitch
You a nutman fucking bitch
Nobody fucking likes you
Nobody fucks with you
You're fake as fuck
You look like a fucking ass
Shut up bitch
Shut the fuck up bitch
You ain't gonna do a lot of damn things, but when you motherfuckin' that mouth, bitch, you can dance with that ass fuckin' nuthin' ass bitch, you a nuthin' ass bitch, you a nuthin' ass bitch, bitch, you a nuthin' ass bitch, bitch, you a nuthin' ass bitch, bitch, you a nuthin' ass bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch, bitch
I don't know why nobody's ever come up here and say anything, bitch!
Why fuck you, bitch?
Fuck you, bitch!
Why the fuck did I do that?
How did you sit here and talk to everybody on this motherfucker?
You've talked about everybody over here, bitch!
Fuck you!
Nobody's scared of you, bitch!
You talk about everybody, bitch!
You thought I wasn't gonna come over here?
I've been waiting for you over here to come over here, bitch!
What the fuck you, man?
What the fuck did you say?
Did you talk about everybody?
What the fuck are you?
What the fuck is this?
You don't want to trade, bitch!
You don't want to trade!
You don't want to talk to me, bitch!
No one can say fuck, bitch!
Who gives a fuck?
Who talks about everybody over in this motherfucker?
You ain't doing shit over in this bitch thing,
so what you fuckin' thought, bitch?
What you thought, bitch?
Fuck you, bitch.
That's what you said.
This bitch go out for the next three seasons because you don't want to spray home.
You take a break, you thought he was gonna come over here and just come here and he wanted to see boo.
He's not talking about everybody over here. Fuck you, bitch.
Fuck you, bitch.
Fuck you.
asshole bitch shut the fuck up you look like a walking asshole you look like a walking asshole you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look like a walking asshole bitch you look
You got shit on us motherfuckers man, always looking for a man on an Indian, goofy bitch.
You know, in the way of this, hey, cause you ain't got no fucking man you can really stay with.
You said that you went up there, motherfucker.
You ain't got no shit.
You ain't got no fucking shit.
Don't push the thing now!
Somebody patch me!
Somebody patch me, bitch!
You rascal-looking bitch!
Shut up, fuckin' bitch!
If you don't see what I want from you, thank God, bitch!
Shut the fuck up!
Shut up, bitch!
Come over here
And hang out with everybody!
No bitch! We don't like you!
Please don't like you!
Don't fuck yourself bitch!
Please don't like you Janet!
Bye bye!
Nobody likes you bitch!
Nobody likes you!
You're not supposed to want it bitch!
Bye bye!
I got ass out, son of a bitch.
Garret, Garret, fucking T.
Fuck you, you got the moisturizer on your head, baby.
Fuck you, you got the moisturizer on your head.
I got two balls in my head!
Talk about me, bitch!
Talk about me while you're there, bro!
You said fuck it!
You got mad!
Yeah, I could drive!
You can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man, you can't drag a shit man
Who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch, who's the son of a bitch
How many people want to fuck Danny bitch? Shut up you watch the fuck I can't ask bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up bitch. Shut the fuck up
You could be in a U2 or a bitch!
Just the fuck that you watched a bitch!
Fuck the fuck up bitch!
You have the fuck up here!
You thought you was gon' come back over!
Bitch, y'all daddy's dead!
Shut up!
Suck a dick, bitch!
No one gives a fuck!
Fuck your daddy, daddy bitch!
Fuck your daddy too, bitch!
I'm gonna punch your motherfuckers for this and I'm gonna bet you I should know if I give a fuck with these men.
If I give a fuck with these men, I'm mad to be in the new two water.
I'm mad to be in the new two water.
Jimmy.
I'm mad to pass her around on these new two water.
I'm mad to be in the new two water.
Cigarettes, my guy! Let's talk about that, you son of a bitch!
What the fuck, bitch?
Fuck outta here!
The path around a huge school, baby, can it!
The only thing I know that's open up-
That's the only thing you can dig, that's the only thing you can import, son of a bitch!
Fuck off, bitch!
If you don't, bitch!
What the fuck is that?
Slap it!
Slap it, bitch!
What's your love life?
You've been ugly since the day I met you.
That's your love life, bitch.
You ain't in my shit.
It ain't nothing, bitch.
It ain't nothing, you all.
Shut the fuck up.
Shut up, bitch.
Shut the fuck up, bitch.
like you guys can we do one at a time can we do one at a time
we can't do one at a time
then it looks like you think
then it's a pass-around youtube bitch she looks like she's thinking dirty bitch
she's a fucking e-hole
yeah e-hole ass bitch
the man could be in a hole on youtube bitch
you have to suck it up bitch
he's an e-hole she went out with a jailbird
And the jail bird still dumped her make that
All right. Nobody wants that bitch.
Nobody wants it.
Sikey. Let's go.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're speaking one to one.
We speaking one to one.
Hold on.
Speaking one to one.
That's what we're doing.
This bitch is a low life loser.
This bitch.
Let me talk.
This bitch can offer to me to live with a friend that you really want.
Everybody's slandering her?
We all want to walk, look at that bitch, look at her.
But you don't know how much makeup you put on,
you still look like a walking asshole, bitch.
You look like a walking asshole, bitch.
And look, that big old mouth,
and you still can't suck dick,
because you can't kick a man.
That big ass mouth, and you still can't suck dick, bitch.
You still can't suck dick with that big ass mouth.
You can't kick a man.
Nasty as bitch. You can't wash up in fake bitch. Everybody on YouTube doesn't have you bitch.
Everybody on YouTube has you bitch. Everybody on YouTube has you bitch.
Look at big ass, nasty ass now. You're looking like a fucking horse bitch.
You got horse mouth bitch. You still can't keep a man.
Really, you can't suck dick. Really, you can't not suck dick because you can't keep a man.
You can't suck dick, bitch. You're worthless.
I got an online boyfriend because I'm such a worthless bitch, nobody wants me.
You know you was going to come over here and just sit down right up there and run in your mouth about everybody else and write nobody going to say that to you bitch.
Say that man.
Man, I hear these things.
You wish you could be on a group Z.
You're not in the bad bitch category.
You're a white trash for 17 years.
Where's your marriage?
You're a white trash.
If you forget, you're not black.
You're a mixed bitch.
You're black.
No.
Nobody wants you, black people don't want you, white people don't want you, bitch, imagine. Imagine, bitch. Imagine, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody wants you, bitch. Nobody
Shut up bitch
It's been years I've been sucking his dick, but he ain't going nowhere, I like you, bitch.
You can't do that. You can't do that, bitch.
You got 17 years I've been with the same motherfucker, bitch.
Try and get in. Try and get in. You watch that, bitch.
Try and get in, bitch.
You can't travel in the same commitment.
You can never. You can never.
Nobody wants you, bitch.
Nobody wants you.
How does it feel, Janet?
No one wants you, bitch.
No one wants you.
On the fucking internet bitch said all you are that's it. Oh, you were evil
Nothing, you still don't know how to suck a dick right to keep a man
That's what you are
Excited because a man
This bitch talk about I have a date
You're not you're not bitch. You desperate
Open your face like an asshole. That's what you look like an asshole. I have a life
Big ugly asshole this bitch you this bitch want to mention Mona Mona is ten times better looking than you and you was jealous of her
You want to explain that Janet? Yeah, she's still my friend. She's not your friend. She don't like you
You're pathetic. You're pathetic. You're pathetic.
You don't know how you're not going to learn it, right bitch? You're pathetic.
You're pathetic. You're pathetic.
You're pathetic.
Sorry summer sorry summer sorry hold on and Bronzeberg. Okay, you guys okay guys you guys had a chance to speak if you want to come back on
I just want to let the old friendship was
First of all she said that I was supposed to listen to what Bronzeberg said, but like I told you I was on the phone
So whatever he said I said moving right along. That's all she didn't have to jump in but she wants to
You don't like me. I don't care moving right along. I'm here for you like they can't make me go away
No
Janice
All right, all right
Talking about
Bitch that talked about you. We ain't we at least kept it real with you and you won't have this bitch
Priority straight
But that bitch in a bag
Man fuck that bitch back for a second. Okay, but guys, I'll put it back as long as I put it summer back
So it'll be even okay, okay?
You do this and you sit up there and ride over the bitch that talk about you at least me and some I say the shit to your face
We keep it
Bronson, let me run my own panel. Can I just I just okay? I'm gonna bring her back and then I'll address that
Okay
I'm talking to you.
I don't give a fuck.
You talk about him all the time.
What is he apologizing to you for?
I want to have a conversation with you.
I don't give a fuck.
You want to run his panel.
I don't care, Janice.
That's fine.
First thing, did you not come to my panel and we talked?
Did we? Yeah, we talked, we talked, we talked, but did we, did we address like, did you, did I not apologize for her? Yeah, she, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did, she did,
You fake-ass
Supposedly apologize to you and then talk shit about you again. This is the money you're rolling with
You're riding out
Productive if everyone's screaming, okay
I can't hear I can't hear anybody talk I've ever talked to you. I'm sorry
I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about you, I don't give a fuck about
I'm trying to have a
Prison boyfriend like you always do bitch. I don't give a fuck about you
I don't give a fuck about your opinion either
Okay
Stop
You're a lame-ass bitch, and you know it you sit around and talk about every fucking body and you want to try to act like you're somebody
But you're a nobody you're a pastor around on fucking YouTube and understand that that's all you will ever be bitch
Your projection is that's it. No, baby. I'm married 17 years. It's married. You can never do that in 17 years
Everybody
Horts face ass bitch. That's what you are
Okay, so me Goddy so Empress this is
I don't believe that happened.
But you would never lay your mouth on me bitch, you tried, you tried to hit on me bitch, you tried bitch, you tried bitch, I would never, you never, you tried to hit on me bitch, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried to hit on me bitch, you tried bitch, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried bitch, I would never, you tried
You can never touch me ever.
I'm one person on the online.
You can have it.
Down those.
Okay, I just want everyone.
We can go at a time and everything out.
Everybody got everything out.
She's a horse face.
Okay, well, maybe we can make some
progress.
You two could be besties.
Now I'm good
You try to act like you're fucking tough bitch, you ain't tough.
Now when the real tough bitch steps up to you, what fucking horse face are you gonna ask bitch?
Bitch, please.
Bitch, you can act like you're fucking tough.
And don't let me to goddamn say bitch, I work out every day too bitch, and I'll crack your goddamn soul wide open, bitch.
Understand?
Rubik's Cod, bitch! Come on, bitch!
Come on, you fucking horse face bitch!
Rubik's Cod, bitch.
Come on, bitch!
Real support
Knock out
I'm going to punch somebody a lot.
I'm going to punch the screen.
I'm going to punch the screen at you.
This is what happens when you shoot up here
and you jerk off men.
That's what you do.
That's exactly it.
That's who's look like that.
Okay, guys.
Oh my God, now it's your butt.
Yeah, she's twerking.
This is what I mean. She wants attention. How am I missing this? Come on. Because I only I can see it only I can see it
She doesn't every man she likes
Are you going to airpunch again?
Are you going to airpunch me?
Are you going to airpunch me again?
Where is your thick heart?
Airpunch, airpunch, airpunch again.
Come on, airpunch again.
You stupid ass bitch.
This is good to suck about.
Because you want to suck my dick, right?
I remember.
You want to suck my dick.
You want to be the fuck.
You want to be the fuck, didn't you?
Let's talk about that.
Virtually
bitch! You're not mad! Watch some Alan Black lookin' ass bitch!
I'm talking about this bitch like I'm a two-year-old. Summer is married for over 17 years.
You could never, bitch! You could never! Never!
People are looking for a man on the stream yard. Make it make sense.
Let's compare this. A married woman to a desperate hoe. Who is more of a loser?
You're not even going to sucky dick.
You're the donkey on the corner that somebody fucked for five bucks, bitch!
Take the roll, man.
Yo, what the fuck?
Jared out here sucking dick to 80 man, I paid his attention.
That's why you do the groovy thing.
Try not to suck any dick on your way out to the parking lot.
You're the donkey on the corner, bitch! Everybody pays five dollars to fuck, bitch!
That's it!
We ain't got nothing!
Donkey, donkey ass, bitch!
Look at his middle-aged bitch put her on a leg over.
You suck 37 dicks.
You're boring.
You're boring, bitch.
Not as bad as the dick.
And look, he's hitting the boomerang.
Let's see this one.
B is coming out your fucking dick, bitch.
Whoa, look at this shit.
Look at this shit.
Is somebody turning?
Oh, yes.
Hey, take that banner off so we can fear.
Take the banner off.
Oh, my God.
Y'all bruh.
What the fuck?
Yeah, you lost this one.
Are you going to just swim?
Ding, ding, ding.
He's out.
I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't have to drive any way on it. I don't
You can't keep a man, bitch.
Damn.
I'll be leaving there.
Turn for a minute.
Show us that flat ass you got, bitch.
You got such a black pay you like that.
What's the funny thing about this?
This is the funniest part, bro.
Come on!
I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I see it's over. I
Come on
She's mad cuz it's my bitch. I'm not I'm into entertaining watching you look like a fucking clown and you're falling forever
She just that's what she just basically demonstrated how much of the ego she is that's what she did
Make it make sense my guy
what we needed you to do today, bitch.
You did exactly what we wanted you to do.
You did exactly what I wanted you to do.
You did exactly what I wanted you to do, man.
He controlled you, bitch.
That's your highlight of the day?
Yeah, it is.
That's a great highlight.
You guys are all welcome.
Yeah, you're making an ass out of yourself.
You just proved our point. You just proved you were eager, dummy.
Oh fuck you did all that representation for Rod Rax and he still dumped you. How do you feel about that?
My business. I'm the celebrity and you're talking. You're not a celebrity
I don't know nothing about you much. You're lying
Dingleberry
Are you an actress
Craft
I got a master's in a in a dope entertainment
This bitch Janice son
Janice
Oh
She's sweating the whole attire Tom she had a nice workout look at us
You didn't look crazy, bro!
You stayed behind the screen. That's all you did.
You got there right, I did, bitch.
I let you hit a superstar!
Hold on, wait a minute!
That same man said, bitch, I let you hit a superstar!
You hit a superstar, baby!
You hit a superstar!
When I leave here, I'm still gonna be happy and you're still
Where do you want this attention bitch you want this attention you ain't going nowhere
No one cares guys. Hold on. Do you know Samman? I'm Empress. Here's your Samman and then
Oh
We don't care, bitch.
We don't give a fuck.
Four times you said you're gone.
Bad bitch!
You and your dick suck your hands, bitch.
We love you, bitch.
Rest some more!
You're not one in here, bitch.
Don't let the touch screen hit you on the ass on the way out.
I can't make it late, damn. Shout to the cook up.
Damn, I can't make it late.
Y'all was cooking.
I cut that bitch, and she was sweating.
That bitch was sweating, you know?
She pretended to suck dick in the hair.
She fucking sucked with no hands.
This bitch ain't got no A.T. in her crib, the man she fucking right now, she ain't got an A.T.
She said she got a master's in pornography.
Yo, please, somebody donate to Janice, a fucking cash app.
We need the A.T.
Why this bitch an A.C., why this bitch an air conditioner crib?
She fuck all these men and she can't buy a fucking air conditioner?
God bless.
God damn.
That's just crazy work.
So that's a Jamie Cowboys. Hope everything's good with you Jamie. I heard me girl
That's healing yeah, that's crazy shit. Yo, I'm crying I can't
And you can't even buy air conditioner bitch
Who's a married woman this bitch searching around for men on the internet and especially me
But down is gonna be always a bust down. That's just what it is
We put on my AC right now. Just
What's the overrun there when she comes back you think how long it'll take it until she comes back
You know, she's gonna end up coming back coming back. I don't know. Yeah, I'm actually supposed to be leaving out soon
But you know, I didn't mean it. I did not the for the record. I did not mean for the conversation go to Janet
I just she went right at you. She went right at you as soon as you came up. I don't like Janet
Yo, I don't like people who lie on me. You know what I mean and then bring up people
I don't talk to me anymore
She definitely seems scorned at you that she definitely
Listen all I have to say was she was crying
She's not tough she cried over me I've seen it at least three times she was
Like you're not gonna talk to me sideways, I made her cry and I don't take back shit I said fuck that bitch
First of bitches those are the dumb bitches you dealing with psyche
So summer just dropped off. Okay, well, thank you summer that was that was it
I mean say that's what people, you know, it's the guy I think it did make for compel a radio
So that's why it's like sometimes people on that are controversial, you know, it's like
people that hopefully, you know
It's like she'll come back again soon. So right now. We'll have another chat. We're up Amanda. Hey sassy. Hi, Christine
Irby, what's up? Yeah. Hey, Sam. Yeah, what's what I think I was
I came too late for the cooking the bark y'all wanted the plate would quit you feel me?
Yeah, well, she started her own she started alive. I guess maybe you can
She's gonna wind up bitching and complaining about oh, sorry, sorry
There's some respect. Yeah
These different things about me and summer
Then see what'll happen as her people come over to my channel see who I am and you know
It's just a part of the routine. That's how it goes. She didn't so I'm sorry
I'm sorry to put Irby into this
She just sat there has some fucking goofball sit up there start with Irby on my channel for no fucking reason
They're gonna talk about Irby's a backstabber to Janet because her stuff dumb ass rules
Oh, don't be going over to ops channels and blah blah blah like
You think I'm really offended by some goofy bitch that got 3k subs and only 4-5 people watch her streams and she talks shit about my channel?
I have more of a full panel than she ever does.
Are you kidding me?
That should be dead.
When she talks about you all the time slaggy she sits over here and talks about every fuck a body over here
Ever since you didn't come back like I don't know why you left like come back and chat
Remember this you put me in some in the back for this goofy
So this is there that everybody, I just need to be able to like, you know, like, just like
try to do people one time.
I'm sorry.
Well, I will try to stop.
I'll try to stop that.
I'll try to stop.
No, no, I didn't.
I'll try to come back on.
Come back on now, Empress, or if you want to, or do you want to come back when there's not as many people here?
Okay, I was having a nice conversation with her. I wanted to talk about some things
I never got to ask my questions and stuff like that
I wanted to address like so like what if she did talk about me or whatever, but it's like you know, she did
But I just want to like and then maybe like that we can get a lot out and I just wanted to ask her that but I
Didn't have a chance to say anything. It's not really productive when everyone is yelling at once
Okay, I know I don't you say you see here and you tell us
Oh, I don't give a fuck if people talk about me and people talk about me
And then you run to the channel people's talking shit about you about I don't always no, I don't I don't usually
You went over fucking Janice and did that shit, bro. When?
Oh my god, bro. I wasn't a chance. I didn't say today
I said I said you have a constant theme of doing this and then you put us backstage when we keep it real with you
But the motherfuckers that talk shit about you
And you let you shut your bad bad thing me in my panel stop it. Okay. Hold on. I
Do miss you. I do miss you and for like Empress is like saying she'll never come back. Thank you
Why why are you bad at me like now see?
You don't need to come back here
She's gonna talk about you anyway. You have some people that support you and really support you psyche
Don't support you and you sit up there signing that shit, bro
But I bet it's like I don't care if people like
Because I really I mean it's just like I don't feel like it. She said maybe anything that bad like a lot
She said nothing that so you make an excuse as far as what you doing. Oh, it's like, you know, hey, what's up Vita?
How are you sweetheart? Yeah, so
Come on up Vita if you can
It was
She's making fun of you to a whole audience that doesn't even know you
My gosh, she was
Janet why are you doing that? Why do you talk shit about everybody Janet like I thought we're like all supposed to be like
And it took a while. I don't want to be over that channel is drama
Psychic I'm telling you these are the type of people
I'm not in this board by the way does FYI she does this shit on her regular fucking panel
She talks shit about every fucking body all the time on her panel. I don't I don't belong in any discord
I'm in this court, but I don't fuck that I learned my lesson a lot of time ago. What's for it?
My my peeps. I'm a peace out. It's about the gold peace out to everybody
It appears
Hey that forward bronze pay forward if you can love you later, bro. Hi yo peace out
Okay, so now it's a little it'll be a little quieter Janet if you want to try one more time, but
Okay, I'll be in a chat if you want to she wanted to peacefully want to get the one-on-one with summer
Yeah, I'll let you want to talk to me if you want to talk to me again
It's fine. Yeah, we can like have it like quieter chat. It'll be like, you know, but I apologize if I'm not like
Working the panel. I love you. Yeah, I love you summer. Thank you so much
You know, especially for for a sponsor in the panel
I did put your banner up again for like an hour this morning if everyone subscribed to
Hot mess summer and talk your ish if a mod could put those channels in my chat
So everyone can subscribe to hers give you a beat as wrench. No, I'm not going to pit say but you are a member
So I just want to shout you out beat as a mod. Hey, nobody who did so he's gone
Everyone doing in chat. Hey, nobody
Hey Athens, hey Summer, and hey LES, what's up guys?
What up, what up, what up?
I did want to address stuff with Jenna, and I don't think she's like, I've talked to her on a private,
and she's always been pretty kind to me on a private, you know, talking in private, like, personally.
Yeah, but in public she talks shit about you, so just so you know.
Yeah, I know she was very upset with me and so she uh sometimes people say things when they're upset like maybe she was
Yeah, I don't know. I just wanted everyone to get along and like forgive each other
Some people okay, okay
There's summer's channel
Yeah, you just missed Janet. You just missed Janet's appearance. You're going to rewind
and see. Janet's appearance and there's a talker-ish. Okay? Everyone subscribe to the
list.
It's an ankle beat-up.
Yeah, it'll be down. Yes. We all troll each other. We all do our thing or whatever
But like she literally sits over there
She talks shit about every fuck a body and then she'll let nobody on panel don't let nobody on chat
You know me fuck a bitch. We're just looking at us bitch
Well, it's gonna be a cast around on fucking YouTube and you big-ass mouth like that
She can't even suck dick good enough to keep a dude like what is wrong with that?
I
Wasteful of a big mouth man, cuz I know my fuckers look at that big ass mouth like that
I bet she's a suck dick. Nope. She can't as well. She can't keep a man
Well, so can I ask you? How was the how was the crowd and stuff like like being there?
But yeah, that was good really cool stuff
Yeah, well, okay, so hopefully everyone's having exactly TV. She said I still believe that I should have her say but on her own panel
Maybe she'll start a sort of panel I think I thought she was going to someone said she had scheduled one when she's during the show
But she's probably talking shit here. Let's see. I was
Fuck it summer fucking I can hear it now
I love it.
It's great.
Yeah.
Let me see.
Have a great day.
I'm psyching you.
People aren't slandering me.
You're repeating this.
I did not see one person say one thing about you in the chat today.
Okay?
Nope.
I did not see one person.
Not with anybody.
Did anybody see anybody slander scum?
No.
Did I call it?
Vida Veracuda, when she got the biggest mouth and nastiest seat.
Okay.
Come on.
That's not very nice of a stage.
You don't call people any kind of like a...
Names her new boyfriend by the way is gonna be Jimmy. Oh, yeah, I didn't see like
So it's 27 and I don't think the big age difference 27 is pretty much like late 20s
They're good. I guess I can be someone in the 40s
You see easy. That's just because we know you're okay. The girl it's cheap is a little bit big today off my shoulder
Oh, it's okay, so I know
I'll be so but yeah, I mean, I guess it's been a
Astrology or something that could be in the stars to be like a little bit everyone's a little bit on edge or sensitive lately
It's the middle of summer. It's like called the dog days of summer
The serious galaxies that can charge or something like that
One thing when the universe and everything others like what the fuck is it called Gina always would say
forget what a line alignment and everything's aligned or
the mercury or something like that mercury retrograde yes that's it yeah you know if you
like some of the mercury retrograde or how are we saying it is oh yeah yeah it because mercury is
the planet of communication and it's like the fastest moving planet but when it's in retrograde
so it's going backwards it's like it uh the communication gets all wonky and like there's
a lot of misunderstandings and there's a lot of like technical difficulties during those retrograde
So it's just started. It just started right? There's one right now. Yeah, I can't look it up like like it just started
Today's Saturday, yes
Somebody was talking about it on
It's currently in retrograde having entered its phase on July 17th and lasting till the 11th of August
Yeah, and it says about Mercury retrograding in case you're interested in it. It says
Let me see if it gets a good description of it
Do you know?
It says understandings miscommunications delay messes, right? Yeah, exactly. So that's because that's because it's like it's like
Mercury, so it's the planet of all the communication and you know commerce dealing with people
So yeah, so there might be something things always happen. There's always like some misunderstandings like you're like always always like Mike
It can be a heightened time of emotions, anxiety, and overwhelm for some people, it says.
Be mindful, tech glitches, malfunctions.
How often does it happen a year?
That happens like a lot. Yeah happens like a guy does captain quite a lot
It says because it is the quickest planet to orbit mercury retrogrades more than any other cosmic body
Entering its backwards spin three and four so times a year. We know this energy
Well, we've been breathing moving and dancing with mercury retrograde. It's our first breath
Something innate within us is attuned to the wisdom and medicine of it
Yeah
I want to ask you a question does mercury not I know it um revolves but does it not rotate doesn't it not rotate?
You see what it looks like
Yeah, I mean, it's like it's spinning backwards basically and going the other direction
So it's a completely going the other way. See that's what that's the pattern looks like right there. Oh, it's cool, man. Yeah
Uh, is there anything else about it? It says yeah, and this is the second one of this year
And it says that astrology mercury rules the mind. It's communication,
mental processing, learning, and memory. It's the framework of through we wish
or pre-perceive our life, ourselves, our experiences, and our future. Okay? And then
it says retrogrades our necessary step back, necessary step that brings us a
faster perspective from which we can take a more expanded intention,
consciousness, and alignment with what lies ahead.
If an inward reflection and reconnection truly matters to us, there is space to disconnect
from the many messages of how lives should look so that we can instead listen to the quiet whisper
within us of how our lives should feel. Think of Mercury retrograde as any planet in retrograde
as refueling, reorienting, realigning, and return to the inner so that we are moving through the
outer. We are certain to move in our truth. Here we go. It takes 59 Earth days to complete one
And, due to its slow rotation, a single day on Mercury is 176 Earth days.
Interesting.
Yeah, because you would think it would be quicker, but like you said, it's going backwards, so it fucks everything up.
You know all this shit.
Well, it's just a little bit. It's kind of like the most notorious kind of retrograde because there's also like Mars retrograde
And their planets go retrograde, but Mercury's the fastest one. So are the closest to the Sun closest to the Sun
So it's kind of like very important planet
Yeah
Hi, Vita. Hi, Brian. Sweet pea Christine. Wow. We got a lot of people here. We have we it was quite a
There's quite a little show show part of the show right there. It's pretty
Interesting way to open a Saturday. You know, you don't know what's gonna happen though
I was just saying that it was okay for bird to be able to say something when somebody's talking shit about her
Him and she didn't like that. And so she wouldn't talk shit. So I thought she'd back
I got you. Yeah, and you and you and everyone can you know have their say here, you know, it's like
I've always thought she's a weird ass bitch, but you know, that's why I ain't really fuck with her
Even what she was here the last time because she just she doesn't like she just she's got a snakey personality
Yeah, I mean she brought it
She seemed like she brought a lot of drama to the thing and it's like, you know
It was a little bit too much having her as it was like a weird time for me
You know, I was just getting started and
It's everybody else's fault like everybody else is doing it
You know, I mean like she she does a bunch of dumb shit and she doesn't want to have her taking accountability for it
So, yeah, she's just so she's a weird bitch
Her energy reads naked
Yes
Yeah, well, yeah, well, what is that reptilian? Well, did you see like the
Think the triptake I think triptake or something does the who does like those the AI like things like
Put her as the Crip Keeper. That was pretty
Love you, Vita
Hi, Vita
Uh, yeah, so it was it. It's just a conversation. It was kind of like, you know, it's hard, it's hard having a panel sometimes because it's like, wait, and like just digitally when like so many people are talking, you really can't understand, you can't focus on one or understand one.
And so it was like, it was just going for a long time. So I do apologize.
So, don't take it for yourself.
I get it, I remember, I put people in the back,
I ain't mad at that shit at all by any way,
but in the moment, cause I'm hot and I'm a little hot head,
I'll be like, God damn it's like, what the fuck?
Cause I'll be like, why you, you know, like,
especially when I'm cooking a bitch, like, I don't,
but I get it.
And I'm not sending you it off.
Thank you, thank you, love you.
So,
So how's everyone Saturday? I went and got a bagel with locks and I have like a oh, yeah
So, you know, I made that a that the Alex and Paige song like I put I like
I want to hear that. Do you want to hear that one? Yeah, I'll play this. This is so funny
This is the Alex and Paige song. Okay. Oh, it's called. Yeah
Walks a beat in the city light
Flashing blues under New York nights
But his heart's up north
Where the rivers run free
With a blonde hair, beauty from April Country
He's got a badge of dream
And a thing for a laugh
Caught a glimpse of her smile
Now he's doing the math
From the Bronx to the Bush
Oh, he's thinking real deep
Paige, are you the one
I've been missing in my sleep
Paige!
He said she's gunning trout
He's eating steak somewhere in the middle
They both take a break
He'd trade his knife stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol
Oh Paige, don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Blend our flags and plant a tree
I'll hold you close like a holding line
Give you my heart and maybe my spine
I'm just a cop
Living country dream of bonfires, beer and a northern war
Say good girl, give me that key
I will see you.
I think that's a cute song. It's funny.
A little contest or whatever and maybe have everybody do songs or whatever and send them in and that way you can get different versions, you know what I mean?
Yeah, and then people yeah, people can yeah guys you can start making like songs too and like you know
Come on and have it played and stuff like that or something send me the link on discord or put it backstage and I can
I can start you know, we can all do songs, you know
And just like I like
I'll teach you how to do it. I'll teach you how I do it and then it's not too hard
I swear everyone could do it, right?
Katrina's made a couple. We've we've got a cut. We've made a couple. Uh, well Katrina makes food, but yeah, it's cool
I think we're all pretty uh, we're all talented and we all could all like have uh, you know within the combination with the AI
It would like maybe make some interesting and funny things in content. So good idea summer. Thank you
Let me fix my how does
Well, what looks the best is this look best or is that look best or
Maybe a blue because you have a blue, you know back in the sky. Yeah
Oh
There we go, how about that? I like that
It's not express. Yeah, that looks good. Yeah. Oh, yeah, what's pink in the pre-outer? Yeah, that's it
Oh perfect
Hey, Brian, we had so are you okay, Brian? Yeah, so great guys. Yeah, we can do that and
You know, but okay, so I want to tell you a story though.
It's like, I subscribed to this,
I wanted to make a music video for that
and a couple other things, right?
I wanted the AI generated music video.
So I was like, I looked for like,
all these, there was nothing that was like free, you know?
So it's everything was like, you know, you have to pay
unless I just wanted to like use one,
one like a still picture or something.
So, but I found this one that generates like a whole,
whole like graphic cartoon thing to go along with it and you get to choose like you know,
what kind of how you want it's like really all accustomed right and so I subscribed for like
$19 and I started to get make the video for the Alex song right and then
All the thing gets halfway through it and it stops and it's like you're out of credits
And it's like it says I have to buy like more credits and so I don't have a bunch of fucking video will cost to produce
But it's already costs like 19 dollars so far
Three quarters way through it, but it's gonna be so great though. But it's like I'm just gonna
Hold off a little bit
Yes, and she yeah, she loves it like her friend was like, oh my god
Her friend like her these songs like she was walking by she's like are those songs about about you or those are youtube friends
It's so funny, like, yeah.
It's a cute song.
Yeah, I mean I'm gonna get better at doing it and then like I don't know but maybe I can I like I do like doing it
But did you hear like people that have been exclusively like AI content like they just have like they just use AI or they just like you know
Or just they they just watch other people's content like you know without like
Commenting and stuff those people are gonna get get demonetized. I said I think my audio was fucked
Okay
How you doing?
It's it's it's going Pat
Patty it's okay. It's not Patty. It's just P. P. It's like you know, I'm Patty. I'm Patty Patty
I'm not Patty. I'm Pat's P. A. T.
Since for psyche we can tarot, right? That's why it's that's a nice acronym. It is pretty cool one
It's it's Pat Saturday night live correct classic question. Okay. I know it's not AI. It's okay. I've assisted learning intelligence or something
It's a GPT
Keep that shit. Yeah, Chatcha BT. Also, it was like remembers details that I tell it
And so it will incorporate those details into the new songs that I make and so it like learns as it goes along
And then it's like and then I you put that into the music thing and the music thing is like a really
I just found a perfect combination of software. It's pretty like it's pretty cool
Like I was taking my job there man because I'm mixing master my own songs and you want to plug your little fucking prompts into AI
You're kind of pushing me out of the hate
I don't know, but you can use it.
You can use it.
You can use it, too.
Yeah, but you're taking the soul out of it, man.
You don't go with it.
You don't have my talent, motherfucker.
I know I don't have your talent, but what I'm saying is...
Know your musician and I know I think is threatening to you and everything
But I'm saying you can if you put your music you can put your own music and then put it through AI and do different things
Their music I know like it can improve whatever you do
Well you can improve it I guess but what I'm saying is like I put I just take the prompts and ideas like I put like little like
So those so I do like put it like a large amount of like
Input into that and it comes up with like all the song but it's like it uses all the input
I give it and so it's like I have to be very careful
But when I tell it and exactly tell the right what I exactly what I wanted to do
So that's why I I think like sometimes it's works well with me because I work with it
You know, it's like, you know a kind of respect
I even say thank please and thank you to the AI and so it's like it always like kind of like
Um, it's uh gives gives me a good effort. I think you're trying to have some good stuff. Uh, congratulations on your new album
Pat. Oh, thank you so much. It sounded pretty good. Yeah, thank you for your content. We all appreciate it. Yeah, I love you
Thank you. We're going to find your music yet
Yes, it's for me. I make it for me. Okay. Well, do you have a channel random guy or do you want to promote?
No, okay
I wanted to make sure yeah, I know you've been very generous to the channel. I want to make sure I recognize you and
I wanted to talk to um
Summer I'm not trying to like see what you don't summer, but you there was like you had a big beef recently
Was a half hour ago or something like that?
What is my calls fucked up with it with Janet you mean?
Listen, I know that you're you're a fellow white girl and you know Janice a little whatever, but she's from the 412
So I gotta kind of like I got a rep Janet. I'm sorry just for that
You know I'm saying she's from Pittsburgh. I got a stick with her
That's why she gets
Just for that reason just well then how about this how about this and it's no disrespect to you, but it's still fuck her
So it's all good. I don't even know the past history. I don't know
was just saying bird bird came up here she was talking shit about you know
bronze bird and so I came up because browser was trying to link or whatever and
so I was like let him up you know me and I was like he has the right to talk
shit if somebody's talking shit about him she felt some type of way about that
and started talking shit to me so I'm saying clap your backs
Yeah, I got to represent the Janet though. She's she's a fellow Pittsburgh. She's she stays even though she don't let that white boy
You're white self on her panel, but okay cool. Go ahead. I'm out of here. I literally made that up
I flip flopped really fast once I actually heard she was from Pittsburgh's but uh, you know
Hope it works out well for you. Yeah, we'll see where it goes, but I gotta go. Thanks for letting me on. See you
Later skater
Okay, yes
Also, but there's did you hear the gaudy song summer? That's really cute too. I don't know. No, I haven't heard that one
Did you like to? I
Know it's like
This one's good. You'll like this one
Out of New York, came a storm on wheels
Rollin' in smooth with the mafia feels
Cuban cigar, lit like it's temper
Pizza in one hand, hot dog for dinner
Said psyche on board, had to switch the scene
Left some poor woman screamin' on live stream
Trolled her down to the void and back
Then crashed my show like a heart attack
Gotti, mainland, Troll King, mafia's so rollin'
Wild but they still my friends
Yeah love you got it till the bitter end
We fight, we troll
But we friends, forever my friend
Things he's got with the lowercase g in a wheelchair still stomping through the live feed
Bow to your king while smoking that leaf laughing at chaos like it's comic relief brought
Spunky too now that trolls a gem mean one sweet ones. They all jumped in
Cameras glitching chat on fire mods begging me to cut the wire, but nah, I like my circus
I love this mess every troll is just a test stock in this got you room
Absurd and free, but deep down you got lo-
We troll, but we friends, forever my friend
You called me a fraud, then defended my clown
Spam my chat, then held it down
You got layers, like a deep dish slice
Under all that shade, a heart made of ice
And maybe rice, so let's light that cigar
another night of chaos welcome to psych you brought the drama the heat fun and
weirdly it feels like you're the one got it yeah you crazy but your family now
rolling through fire still taking a bow no matter the madness no matter the
weather we can't we but we stick together
My show tomorrow
It's pretty neat
I'm not like the best like writer of the music but I know exactly what I want to put in the song
and so I think it's like all about the input you know and so that's the key to like chat
GPT and stuff just talk to it like a like a assistant or something like that you know
and it really like it's like it's like a superstar like it gives you great ideas and it's smart too so
And I went out but I went and put and make a video to this one too
I just don't know how expensive this fucking this program is but it's like yeah for $15 I can buy like
6,000 or no 600 credits or something like that. I don't know how but it's like he uses so many credits when it's making this video
I think I'm like
$40 to make the video that's gonna be too expensive
I thought it was gonna be like I could subscribe and then I can make as many videos as I wanted it's like
It turns out to be fucking. Wow. I'll be making some professional
Ain't nothing for free. I can promise you that nothing life is free. It always
Yeah, but it could be worth it, too. I think it could be like yeah
I will I will uh, so I think I'll be
All right. Well, thank you
Thank you
You give me life for a long time
Uh, probably. Yeah. I mean, yeah, I will. I mean, I'll be back. I'll be back. Okay. Love. Love you. Love you back. See you later. Bye. Yeah. I'm gonna follow suit too. I'm going over to my brother's house. We're gonna go swimming. See my nieces. All right. Oh, have a great day. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. I'm gonna be over there for a couple hours and go swimming and stuff. Hang on my nieces. But if you're on, I'll stop by later on. Okay, come on back. See you later.
Adios
Later, I'll talk to you later, bro
Later psych later
Hi, Jamie. We got Jamie here from the hospital. Oh shout out to Jamie. Hopefully you're doing okay. Oh look look how big I
See now we're in these big circles. I like that look of that
You like it's like
You know yin and yang. Hey shamrock. How are you?
Let's see why you think they require subscription, but what do you mean?
Brian, but yeah, so it's not like a real intelligence, but it's like how is it able to like figure out?
Certain things like that there's stuff I tell it there's stuff
I don't tell it, but it knows stuff that I don't tell it like and I don't know like in the songs
It like puts the details that it shouldn't know it it knows sometimes. I how does it do that? I don't know I
I think it's kind of, I think it might actually be learning.
It feels like it's kind of like sentient on some level.
I don't know.
It's very, very, very realistic.
Very strangely realistic.
Trippy.
So, LES, it got anything to share with the chat?
Not really.
Okay, well when you leave the chat the panel will be closed and then to open it up again
It will be $10 chat. What's up?
As soon as somebody comes or wants to send me to open it, I will, yeah, you missed the
Janet.
Yep.
Can I read you?
Sure.
Hold on.
Let me get my cards.
Of course, if you purchase a reading too, you can come up on panel two and I'll do the
reading on panel.
So it's better for people that want to do a reading at that time to want to do it one
on one.
It'll just be one on one when I'll do the reading and have you on the panel.
See?
For the readings too. Okay, so
Yeah, you missed it. You missed the stuff
I asked Janet to come back but Janet, that's a good time to come back if you want to come back
You know, it's quiet like everyone's gone for the comfort a little bit, so
If you want to come back and have a one-on-one and get your word out. I don't know if you're talking, but I'm not Maddie Jen
I hope you're not mad at me. I'm gonna post them. Oh shit. Okay, so this one for sure
Okay, that one for this is for shamrock. Okay, there's gonna be two couple more for shamrock. Okay. We got that. Okay
Okay, okay, so we have okay, so this is interesting. Okay, so we have
Um, the six of coins. Okay, so the six of coins. So this is the six of pentacles the six of pentacles. That means you've achieved
Um, some, um, let me, I'll put myself on full screen for a second.
You've achieved some kind of success and it's like, you know, and now it's time to be generous.
I'm back, you know, now it's like, you're like looked at as like, oh, there's, you know,
you know, you got the nicer clothes and it's like, you're kind of being gonna be looked to,
you know, like, um, for like, some people may be asking for, you know, charity.
Just know who to give to, give to the right people, right?
Because you got this like ruling, like this king energy and see how is that staff right there,
Just a far look and then you got the ace of one. They got the exact same one that's in his hand
You got that too. So you have this you have this ace of one which is like this power
this like maybe it's like a this, you know, maybe you're reptilian power or you do you
Do you have some kind of like strong?
control of your reptilian part reptilian part of your brain or something something like that, but you know you have this
You have this passion what what's that face person a person looks sad?
Don't be sad. You're everywhere and nowhere. Yeah. Well, look
Okay, I'll read the ace of of wands, you know
This is gonna be something that is a start of something that's gonna make you like really
Excited about the king of wands that represents a focus determined creative leader. Oh, this is the king of one
I'm sorry the king of wands, but that's yeah, this guy right here
for the king of wands
represents a focused, determined, creative leader.
Jafar was a potential of a diamond in the rough.
Like him, the King of Wands is a powerful visionary.
Though his methods are unconventional,
his commitment to them inspires loyalty.
The cards aside to trust your vision,
even if others don't understand it yet.
And then the ace indicates major opportunities
to show off your creative process or headed your way.
This is the great time for brainstorming because you're being inspired and full of great ideas.
Pursue creative projects with positivity and enthusiasm. Your potential is limitless.
Yeah, I think you got the power. You got the power. You got the book and the magic wand, right?
Okay, good. I hope you like that. Okay, the mind is a powerful thing. Yeah, Jamie
You know what especially is powerful like the power of suggestion and that's what everything and runs on
Mainly is like the power of suggestion
It's like basically hypnotism and we're basically going to trance the entire time because we're just being trained to like be
entertained or just be learning and to be accepting information and receiving and also receiving it so it's like
Yeah, it can be very interesting
the mind is a very powerful thing and it's a very vast thing and it's the most
complicated thing in the world too and so people that it's like psychiatry is
not even beginning to scratch the surface of what's really going on we can't
there's so much going on there we will take us a long long time to figure out
everything right but you know we are figuring out some things rudimentary
things though
Things that maybe not necessarily are that helpful at the moment, but when we were able to control dreams or see dreams on a screen, like that are happening in the head, we can't be, can you really do that?
Or I'd be like, our mind is a camera kind of, if we could suit your cat with nine lives and you use eight of them?
Well, I wish you a long life, not a long night life.
See this guy has nine lives too
Guys if you haven't like tried chat gpt and it's like if you if you need like
This idea is of stuff it was like
It'll give you like business ideas. It'll give you and then tell you how to like do everything
It'll give you like fucking like you map out like oh, it's like there's really really cool things
You know you see you save you up, but I would really recommend just checking it out
It's free and you just like talk to it and then say hey if you have a business
You say hey, well do you have any ideas about this even if it's just for graphics or if it's like for
I mean, it will just give you ideas, and then you can say, sometimes it's like having a very expensive assistant.
But I know a random guy was all like, oh, you're not talented, I'm talented.
I'm talented. I know you're just talented. Musicians are very talented.
But would you say computer programmers are talented too?
talking to a computer. Being a programmer, if you're good at it, you'll get some good results.
but it's also, use it in conjunction with what you have.
You can put your own music into it
and you can do all kinds of stuff with it.
I mean, it's like, if you want to,
or but you think, okay, my music is so pure.
Well, do you use a synthesizer?
Do you use a computer in the first place?
Or is it all just purely off the,
you know, this acoustic instrument?
That means you're not really recording.
So how about your, you know,
incorporating your technology with your instruments
so you can share it if you want to.
But you say, oh, it's just for me.
Yeah, okay.
I don't know.
Why you had to fight with me, random guy?
OK, yeah.
So yeah, you can check out the banner.
I thought that it would be really cool to have the
panel be sponsored from now on, because then I will be
able to do more panels.
Because it's having the panels sometimes do distract from the show right because or from like the
Focus of the show because they can go on for hours and hours and sometimes the topic it doesn't even have
Not even that interested that I think the audience might be or the audience likes the people and I I
Don't know we have a lot of different stuff going on. So just to make it
easier for like me to like continue to do the show and
Oh, yeah, and we're almost at 100 memberships by the way, I think we're like 96 or something we get to 100
There'll be more emojis, but I'm gonna replace some of the emojis that got there already
I think I like some of them some of them are not that great, so I need to replace them
But if you already see suggestions
Let me know
Let me see
And I can do readings for anybody in the chat right now. Just let me know if you'd like if you someone shout out at astrology sign
I'll read some more of the dark side astrology. That's always fun
Yeah, we'll be software that can help modify its own code and add it to things code with zero human interaction to learn new
Things with zero data good enough coding your generators don't even exist yet
Good enough code generators. Yeah areas, okay
So Aries, yeah, okay, so Aries, this is a good one.
This is also a good way for us to learn
about the signs, guys, and so I'll read all about Aries.
And is it, Christine, is it, so you are Aries, right?
Okay, so Christine, you're Aries.
And I'll read about, I'll read all about Aries, okay?
So here we go.
Okay, so Aries says, and Aries is the first sign
of the zodiac, right?
And if you guys didn't know it, so Aries is to me like but it's like the
It wants to be first, right? Okay, so it says Aries. There's a picture of a cannon. There you go. Oops. I can't I can't
It says mommy dearest meets
Peck's bad boy element fire Aries is the dragon that lays waste to the countryside then falls asleep satisfied that it's burned a few small towns
Quality cardinal the only thing in areas is qualified to lead is the chorus of kindergartners singing the Barney song symbol the ram
But battering ram ram it to you, but headed
Ruler marched to God of War and in bar room brawls.
There at past time, shooting first and asking questions later.
Favorite book, the self-published journal of the personal wisdom.
Role model, Yosemite Sam.
Dream job, sex therapist.
Key phrase, are you talking to me?
Body part, the head chronically aching from running into all those brick walls.
Approach with caution.
Aries' first sign of the zodiac resides in the house of self, a astrology textbook described
the ram as a charming, enthusiastic, natural-born leader who gleefully rushes through life with
tremendous joie de vivre. The truth is, this bossy, egotistical motormouth is as self-absorbed
as a two-year-old and has a me complex the size of Texas. In Aries, Mars gives courage, determination,
and energy, passion, and ambition. He also bestows temperament, ego, and impulsive action.
Just like Yosemite Sam, the typical ram barrels through life, daring anyone to cross his or
her path.
Be unlucky enough to get in the way, you know, suffer a red-faced temper tantrum.
Jumping up and down is optional.
The worst thing you can do to an Aries is ignore them.
The way you would ignore a cranky toddler who's in dire need of a nap.
Aries are reactive not reasonable by refusing to think before they act rams off and ruin their chances by happiness for happiness
By making wild assumptions without gathering all the facts being born without the humility gene has negated their ability to admit mistakes
Argue with one and you'll suffer a barrage of irrational angry shouting
Prove they are wrong and they will react that they let that toddler who says I'm not and shrugs his baby shoulders and walks away
And this is Aries woman. Okay, if you love one Aries woman, so this is about
It says, I've been uncompromising, peppery, intracable, monomaniacal, tactless, volatile,
and off-times disagreeable, Betty Davis, April 5th.
It says, do you like that, Christine?
She is independent, fun-loving, and honest.
She's not a game player or easily shocked.
This lady can clean her own house, balance her own checkbook.
and put the pieces of a shattered dream back together
with such aplomb that no one's the wiser.
She loves romance, sentiment, and men who are bold,
and her ardor will not fade over the years.
Just a minute, bud, before you jump in that long line
of frantic, scrambling men, take note.
These haggard guys are looking for the nearest exes.
If it doesn't belong with I and the end with me,
the female Aries isn't interested in the conversation.
Ask how her day has been and be prepared for all the boring details.
She thinks that because she's fascinated with herself.
Why naturally, so are you.
A female ram will compete with you on every level.
Land a huge account and she'll tell you that it was just dumb luck while touting her conquests
of the day.
Taylor, you just won the Lotto and she'll say, that's nice, but I just broke a fingernail.
She's impatient, critical, and will start to stop as many projects as a Gemini.
and end up at the head of the line.
There's nothing altruistic about this babe.
She wants power status and lots of dough.
And to get it, she'll drive herself and you to frenzy.
If you want to be treated like a man,
marry any other sign in the universe.
If you want to be told what to wear,
eat, think, plus be constantly reminded
that she is faster, better, and smarter than you.
Here's your girl.
Think of Mama Rose and Gypsy,
the eternal stage mother,
the woman who expects everyone to live her dream,
dangle in her shadow.
She says, jealous as a Scorpio, but don't mistake her green-eyed snarling as insecurity.
Jealousy in all rams comes from the head, from the need to be honest, the need to be first.
Even the kid will have to take a back seat to her in your affections.
Prone to frequent temper tantrums, she is the perfect example of a pushy broad,
determined to get her way, come hell or high water.
She's not squeamish about who she has to walk on sleep with or
to get to the top of her chosen field. Joan Crawford and her arch-rival Betty Davis are perfect
examples of why Aries female is known as the queen bitch of the universe who deserved the title.
The legendary feud between these two stars and well-known in Hollywood in the 40s and 50s.
Davis said of Crawford, she slept with every male star at MGM except Lassie. In return Crawford
said, I don't hate Betty Davis. Take away the pop eyes, the cigarette and those funny clipped words
Baby Jane, Betty Ann had a Coca-Cola machine installed to irk Joan because of her affiliation
with Pepsi. Joan got revenge by putting weights in her pockets when Davis had to drag her
across the floor during a key scene. In an interview after filming wrapped, Davis said,
The best time I had working with Joan was when I pushed her down the stairs. Remember
this with your own firebrand.
For every night you snuggle with her on the sofa, you'll spend the next 10 either dodging verbal or physical darts or an endless world of friends, dinners out and rushing to be first in line at the latest movie.
The female ram can outrun, out gun, out shoot, out talk, and outsmart everyone around her. How do you know? Just ask her. Like a Leo man, an Aries woman is a legend in her own mind.
Uh oh, do you like that?
Christine I'm sorry. I know I forgot to tell you it's like a it's like a it tells him of the dark side of the site
It's a funny book, but I hope it didn't offend you. Oh my gosh
Hold on oh
Christine yes, yes, I'll let you on oops shit. Bye
One second Christine
Hi Christine, okay, you made yourself sideways
Oh
Undo yourself
Put yourself straight. Okay. No, that doesn't sound like me. Only a couple of things that sound like me
Shoot first ask questions later. It's always been my motto
Right, I will be a view and ask later
in the leader
I don't ever jump to things because I have to have facts and
I'm probably always right because I don't say anything less. It's factual. I will never ask you a question
I don't know the answer to already
Oh, does that make sense? Yeah, we'll never see and people get people have a problem, you know that they learn
Oh, yes the question. I'm not gonna give it an answer because she knows the answer
So my return my answer my questions are kind of rhetorical. Yeah
Yeah, and it's like but I would say like you know my grandmother was in areas and it's like I see some of
But I do love Betty Davis. I do love Betty. Yes, and Joe Crawford. How about Joe Crawford too?
Yes, I love Joe Crawford too. So I like to do my favorite.
And have you seen Baby Jane? Did you ever see that one?
I did.
Yeah, and so that's like the classic because they like they were like getting to the end of their careers at that time
And let's put them in a movie and they they just hated each other
But they they so but it made it it made for good a good acting, right?
And it kind of does help the acting when you have actual emotions behind it with each other
Yeah, it's interesting
I'm I think I'm selfish
I don't think yourself is either, but they would but it's like me first kind of energy not with you
But it's like that's what from Aries. I get that a lot. Yeah, it's like well. I always tell people
Ram you
Yeah, it's a yeah, and they're like, you know, they're like
In my way
Yeah, yeah
Because I will push you out of my way, but you know so funny
Um, you know talked about first in the movie like things like that. Yeah, no
I don't like people honestly. I don't like people
So I don't like people. No, I don't like people
Well, you know, it's like, uh, in my younger years maybe but as I got older. No, I don't like people
So so aries is like the sun so it can be very much part of the identity but
There's also the but women oftentimes relate more to with their moonsign because women are very well
Right. I'm gonna say because we're maternal. Yeah
I do not know my moon sign. I forgot it. I don't know your sign forever
If you know your exact time of birth
Then the next time you run a chart just like I know I do know my exact temper because I have a birth certificate right
Here what you can go to you know to astro comm and just fill out the
Make a chart and then you can see your moon sign and you can also tell what what house the moon is in exactly and then I'll be able to
It will tell you a lot of information. I can either tell you where you can go on that website and look at it, but it's at Asteroid.com.
It's so funny because, you know, I went to go get, you know, that real ID crap thing.
And I couldn't get it because none of my names on everything I have didn't match my burst certificate.
And even my driver's license, I've had a Florida driver's license for what 18 years 15 years
And I couldn't get my real ID at first and then I had and I had an old
First certificate and even I married certificate didn't have my name spelled right. It was just it's just the weirdest thing
So I'm not really who I am
Not funny
Yeah, I mean yeah, exactly. Well, it's like you're always we're always changing those two, right?
It's like we're we're so many things like we're like so day like we are basically
We're like a spirit and like a human body and our spirit is like so many things. It's like everything, you know, it's like it's hard to explain but
so we are like very complicated beings in this universe of the brain is the human brain is the
most complicated thing on the planet like that like no one can get close to understanding everything
about it right no because when they think they understand it they find something else and that
So I think I think for the for the open panels I think from now on I'm gonna be either like I think I'm gonna have the open panels be
Sponsored but I can I think and I'll do like you know
I'll talk to I still have like one-on-one guests like we know that I can just like you know people like you know you that I
I know that I only came up with you did that reading there was too much
Yeah
Did you like the reading or do you see if you find it funny or did you not?
Okay, there's a little bit more. Can I read you the rest? Okay, I'll read you the rest. Okay, it says,
it says, if you are one born rotten, it says, it's not the earth that the meek inherit,
it is the dirt that is from Camelot. It says, you are capable of soaring to any height,
sometimes by utilizing your determined Martian energy, sometimes by hopping on the nearest broom.
You play all the angles, are jealous, competitive, and totally oblivious to your own worst behavior.
You don't do laid back, instead you picture yourself as a great enlightener and spend your time haranguing the rest of us into submission.
You are nearly as tactless as a Sagittarius, stuffing his size 12 foot into his mouth.
And at the least, you have a gift of gab that can make a Gemini cry.
and at your worst, your bellicose attitude loses friends
and starts family arguments.
Since your favorite topic of conversation
is the endless minutiae of your personal existence,
you are also a colossal bore.
You, of course, this means little or nothing to you
as long as you get to hear yourself talk.
You're genuinely perplexed when rooms empty
as your appearance and all your friends get caller ID
or then refuse to answer the phone.
Your home is combination trophy stop and arsenal.
The wall next to the gun cabinet is filled with heads
from your latest Bambi shoot.
The table in the corner holds a hide school debate
team cup, and a marathon dance blue ribbon. Pictures of relatives lying in the hallways
in the basement of stuff with assorted military gear, World War II surplus K rations and bottled
water. From the time you learned about the birds and bees and people would be surprised
at how early an age that was, until you're dead, sex is the uppermost thought in your mind.
In grammar school, you played doctor. As a teen, you wore out the back seat of family sedan.
As an adult, you'll fall forever in and out of love.
When you aren't filing your fingernails, you're sharpening your rapier wits on unfortunate
friends and instigating family feuds.
Actually the worst friend is something of a misnomer because you usually choose people
as friends in direct proportion to how they can help further your own plots and plans.
You Martians climb the social ladder as eagerly as Capricorns, but with far less finesse.
You'll transparently kiss up to the most powerful person around and have the blush
In fact, you'll twinkle and smile, but be all the more charming and get away with the whole mess.
Ares is a sign of the sculptor, warmonger, chip and dale dancer, and the bad half of a good cop,
bad cop team. Rams are also great athletes, freedom fighters, and bank robbers. Ares Clyde Barrow.
You were the type of child that flung open the closet door and dared any monster living there to get out of your space
You also had to get burned before you believed that the stove was really hot
You still do and therein lies your strength
You have no shame and eat more nerve than a one-legged wire walker
You have a true warrior spirit and are relentless when fighting for a cause or a person in whom you believe
Once you truly learn to listen to other viewpoints and accept that you are not always right the rest of the universe will fall at your feet
However in battle no other sign can match you Scorpion
may try to sting, but a well-armed barb flung straight from your flaming tongue,
stinging the scorpion's tail. Cancer and Pisces cringe and fade,
away with a single smoldering look.
Taurus Virgo Capricorn soon learn what scorched earth policy means when they try to rage at,
nag at, or trample you.
Your ability to push air sign Gemini and Aquarius into the ozone with your one upmanship soon
bursts their respective bubbles, and you have wishy-washy Libra begging for mercy when
you demand that he make a decision now.
You are the other fire sign.
Leo and Sagittarius understand each other on a soul level.
and therefore rarely have serious confrontations.
Your philosophy is nothing ventured, nothing gained.
You wouldn't care less what other things,
but you don't care less what other things.
You're spending the confident, rugged, individualist
who lives life on your own terms.
Let the rest of the world bake cookies
and tend their gardens.
Years from now, when all those folks you've left
in the dust are reading the window boxes
at the old people's home,
you can give them to giant raspberries you raced by
in your drop dead, red, supercharged hot rod.
There you go.
my husband's is actually very yes oh he is yeah so both both fire you're both
fireside and we both do well I mean for almost 42 years the marriage
Mm-hmm, you know
Yeah, well, they're very you know the fire you does that's because that's some determination
I guess it would be like a lot of determination to like maybe also make the marriage work
But that's which is a great thing, you know, it's like, but you butt heads sometimes
That's I am the ram Bob Ram you
But you know we're both kind of that way
So, you know, I guess we compromise like yeah, you know, it's not worth it
You're gonna see probably a TV broke
Well, another relevant another relevant thing is the ascended sign and that's how you are viewed in in the in the world
Okay, and like by other people and so
Yeah, so do you want to check maybe you're ascended because that's how people kind of will see you like they'll maybe see you as a certain sign and then you have the
the
the moon sign which is your emotional side and the sun sign is your identity and then
you have to look at the houses there and because those houses mean a lot means something to like
some kind of area of your life you know there's like houses one of the home and one of the self
and all kinds of ones mine are mostly in the first house my placements and so i'm a lot about identity
interesting it's a very interesting i'm more emotions you're more emotions
I mean, I mean
The moon sign is like also in the first house
So my emotions are part of my identity too, but it's also like a Capricorn Aquarius Capricorn Sun Aquarius moon
Which are very opposite signs and so it's like an Aquarius is very cold emotionally. It's like they're very detached
and so it's like
But I have the Capricorn is like my personality. It's like I feel like you know, it's very very a lot warmer warmer than a
and more emotional than Aquarius can be.
But at the end of it, I can be very detached.
That's why I can deal with so many things so well.
OK, well, I'm going to say that was a good one.
No, I mean, that was.
And like I said, the most important thing, the leader,
and should first ask questions later.
And that's not only figuratively,
yeah, it can be with a gun, but it's also, I will.
Put my words down as facts and then ask a little bit more about it later
Mm-hmm. Yeah, and it's like I think you are also very fair with I how you perceive things
Like I know how you deal with things too. It's like you're just like you're very
It's just in my experience with you personally,
you've been very fair and nonshumped to conclusions
because so many people are, and that's funny
because it's like you're supposedly the sheep, right?
And then the sheep are like,
oh, sheep are followers, right?
But you're actually ironically like the kind of the leader,
you always gotta have a leader.
You got always have to have the elite,
but you know, that took years of experience.
It's not something I could say I was the same person
I was in my 20s and 30s.
as I matured and figure out how life really works
and learn don't stress the small stuff,
I think that's where my personality changed
and I think that's where more of my emotions come into play.
Yeah.
You know, but in this world today, you know, everyone's, you know, going like, you know, kind of like, you know
I think some witch hunts are starting again
There's like a lot of you know people that are getting mad about the gay rights movement and
Trans rights and everything and they're getting all, you know, riled up about it
And it's like really good to have people that are
allies that understand like the plights of certain communities and everything and
And actually are you know are out there
You know, and that's that's that's a big thing. Psych. I'll be 100% honest with you and
And your true warriors and your true leaders in my opinion are the ones that for example, let's let's get I'm not gay
I never had an interest in being gay, but you know something. I feel that the gay person has every right
who am I to tell them how to live their life who was anybody and
Right shouldn't be taken away because somebody's different than you.
Right.
I mean, we're now, I mean, now we're like talking about like, you know, what is this thing about like this?
I always call it, I'll spell it out, A-L-L-I-G-A-T-O-R-A-L-C-A-T-R-A-Z.
What is that? Have you heard about that?
No.
It's something in Florida that they're sending people to you right now. It's like they both all the alligator
Petra's oh my god, it's crazy down there
And at first they thought the alligators were going to be the problem
But they're taking anybody that they that ice picks up or the sheriff picks up and they can't prove they live in the United States
They're putting them there
Um, they're supposed to be taken the criminals they claim
That are United States citizens. Okay, so they're taking immigrants there, but
Then what for what crimes like what what kind of crimes of these people committed well
They're claiming that they've come first of all. They're claiming they've they're they're trying to label anybody who came in through the last
administration that they came here illegally. I think we welcomed him here. Should
have our administration did it the way they did it? Probably not. But we are
spending billions, hundreds of billions of dollars to capture these people. Now
they're claiming, claim is from my understanding, the claim is these are
heinous crimes here in the United States and
In their countries, but there's no proof what they've done now. They're also looking for gang tattoos
So people that have gang tattoos on them now a
Lot of people, you know, there there are certain tattoos that are claimed to be gay better game better
Classified as gang tattoos, but there's other people that will have aromatic writing. It doesn't mean they're in a game
Right there. Well, you know, they'll they'll have tattoos of their heritage are Hispanic with their Mexican their Puerto Rican or Dominican
You know, whatever it is
They have a tattoo representing them because they don't want to lose that part of their heritage
Yeah, and that's also the government's society. Oh, no, that's again get to so we are now taking you
You can't prove you live in the United States. We're now taking you to alligator Alcatraz. Oh, that's ridiculous
I mean, this is so ridiculous and I mean, it's like scary and it's like well
It's kind of like reminds me of Guantanamo
It's worse than Guantanamo
One place worse than that from the thing that I'm coming out. So they when they when they designed this and decided to put this here
It is what they call an alligator alley. It's in South Florida
It is swamp area Everglades area and it is stricken with alligators. That's why it's called alligator Alan
and alligators, snakes, spiders, you name it.
Well, now the problem is that they're having,
it's not the alligators they're concerned of,
it's malaria and something else they were talking about.
Dungay fever and supposedly there's medications
and there's vaccinations.
So, you know,
here my conspires conspiring in my mind are they using these people that they
can't prove that American that they have decided to take into custody without
any new process and are we going to start doing medical and social experiments
up
Well, they're trying to scare, they're trying to scare other people too. I mean, cause I've heard like a lot of people like reference like, oh yeah, you're to get sent there, you know, to people, you know, whatever.
And it's like, well, it's like trying to scare people. I don't think, I don't know. I hope that nobody, they're not targeting immigrants and things like that.
No, they are. And I will tell you today's, what's that, Monday, Tuesday, Monday, no Tuesday, it was Tuesday.
We had ice.
with about 10 sheriffs in our neighborhood.
And I don't have a very big neighborhood.
But they took their, I know for a fact,
there's two Russian families
that have been relocated here
and one Ukrainian family.
I do know that for a fact.
Um and rumor has it because we can't find any information now. Nobody's talking
Rumor has it and those three homes have been very emptied like
Quiet nobody and nobody out cars haven't moved nothing and neighbors aren't talking or speaking about anything
But rumor has it they took them
So I don't know
Yeah, because I'm sure it will be
It seems like it's like a testing thing
You know, they're just testing how the reaction would be and like then how you know this one
We're in the district. They would probably like spread the idea just like another be like us another another
Well, wasn't there a prison they took some of these people that was it El Salvador or something?
What's the name of that prison that they were taking?
The sound they send a bunch of people back to El Salvador, right?
And it's this that prison is a very like it has like the most state-of-the-art x-ray system
It has like, you know, yeah, like I just a body x-ray so it's like, you know
a 3d x-ray inside the body
It's like better than any any prison I've seen here where we still have to squat and cough, you know, so
Yeah, they do it's like incredible prison. But yeah, they they did send a bunch of people
I think they've been considered as gang members back to El Salvador
huge men have
I think all the and that's why apparently they have a minimal gang problem
Because they don't know if they're a gang member
Well, and in you know this this administration from what I am understanding
They feel that every country let empty out all their prisons sent them all to United States and it's like I don't believe that you know
Is there some sure?
You know, I hate to say this, but humans have an evil aspect within them.
Most of us have learned, you know, how to cope with that evil aspect, but we all have
it.
And, and they just, oh darn, that was a huge light.
Sorry.
Yeah, and people uh-huh
Yes, yes, that's because crazy you just said evil and then like the lightening well
It's like
Like a lot of people like they go they don't recognize it like especially nowadays
Everybody's very into like, you know looking for
They think shadow work is like looking at like hunting shadows
I think they're like the Ghostbusters or like, you know, they're even programming, you know, the movie
It's like the program all these people to like, you know
It's our little gang and like, you know, cunt out the monster the neighborhood blah blah and then kill them, right?
But anyway, so that's the man
That's but then that's also stranger things are the same thing and they put a paranormal stuff to it
But we know what they're really talking
And so we have uh, so everyone's chasing shadows and it's like but it's like this real shadow like everybody has a shadow and everybody's shadow is pretty much
Equal to everybody else's shadow. It's all the same and we all contain so many things that's human beings
So many things in the brain so many psychological processes
We're so infinite vast universes are within our mind, you know
And so we're very complicated in other words
But people have different ways of coping with things as long as they're not harming any other human being
I don't think that they are like what's happening with what you know i'm calling what they're i mean
i hate seeing illegal immigrants and that's why i call it say migrants i know they think that those
words can be interchangeable but um they just want to label anybody that's not an american
These people and they're picking up people that are American citizens. I don't know if you heard me not a while back
I said this
So I my family has a Hispanic name
Okay, and they do look Hispanic
They have started carrying a couple months ago when all this started happening, they've been carrying their birth certificates with them, their social security with them, their driver's license with them, everything with them on their possession at all times because they don't want to get picked up in the crossfire because of A, their name, or B, how they look.
It's crazy.
I don't know, but the Alcatraz thing, the Dungay fever and malaria, I mean, we're getting an outbreak in that in the United States, we've got problems, and it's because of the conditions, and I know, that's why I said they're spending like billions, I think it was like maybe 100 billion, I'd have to go back and look at my numbers.
build these types of things and to to take into custody what they're
classifying as illegal immigrants why couldn't have we have taken all that
money and did something productive I know I'm wishing too much productive to
make because I think our immigration bill is obsolete totally obsolete
Couldn't have we have done something to better humanity and to better the United States
Yeah, I mean people just are we're like all we're concerned about is that you it's like, you know
It seems like other people's business, especially even in the country. That's that's true, right?
We're always poking our nose all around the world's like oh
We're trying to be the big brother of all the world and protect everybody right be the world's like security force
but at the same time it's like how about like pay attention to our own people
how to make sure our own people are all fed and our own people are instead of like putting
billions of dollars into the space program which is like what are we doing when we're learning
yeah like what color we could have we could have we could have ended up we could have
ended up homeless in the united states with all that money
yeah oh my gosh we could have but yeah
But we don't, and we let them starve,
and we also bring immigrants in here and pay them.
Like more than we pay our own citizens,
we put them in, we put them in housing.
These people that are in military age
from other countries, besides Mexico too,
and they're coming across the Mexican border,
or they were a lot recently, like the kind of last year,
which is like no problem with immigration,
or I mean, I know we have like, you know,
A lot of like a large labor force, but then it's like exploitative. It's a highly exploited, you know
Because they are like always just threatened with a whole call that you know immigration or whatever, right?
I mean not only you know or whatever language they speak, right?
Yeah, your sideway is too good.
Oh my gosh, your sideway is, oh my gosh, I'm missing it.
It's bad for you besides.
It's because when the battery starts to die,
when I get 35%, it starts to, like, start to two.
And I can't, like, put my tripod as they all worn out.
So I got some gorilla tape, and I
have to wait till it gets here to fix it.
No, but uh, did you see how clean my house was though? I cleaned up my whole house
You're taking you're taking time and I you know, I always look at cleaning my house and it's also self-care
Yeah, it really means it really feels good like to be in like a nice
Nice organizing space and I still have like a little bit more to go
But at least like this area is really great. You love my alien. Do you like my?
You see my alien
Christine, oh, she left.
Hey, guys, my Christine, love you.
Okay, so anybody else, I'll do one on, so from now on,
I'll just do like one-on-one interviews with you,
and then it's like, or unless we're doing open panel,
and then the open panels are sponsored,
but I'll be happy to have one-on-one with anybody
for no cost, okay?
But I just like went, but I'm saying for the open panels,
when it's like, there's a lot of people,
and it's like, you know, they can get kind of rowdy,
and so I think this will be the best method.
Also, I'll give you the advertisement.
It's only $5 right now, it's just $5 an hour,
so you can either send five, 10,
Up to 20 and that will be for the day six hours. I'll sponsor it for the day
And I'll pretty much let everyone say what they talk about what they want to but
I do have the right to like, you know, put anyone backstage and like, you know
And back, you know, and I'm going to please follow the rules for this for the TOS. Thank you so much
So anyway, I think that will work better. Very good. Awesome. And I love you guys. Thank you so much
You're waiting for your live yesterday money for 20. I think it wasn't my for 20 rounds. I hope you're good
Do you like the emojis Jamie? I think we're almost at 100 subscribers and so once we get there
I get more emojis like I think I get like really for 20. I'm gonna reduce some of the ones I have right now
Hey spunky. What's up girl?
Good to see ya
Um, we can't even that we willing to help them so well some people don't want me to save or even try right?
Well, that's our true arm in but it's like also and there is like ways
for people to get assistance and things like that, especially in big cities like, you know, Los Angeles in places, but
They even like took all the people out of the tents and put them in like hotels and stuff
Are you a little bit? You're a little bit wonky from them. You probably have the
Medication Jamie might be a little little walk you from medication
Yeah, yeah, cuz yeah, people want to talk shit. I was like at least I was like
This is called alchemy guys alchemy is like what if there's it?
What if there's a negative the negative thing where it's like people kind of like some people don't like me or hate me?
And then what and then it's like and then what do I do and I was like how about the
How about like monetize the hate for me and then
Then it will be
Then I don't care that you can hate me. I'll be getting paid
So I agree with psyche of people. Yeah, and or the opposite they should pay for it
Well, I think that I think the one-on-one
I'll do one-on-ones with people and that that's like good because I like when one-on-one because it's like then I
Because when it more than one people are in the conversation, I feel it triangulated sometime. Yeah, I think that's the new thing like you say it
So if you sponsor the show, you know, I think it will be it's either like, you know, the open for open panels
I think open panels. I will not open until
It's sponsored, but I will do one-on-ones with people for free, right?
I'll do one-on-ones. There's no charge or whatever.
I'll bring people up one-on-one because I like to talk to people one-on-one and have guests and stuff.
But when I have like a big open panel,
someone can sponsor it and I will also let them, I'll advertise for them in my banner and I'll, you know,
say their name a bunch of times and it'll be the hero of the show, right? So
that's way, that's, I don't know, I won't give away too much, but I'll just say
I did I did marketing so I'm ready to pivot and figure out how to succeed no matter how. Okay, so yeah
I think it's fair and it's like less little less complicated in the clapping system
Which will probably be kind of like we'll probably maybe phase that out a little bit because I think that it's better just to like
Have more friendly open panels with people that appreciate being there and everything, you know, so
What do you think Oliver? Is that a good thing? And sometimes they say we have to change for the better
I think it's improved. That's what a human being is about constantly improving
So I don't know. I'm not perfect. I'm trying
Yep, I
Happen sometimes
I'm full of it. Oh
What's not for long
Hold on. Oh, yeah, hold on. Oh, yeah, got it. You're talking got it. Okay
So guys, it'll be so cool when I I'm gonna do with the gaudy music video
I think I think I'm gonna make the gaudy music video, but I'm also gonna do the
The Alex one I'll finish it off. Okay, so you know what? I'm really trying to I'm paying for that right now
If when Alex gets here
I will see if he wants to help sponsor that one because it'll I need to buy more credits to finish the video
It's like 60% through it, but it'll be so good it guys. It's amazing
It's like it has like a animated cop and like an animated page and they're like, you know
It goes all to the that goes all to the music. I think you'll love it
But I mean, I'll I think I'll probably make it today
I don't know how expensive it'll be make these videos. It's like crazy. It's really hey spunky. How are you sweetheart? Good to see you
Spunky sponsored last night. Thank you so much. It was like awesome and crucible ghost, you know
I need to find your crucible ghost. Where'd you go? You disappeared once you like, you know
You told me as a man
you know
I like to I like to have men sick up to their word. Okay, we'll see what happens
Hey, sweetheart
Don't you get free credits when you invite people?
Wait to stream yard only if you're going to stream yard or what or free credits where?
Free credits oh
Okay, like free credits like you know you I'll let you on I'll let anybody on the show one-on-one
But if I'm saying to like open the panel
Open the panel to more people and have everyone like on the panel
I'm gonna have to start sponsoring it just so because it takes away
Sometimes for my tarot reading because I'd like to you know
I'd like to be like doing readings and stuff like that and it's like a lot of people just come here for the open panels
And stuff so I wanted you both right and I don't want to like
Oh, the music thing. Oh, okay. So would you like me to invite you to I'll see if I can get pre-credits. Hold on
Let me see. Oh, yeah, that's good. It's a good idea. Hold on. I'll teach you how to do. Here's how I'll teach you
How I do the music, okay? I'll put the website there
Okay, I mean I'll tell you anyway what it's called, but I actually can you pay to ban God if we're 24 hours?
Yes, you can
You see yeah, we still have the clapping system. I think yeah, we can but uh
Here but I'll say hold on. I'm gonna say right now. First of all, though the panel is closed
Okay, I need to redo the banner to like make it the panel is closed right now, okay?
today is shadow work Saturday okay so yeah we'll talk about shadow work a
little bit so I was gonna say people like to spend all their time on other
people's shadows like it's like let's go hunt some shadows let's go hunt some
shadows just kill all the shadows do you understand like everybody has a
shadow and so we need to each work on our own shadow that's what shadow work
is really about is like recognizing that as human beings we all have a shadow
So God, I would not let do that to you, just joking.
Oh, you sponsor the panel and then get clapped.
That could be a problem.
Yeah, so if you sponsor the panel,
then you cannot get clapped on the panel.
If you are the sponsor, you cannot get clapped.
That's the rule.
That will not, yep.
That is the, yeah.
And I also, I have like this McAnner.
This is for the clapping system right here.
Let me see.
Oops, let me put.
What do you think?
Oliver can Oliver can come up. You guys can come up now. You can come up to just one on one Joe if you want
Okay, what song do you want to play? I?
Played them up. I've played some songs already. So I see
There we go give the link, okay, here you go
I'm gonna sit down for a week or the month. It's just $25 a day
There's a link
Okay, this drink the image, okay
Yeah, I'll just go like this
Okay
Hello, we're not sorry. Let me get that close and scare you guys. Let me back it up a little bit
Cheers up, man. I'll drink one with you. I won't stay all night. Just one beer psyche. Okay
From here, but then I know what all of us like $10 now. What do you get money hungry on this man?
Come on site. I'm not money hungry
I'm money not money hungry, but I feel that the panels are in such demand and they get so mean that I'd rather just do one-on-ones with
People for free and then that's like it's been a bit of multiple people want to join the panel because sometimes the people like to like
You know joke around each other
Yeah
No, no, he's trying to join right now.
He has to wait until you go off or someone pays $10
and then I'll open the panel.
All right, I'll leave it to Oliver.
He'll let you up, Oliver.
And then he, Oliver, will hold my space
till I come back, Oliver.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Hope you're doing good, Saggy.
Nice to talk to you, pal.
See ya.
Love you, Joe.
Okay, bye.
Hi, Gibran.
I knew Joe was gonna do that.
I knew he was gonna steal it.
Oh, yeah, there you go.
Hold on.
You knew he was gonna steal it?
Well, what do you steal? I knew you said it. He did my spot. Yeah, he saw your spot. Yeah. No, he didn't
Yeah
I'm sailing away set an open course for the vergencies
Cuz I
Got to be free
Free to face the life that's ahead of me, oh I'm bored, I'm a c-
Okay, so I think, if I'll ever like to come back, please do the $10 for the open panel.
So anyway, let's go on, so let me see what we're going to do today.
Okay, I mean I love you to showcase your talent, but if you're going to use the show as a platform
No, join it for sponsorship.
Gotti, I didn't know.
He was, but if this is not American Idol,
well, yeah, I will not just stay on the show.
OK, evil ones, they messaged him, or we all were evil ones
up here, let's see.
Yeah, that's just fun about having a show, though.
I get to make the rules.
Very cool, and I'm not secured myself, you know or this or the show if I never get demonetized
You know I'll still be okay
But yeah, it does it does like a little you know it does make the
some of the hate I get a little bit easier it makes it easier whenever I talk to people one-on-one even if the person hates me
They hate me usually hate me along with it
Like the group will hate me and then it's like they'll get put into the group and like be part of the group and laughing
So that's why it's like you said I've always had better one-on-one with people
And so that's why I like doing one-on-one better and not having just like these people joking around and then I don't understand
the joke and I feel like left out and I get because I'm like kind of socially not that like
Great, you know, I think so I'm getting better extroverted though more extroverted
Anyway
How is everybody doing anybody I want to come up they're allowed
You know for free, but I do what if you want to have the panel open for multiple people
Hey, you guys can like you know going together with it, too. It's really not that much
the evil one so you like these new rules okay I like them too I think they're
bad I think it's gonna be better because I think we also get to get to know
people better have more one-on-one I think the one-on-ones are great and we
should have more of the one-on-one because you get to see other sides of
people without like you know other people like you know shouting at them oh
you're fucking do you know and so
And so Janet, if you're listening, you can sponsor a panel and that or not, or when I'm
not doing a panel, you can come and do just do the one-on-one and I won't add people.
I mean, I mean, it's like, nobody was coming up.
So I just figured I come back like I know it's one-on-one rules, but nobody was like
knocking the door down the join.
So I figured I got back up and it's all for my best friend, psyche.
Come on.
Come on in.
Yeah
It's a color sure
Where you buy that at vampire calm. What do you fuck?
that they'll be back and
that's a shit you want us to pay ten dollars why you wear your silky little shirts and I'm going to say
Yeah, and you're on you are all right now before you know
I know I interrupt you but I looked up a Rick Springfield video earlier, and he's like in his 70s
So long good you look like Rick Springfield if I may say so psych I do
And you look a little unhealthier, but you kind of look like can you say I wish I had Jesse's bitch
Like 70 years old. I look like I'm 70 years old. You're saying no Rick Springfield 70 and he looks better than us
Oh, he does what I'm saying. Okay
Okay, I'm a ponytail. Oh my god. No, I don't but it's like I could
It's like a little twig like a little um
Okay, twig twig tails, whatever they're called pig tails twig tails. You coming twig
Yeah, charisma something you wrap it all for free psyche. No, no. Oh, okay. Come on. No, you're fine
Like I'll just go join psyche. It's just wasted or I'm wasted and I'll just join your right start charging me
I mean, I'm sorry dollars so far. Okay. Okay. Go ahead. You know, please. Uh, pay me immediately
We're gonna have a I this having sex next I can't wait to see
Look this isn't what I think about getting clipped. It's fucking retarded when you get drunk
it's one night. That's what's cool about going live. You got one chance to join the live and see
people drunk. You shouldn't be able to wake up the next day and like watch a clip of them drunk.
If you weren't there, then you don't get to watch it. Tough shit. Yeah.
Yeah
But people are allowed to because it's very use it's very use what I could look slightly
I could just like make a channel where I just clip everybody's contents. That's exactly to me
Well, that's what the YouTube's gonna start like if you're just flipping the content not commenting on it
Then YouTube's gonna start
Demonstrating this one you say about trip kick. He does have coos intros where he likes makes beta look like she's in the like
Charmed it looks like she's a witch in her feet. They're little heels are dragging on the floor. So trip kick is fine. He makes like intros
Like Sandman, here's what Sandman does, and I like Sandman, but here's how overtarded he is.
He joins a panel and then runs his mouth, and then the next day shows clips of him on the panel running his mouth.
Like, come on, that's not what YouTube's about, Sandman.
Shoo-loo-loo, fuck you, loo-loo-loo.
Can you say fuck you, you, you, on this channel, or is that...?
You can say that, it's fine.
You know you can say it, you can say it, you can say shoo-loo-loo.
I know I talk a lot. Go ahead. It's like it's good to see you. I just get off my chest, man
It's okay. One in the pink one in this thing. I see what you did. I see what you did right there
But you're right about charging these fools they saying fucking this ain't fucking a
Shoot them range for everybody to come up and shoot their mouth off. All right, you're gonna fucking you're gonna pay psyche
You want to come up here summer?
No, come on. So summer already has the sponsor the panel and I did promote her and I promoted her chat
And I promote the channels too. I like to promote at the same time
And so and I want to really promote so it's like that's like actually a bonus because not only do you get the panel
You get the promotion too. That's like a two-for-one deal
One thing I like is we all get drunk and the other day I cost out summer
But I like summer we just get drunk and we just have fun
We just cut each other out and then the next day we're like, oh, I love summer
Yes. What did I do? Summer is awesome. I'm going to put you in a
summer. I'm going to put you in an AI song next Joe Shipley.
Oh, yes. He's she's young. Yeah. I love summer. So summer. I do
recommend everybody check out with her channel. I want to say I
love her like I like her. I do love her. I love her. I love her.
I love her. I love her. I mean, I'm actually in love with her
and I'm and I'm jealous of her husband and if I was in her
area, I would come with bouquet of flowers.
Yeah, a black guy. Is he black? Sorry. Oh, so that's what he is. Huh?
I'm just kidding summer and I guess his name
Yeah, Tyrone. I think his name is Tyrone Jerome. I was gonna say Jerome. It still ends with Tyrone Tyrone Tyrone
I
Don't want to be rude, but anytime I do jobs in like black neighborhoods
I hide my wallet under the seat of my work truck like even if they break in they won't find my wallet. Thank God
Sorry about that. Yeah
What's your tattoo say, man? What's your tattoo say? I like that. I like that
You know, it says love it says love
Solve
Yes, so so long
Solve Solve it you got a problem solve it boy. Yeah
If you got a problem, you know, I'll solve it check out the beat while the DJ revolves it
Just can't believe that that movie interview with a vampire you actually are wearing the prop shirt from that movie
That is badass, bro. You're cool as fuck
Like that's obviously that shirts obviously Brad Pitt wore that in interview with a vampire
This is just a regular dress like the regular dress shirt
Oh, it doesn't matter. I think Jamie. I know and I thought it was like to be sometimes like to tease about race because it's like
We need to get so serious. It doesn't matter. Jamie doesn't matter. I love it. I love I love all races
I really do. I think everyone's beautiful in their own you love me psyche. You know, I really do
I'm gonna do a song about about kissing you. I'm gonna do a song just about a kiss the message
That's gonna be a song by the RAI video. You know, I love Jamie's cowboys and I do
I do. You know she just got. I want to play that boys and Indians with her. She's in the hospital, Joe. So I wish her. She's in the hospital right now, Joe.
Are we snarl or is that forbidden?
You can't. We can snarl. All right. Thank you.
I can actually see the reflection in your glasses. You're looking at gay porn right now. I can see that.
I'm looking at you. I'm looking at you. I'm looking at you. This is my.
I'm Sam and Sam and the panel the pit Sam and the panels closed. Okay, so I'm gonna kick you off Joe
So Sam I can come up. Okay, but then I'll tell you back
Bye
Okay, Sam and I
Have a new thing about
See, I will give you the link though. You're like you're welcome up
But if you want to go on piano with other people
The panel has to be sponsored and so there you go
Okay, oh Alexander mayors. Okay. Well, maybe I'll make an exception because I had one to talk to Alexander to I haven't seen Alexander
Come on up. Can you hit Sam and let Alexander join? I want can I talk to her one-on-one for a little hold on one second
Can someone sponsor the panel, please? Hello, Sam and Sam and what I'm trying to uh, I'm doing one at a time on the panel now
Sam and until unless it this someone sponsors it and then I'll have open panels, but no more like what you open panels
Come on, but I want to talk to I want to talk to Alexandra, but I would
Go talk to her. No, no, she wasn't coming when she comes up. Okay, so she's here. I'll talk. I'll be right back
Okay, thank you, dude. You see you soon
Hi, I just wanted you to know it was me. I'm gonna turn my camera off cuz okay. Oh, thank you
Hi, nice to meet you. Is this the first time talking to you?
Everyone talks about you, and I never talked to you before, so...
Yeah.
I wanted to talk to you.
Are you psychic?
Am I psychic? Yes, I am.
Cool.
Yeah, I've done I do tarot cards, but I'm also like pretty empathic intuitive and I heard that I thought that you were bloggers older brother
Yeah, be the kind of like I joked about like you know, we kind of look alike and you know
He's like the better looking bird. I think you look a lot bloggers brother's nice
I've been heard dad and dad too, and we're both the same age. So that's kind of yeah
But I know I knew that you were live and I was just being a panel
junkie over on
Kate's panel, so I wanted to be a panel junkie today, so I'm over here if you want to kick me. It's okay
No, I don't I
I mean when he talked to you I've heard about you for months, you know, but I think you know
Thorny diamond was came in one day saying
Yeah, she said three pretty terrible things and I was like well, and I thought she was talking about this other Alex
That's on our show. He's like this. It's a cop from New York. Yeah, so it was you
And then, um, then I've seen you also, I saw you on Kate's this morning, but I also saw you
other times and I was like, oh, you seem like a really cool person. And I was like, but then
Mr. Big Types would come in. Look, I'm like right now in the middle of my journey of self-discovery,
like my third journey of self-discovery. And, um, I'm just like, I always battle. I go through things.
I have the worst reputation, but
I just keep going. I'm a Capricorn because I know you do your tarot. So you kind of I'm a Capricorn to I'm a Capricorn to
Yeah, okay. Yeah, then I just I don't stop
I just keep going and it works out even though there's pitfalls along the way and
That's what I do. I'm a goat going. Uh-huh going up the mountain. That's it. Keep go
I just wanna let everyone know the panel is now open
for more people to join.
Summer has sponsored the panel.
And so thank you Summer.
So what do you do over here?
Like just anything?
Like you can just drop whatever.
Well, I know I mean I heard about you like through Mr. Big Pipe's or like people would tell me oh well
He's a spy for Alexandra
Yeah, okay, he would be real suspicious. Yeah, I mean are like, you know, I've not like when I first came in these communities
The first person who was like of note that I talked to or that I got to know and spent time with was Attila
And he used to do like this panel that was super popular.
Oh, Bita, Bita knows.
Hi, Alex.
Hey, girl.
And that's how through Attila, I met Mr. Bigpipes.
And Mr. Bigpipes over exaggerates.
He thinks that everyone's scared of me, which
is retarded in itself, because I'm not scary.
And then he says, if you mess with me,
I'm gonna send Alex after you, and I don't do anything Mr. Big Pipes tells me to do. I mean it's just
But I like Mr. Big Pipes. I want Mr. Big Pipes to be happy, really.
Well, Mr. Big Pipes, first he came in with like, you know, you know, like two times streamer of the
year, whatever, or the month or something, and then, you know, and then he came in with like,
You could be streamer in the month. You want to be psychic streamer in the month. Oh, you could be why not there's no other
I mean, you're the only streamer who's psychic
Oh, no, he's pause you rose them video your video pause
He's like frozen. He'll be back. It's Alex. I saw you up here. I just wanted to come in
Hi, he has to transform into his light-body psychic self to tell us
Everything that we need to know what's going on. Are you feeling really? Yeah, I am are you sweetheart?
I am well, I'm I'm I'm like in a remote place, and I'm chilling good
I'm just like it you know, I
I'm taking the good times philosophy of being in a place where you have to have four-wheel drive to get to
So I can scream and yell and be all crazy and get all my your nature everything out
But be cool, like I just, like I got all my groceries for the next two weeks and I'm good girl. I'm cool.
But yeah, so Psyche, Psyche, what is coming?
To the streamer world in the future. You'd like to know just about the streamer world or by yourself
You want to know what the streamer world? I don't want to know about myself. I'll never know about myself really well
No, no, no today. I do
Yeah, do a reading for Alex. Do you want a reading?
I I will not if it's bad
It's I mean, I always take it out of the greatest boat anyway, you know, I wanted to well, okay
Here's what I want to know psyche psyche. Do you foresee me achieving world?
Domination, that's all we're looking for
World domination. Well, I would see yeah, Melissa will see if the answer comes up or something like that, you know
I think I can I think I can do it
Do you want to do it? Okay. Well, it's like, you know, I think that you can too. I think, especially, you know, it's like, uh,
I don't want to know anything else
Okay. Well, no, but let me ask you from because a psychic is great for business stuff
Okay, yeah, okay
Being that you've arrived you've appeared you're here because I've seen everyone talks about you
But you're a man of mystery, okay
Do you foresee?
somehow the communities that you've appeared in blowing up to where it's financially prosperous
to those involved, is that why you have appeared?
Well, that's, yeah, well, just personally, I will say, yes, I did come to like increase
the panel verse and to like, you know, really inspire people to like start their own panels.
And I really believe like panels are like one of the waves of the future that it will
really take off.
There's like, it's a very under tapped thing right now.
There's like, because everyone knows everybody almost like in these panel versions, because
they're so small right now, right?
And so it's like, oh, yeah, I'll let you join Tommy, I didn't see backstage.
Hold on.
Let me see.
Oh, I'm scared.
I will leave if he comes up.
No, you don't want to tell me?
You don't want to tell me?
Okay, I don't know how.
I'll keep it backstage.
I'll keep it backstage right now.
And I just wanted to come up and say hi to you, Alex.
Thank you for supporting me and, you know, being there when I'm,
you know, having a hard time.
And I'll let you in.
Thank you, Alex.
I think like I saw like are you well are you did you call the police because you might need
to call the police on what happened just so you know I did like a couple weeks ago before it
happened because there's other incidents that were like you know rising to what happened but
I just updated you know um what happened the incidents but I'm good I'm gonna be good and
I do want to meet up and have like a lunch or something or like a little hot stuff.
It'll be over a month from now.
I am on the West Coast right now, but I'm healing like, as you know, I like I went through stuff.
Um, maybe me you and psyche I was still no, I'm probably gonna like live out here
I'm thinking that I want to live out here permanently really it's like I feel better. So
I love it here. So I love the weather. I mean it's worth it
But um, yeah, I'll let you guys talk and it was nice talking to you Alex psyche. Thanks for letting me up and summer
Thanks for letting me up too
More see you guys
Yeah
Okay, I don't want to control your panel if you know you're not at all. Yeah, but like no, no, he's not here
It's just been too much. I got I got I don't wish the worst for him. I just don't want to talk to him. That's okay
Tell me everything that you think about me because you're psychic and I want to know how psychic you are
Let's go. Hey, I see like a lot of like
conflict there's some conflict around you okay so it's like you've got you've overcome a lot of
stuff okay it's like but it's like it is like you know it's taking a lot of strength in on your
part and it's like to change and it's like and still I think that this is like another time in
your life there's another site there's another cycle about to end and it's like and it's been a
maybe a difficult cycle the cycle I don't know what to do and my dad passed away in March and I
used the IRL community as a means to act out.
I decided to combat that guy, Zaea, and his girlfriend, Babs.
And what else did I do?
I've done a lot.
I got kicked out of a bar on stream,
which I've never even been kicked out of a bar before,
but I did that.
So I feel like anyone who wanted to laugh at me
for me being at my lowest, they got it. But it was because my dad was my best friend. And
losing him has been a bit much for me. But I didn't want anyone in the communities to know
about it, but it came out. But I don't mind. I think it was a blessing in disguise, really,
because I need it to vent. And now people kind of know that I'm a bit of a different person because I
You know my life is different now
Anyway, that's it. Well, you know, I relate to you my dad passed away last year in April and it's like just like the worst
I'm sorry. Yeah, that's why you know, it's it is one of the hardest things but then it's like, you know
If you have this were you were you close?
Yes, very good. We have lunch every week. You know, which is very close and he was but he was you know
Very you know quite in his 80s and things like that. And so do you feel older being that he's passed since it happened?
a little bit, but I'm still haven't gone gray,
but yeah, I do feel like, I feel kind of like,
I'm not married.
I feel a little wiser.
I feel like he's with me.
Like he's like more to me, like in my mind,
like more to me advice and like,
I'm kind of like, you know, take after him in certain ways.
And so, I feel like he's with me
and I feel like he can see me, you know, it's crazy, but.
Yeah.
It's like I didn't think it was gonna happen at this point
I thought I was gonna be older for some reason when it happened. I didn't think it was gonna be like now
but you know
Okay, so anyway, let's talk about like like happy or even controversial stuff. What do you want to know about me?
Well, I do
I do I do some questions for you. I just want to tell you real quick this read this reading right here
Okay, so we have this strength right here. It's like in a strength
It's like the strength has these two alligators right there alligators right there
But it's like this is the strength card is about like I guess the person that's all we're doing tarot cards
Okay, we're here with some tarot. Yeah, we'll just prepare for you
Okay, so this is like if you so if this is like kind of like saying if you face if you face if you come across these
Crocodiles you would probably just like be able to charm your way out of it or something like that. Oh, it's like
Yeah, that's like that's like the strength is about like more like being you know
you attract
You know things too hot
I'm good at high-crisis situations. Mm-hmm. Okay. Yeah, because I mean then we have the good tower
I don't know if you had a tower moment or something like that
But you also had this connection like we you know, maybe you were like an isolation or something
But you still had this connection with the other world if the golden cord or whatever as Rapunzel's hair
But the thing is okay, we got the okay, we got
we got the tower which is like the end of a cycle and then we got the world which is also the end
of a major cycle like coming to a completion that's the completion of a cycle the the world is like
number 21 okay there's not number number 22 there's number zero through 21 and so this is the card
zero which is right so but they kind of like are right next to each other so the so what's
interesting is it went the world which is like the last card right then went the full which is
the new beginning going on a new beginning where you don't know where
kind of where you're going and then we have the part after the fool is the magician and the magician and see
it's this one and he uh magic you're gonna gain yeah your magic and you're gonna gain you're gonna
learn magic or you've learned or learning magic and uh i do know some magic okay
Well, good. I don't know if it's in this tradition or something like that, but then I have to be against you or yeah
I think I know magic. I think you're I think your reading is really accurate really really so far
I think that you're like more in the present than in the future
Yeah, well, that's what I because I don't I think the future is kind of up to God and ourselves, right?
Or is it ourself if we believe in God or we believe in our higher power or whatever? I think that yeah new new like new beginnings
I'm totally in a new beginning right now 100 and a million percent. Yes
Yes, and the magic part. It's weird because I feel like I
Feel like in a weird way that the ending like
In my family, I've had two major life things
in my, from my perspective, happen
that I never thought would happen, okay?
I never thought that I would have seen my nephew born
in the delivery room, but I saw that, right?
And I never thought I would have been in the room
when my father passed away and I saw that too.
So I feel like I've seen the cycle of life.
And it's humbled me to where I'm not worried about things that I thought were so grand
and so big.
They seem so miniscule to me now, and I'm grateful for that lesson.
That's where I'm at in life at this moment.
Yeah, the most important things in life are not things right so we would learn like along the way
I became a minimalist when I started my first journey of self-discovery because I'd always been the girl
With a million shoes all the new handbags. Well, you know, I'm saying
and I
I got everything I thought I wanted
Then I realized it was nothing but just shackles holding me down
And I changed my life and I never looked back and I think I made the best decision being a minimalist
Who is nomadic?
Mm-hmm, and I like it. It hasn't been the best with relationships like of the romantic variety
but I
Haven't been the best version of myself either and I wouldn't have wished
myself fine.
No, maybe some people.
Capricorns will think that. Capricorns will, like,
I think, like, I relate to that whereas, like, you know,
it's like, until I'm perfect, I'm not, I'm not, like,
I don't want to subject someone to me, because I feel like
I'm such a, yeah, I'm like a, you know,
we got, I'm like, very independent
go walking up that mountain.
I don't think I'm, well, that's the thing, like,
I'll have flings and whatnot,
and I'll have full-fledged
relationships, but
I've just thought about it and I don't wish myself on anybody really because I can be
a bit much but not not so much that but also I do value the personal development
of another person and sometimes I can be even though I'm the age I am and I'm not young I'm
which does make dating hard. It's like even guys my age, physically they're older than me,
but mentally they're still substantially younger than me.
Yeah, well, it's like that's gonna be men. It's like women are like kind of like in this mother role and men are like an
It's eternal child role almost I've seen this dynamic between a lot of men. I wish I could be eternal child
That'd be so much. Yeah, right. It's like but yeah, it's like our childhood always it goes so fast
You know, but it's like but it is like the women that are like the nurturers the boys are kind of like the destroyers, right?
And so it's like and that's it. Yeah, I don't know if this is gender role or it's like, you know, just like well
You know, I think that's why daughters miss their father
when their father passes because I had you know I there was a lot of controversy in my family
because my dad was LGBTQ he came out when I was 14 okay it really negatively impacted my mom
understandably so but I was always close to my dad and I think that
even if you're a strong, independent woman,
if you have that strong relationship with your dad,
your dad is the one person that babies you, okay?
And that makes you feel like,
I can still be a little girl sometimes, yay, you know?
And I think that is really what I'm gonna miss the most
because he was,
And I got to be careful with dating because I don't want to, you know, be with a guy who's
going to infantize me or anything, but, you know, just not having that immediate,
like one thing my dad would always do for me is make me my favorite beverage no matter what it was
when I would go to, you know, stop by his house, right? And it's just little things like that.
That you know, you don't have and that if you're a strong independent woman or man even and
Your parents who is the one person who babies you you don't have that you're like, oh my god
I got to be a grown-up forever now
Now what?
Yeah, I know. It's like, uh, it's just crazy life moves so fast and, you know, and we got
up, yeah, we got to, you know, grow up sometime, but it's like, I mean, I, I too, like, he
would, they come over, my dad would like come pick me up for lunch and we go to like, you
know, one of his favorite places. Yeah, there it was. Yeah, there was just be like, yeah,
just be like, oh, my boy, he always seen me as like, you know, as like, yeah, let's really,
I really missed that a lot. Well, that's why like, okay, here's a dark thought. Okay.
This is when I go into evil, Alex,
because sometimes I get mad about this
when it comes to people that I think are parents
that don't appreciate their kid, okay?
I don't feel any of us ask to be born, okay?
I feel like, you know, if we're here, great,
we should cherish it, love it, be grateful.
But as a parent, when you really think about it,
It's one of the most selfish vain
Egotistical things to become a parent because at some point you're gonna die and
Then your kid no matter how old the kid is they can be in their 60s
They're gonna be like
You left me
right
And that's and that's what you got to understand about being a parent and if you're a parent
I know what I said you're gonna be like fuck Alex, but I don't care because
When you die your kids gonna miss you so much
That's the thing
so it's almost like I think like okay so there's Adam and Eve right and they're
like so they're in heaven yeah I think the reason they got kicked out of the
Eden whatever is because they took the you know ate the fruit but what the fruit
did is like she got pregnant you know okay so yeah and that's why when you
get pregnant and say that that if they were immortal before but then they have
reproductive so reproduction indicates like death right so they can so if
If they live, if they have a real life, they die, but so it's like, it's different than the eternal.
It's like when they were eternal, they were immortal, but it's like when they had sex.
that they don't need to be immortal anymore.
Well, there was a lot that had, I mean, first off,
like I consider myself a Christian,
but I know damn well that the King James version
and modern English version, whatever version of the Bible,
there's a lot omitted when it comes to Genesis
and when it comes to the Garden of Eden
and all that stuff, okay?
I think...
that there were a lot of false trial runs when it came to whatever was happening at that stage of
Humanity and I think that to this day some of the
Trial runs that were not Adam and Eve. I think that the offspring still exists and has intermingled
And I think everyone's a big mixture of everything that went on
from that point, and maybe even before that, who knows.
I know there could be like mythical beings in our ancestry too, like, you know,
Oh, well, I mean, you know about the whole Lilith.
Yeah, I was going to say Lilith.
Yeah, I mean, Talmud, right?
And then you have the Nephilim and the giants and then the flight supposedly didn't wipe everything out.
I mean, there's so, I think anything that you can imagine exists.
I always my mom told me that her mom told her that and I believe it because I've seen some wild shit in my life and
I just think that whatever
Like I don't think any religion is right. I like Christianity because it makes me feel good. I will admit this
Yeah, it makes me feel great. That's what I was raised with it works for me
But my only thing is I just feel like no matter who you are
try to think that there's something outside of you
because that way you don't get so stressed.
That's how I feel about it.
I think that just to keep your stress level down.
Yeah, and also just to almost like,
life becomes meaningless if you have no nothing to live for.
So if you think like, if you're just like,
there's no God, there's nothing like nothing exists.
Well, they're just like death and.
Where's a lot by coincidence by randomly or whatever that like puts Rick Dury like little like incentive in the
I think that there's I mean, I think we basically do have proof. I mean, I know some people like there's no proof
Yeah, there is I
Think that there's been enough stories enough digital evidence
Enough everything to where you know that you don't just appear like I feel like whenever I die however
I'm gonna be somewhere and yeah, and we were somewhere before we were somewhere before here and we'll be somewhere after right
We don't like we don't just like just appear out of nowhere and then just disappear into nowhere
Well, I think that's why sometimes we're drawn to certain people and sometimes we don't even know why
But it's because we recognize them from wherever we were before
Or maybe wherever we're going because some people don't believe that time is real. I personally don't I think that time is
Experiences, but I think that that's why a lot of Native Americans
Have such an interesting like viewpoint opposed to the Western system of belief
I don't think that they experience, if they're truly into the old ways, they don't experience
time.
And I think also, like sometimes people are like, oh, so and so from such culture lives
an amazingly long life, maybe they'll be a time the same.
Because if you're always stressed about the constructs that we deal with, I mean, social
media has hammered it into our spirits unlike anything before.
then, yeah, you're gonna age quick. That's why I think that people like, you know, in the generation
before me, they look old as hell. It's the stress, because it's speeding up time for it. And you've
got to just look at it like, the way I look at the internet, I think it's giving us a glimpse
as to how God has viewed us as God's creation.
Well, I think he loves us right as like as like a father kind of like your father and mother like like a parent kind of like
That's why he like let's us get away with everything and gives us free will because we're kind of like Brad
Yeah, well, I think that's why I think that the New Testament was when God was like, okay
I'm gonna be like the hippie jam-fest guy because I gotta create an avatar to talk to y'all and that's what Jesus was
and I think that
God would felt really bad about the Old Testament because I like the Old Testament God better the
angry God because I'm an angry bitch. I get so angry at so many things and I'm just like ah
but that's why I like reading the Bible because like God I I get why God got so frustrated with
everything because God was like giving God was doing so much and even though the
people actually got to literally see the miracles they're like when you know
what that's not enough that we have the Ark of the Covenant and we get to
actually see a miracle and something come down now that's not enough we got
to see something else and we're gonna complain and we don't even like this
manna okay
It's like, you know, but it's like almost like, you know, like how kids, like, you know, parents can try to impress the kids so much and then they're like, you know, like, yeah, well, I mean, well, if you if you read the Bible, like when when Moses had to like, you know, get his people out of Egypt and everything, they were in a weird way.
more comfortable in Egypt as slaves than when they had to be in the wilderness.
Yeah, the wilderness.
And they didn't understand the value of freedom because, I mean, it was multi-generated.
Like Moses was living. He was like, I'm alive.
But there were generations of other families who weren't as blessed or genetically strong.
and they were dying while they were out there and you know people are like well maybe we didn't
need to go in the desert you know and that's it it does parallel to what's happening in the
united states in a weird way you know some people feel like well i'm okay with low wages as long as
i can just be but other people want more freedom but then there's a price for freedom so it's it's
Yeah
No freedom apply freedom also implies slavery because they're it's like the duality right so they're so that's like you know
Well, that's why slavery in the United States lasted as long as it did because a lot of the people who are slaves
Didn't want to be enslaved because they knew that being free
Was going to be more expensive and more difficult
Than being an indentured servant. I mean there were there were Europeans who were also basically on the same tier
as Black slaves in pre-Civil War times that people don't talk about that, but that was
happening.
Thank you, psyche.
You're welcome.
It's Joe.
What's up, Alex?
What's up, Joe?
How are you doing?
Joe came on my panel.
You were better than you say one thing.
You were so sweet to me the other night, Alex.
I just can't even believe how sweet you were, sweetheart.
You made my whole week.
You made my whole week better.
You know what, Joe?
You're doing a good job, you're doing a good job on the day.
Because I've had more drama than I think most, and I think I said everything that needs to be said.
So I'm not starting any new fights with anybody, I'm just like, here.
Alex don't deserve this psyche. Don't act like you're not listening to a psyche.
He was listening.
I'm trying to pin the link, but it's like...
He's listening.
She's super interesting, and I've been wanting to talk to her for a long time. Well, actually,
I thought Mr... Yeah, so I hasn't been missing big pipes. I was like...
Okay, okay. Psyche. Psyche, do you think I'm going to have a good 2025 the rest of the year?
I do. Yeah, I think the rest of the year is gonna be great for you, but I can pull a card on that
Okay, so you first you got the moon, okay, so the moon says there's like a lot of surprises and secrets like a lot of stuff to be revealed
All this big, you know, just like I think a lot of like new discoveries and stuff like that
Okay, you got a seven of wands, which means like, you know, you're gonna. Oh, that's my lucky number seven
I'm January 7th to I'm January 7th to the same exact
Yeah, we are
That's crazy, okay
All right, look, I never know.
I only know one other person who has my birthday.
All right.
Who is that?
We're going to be best friends.
We are going to be fucking best fucking friends.
Oh my God.
Are you really, are you really January 7th?
Yeah, January 7th, 19th, you were alive to recite.
Are you serious?
This is awesome man. This is what it's about. This is what it's about man. Wow. I'm so excited.
You know what? My birthday is January 7th. Holy shit. Oh my god.
Oh my god. It's not. It's not. It's not. I want to read it. I actually have this,
I just take a little thing about capricorn women because I know because because January 7th,
like it's hardly anybody is born on January 7th.
That is a rare birthday.
That's rare.
It's Orthodox Christmas.
It's crazy.
It's Christmas in Russia too.
It's a Christmas day in Russia.
Yes.
Yeah.
Hardly anybody has January 7th as a birthday.
It's also a little sad.
It's nine months before January 7th,
because that's the month that your parents had sex.
Nine months before January 7th.
Yeah.
It was like a brown Easter.
They had sex on Easter.
Well, there you go.
They had a little Easter sex and then psyche popped out.
Yeah, yeah, psyche appeared, everyone's appearing.
Okay, so I'll read it. I'll read you back
Let me see. So Capricorn. I like your new glasses. Like yeah, I do even there. There are women's glasses. They still look good
I mean, I'm training these in
Okay, so if you love on a Capricorn woman, it says it's a good thing
I was born a woman or I would have been a drag queen dolly pardon every
Capricorn woman has a built-in sense of style and social grace whether her personality is an outgoing adult partner
Or as coolly reserved as Eva Gardner her basic character is practical and sensible
She seeks a mate who is strong and ambitious, who has plans for the future,
since she appreciates the best things in life, planning to take her to the final restaurant.
Oh, and be sure to bring a final restaurant. Oh, be sure to bring along your stock portfolio
and a copy of your family tree, because- Say it loud! Say it proud, man! Say it loud!
One or the other doesn't push her. So I'm so impressed, but she'll never consider you as a
serious match. Leo may be a queen, but Lady Capricorn is pure diva. She can be as emotional as
a cancer at a pity party or as pushy as Aries on a power trip.
She's so sad is conscious that she won't plan a vacation right now. You're right
To see where the years in spot is located
She'll pay a hundred dollars for a hairdryer if she hates if it's the latest style from the hottest law in the town
In public she'll be the model of social demeanor because she's always on the lookout for someone
At home you'll eat in the kitchen and watch tv in the bedroom because she's afraid you'll get a spot on the table cloth
Or wrinkle the fabric on the sofa. She spends the hour of the day walking through the house on table called
the
Okay, so
So look down on the one who's content to own one service station instead of a gas company and fawn over the one
Who just got pulled from jail for creative accounting the former she views as lazy to ladders inspired?
Capricorn hookers are just a snooty mayflower madam Sydney and Biddle Barrow's and Hollywood madam Heidi flights who are each respectively
Capricorn really I did not know that that is interesting Wow
Makes sense.
They were just as selective about their clientele,
just as socially aware of their public.
When asked to comment about being busted,
Biddle said, the reporter, never say anything on the phone
that you wouldn't want your mother to hear at your trial.
When Plyce was bored,
she had to straight for the Plyce Surgeon.
I had a lot done, she said.
Lips, eyes, ears, boobs.
Being in prison with no skin care
really doesn't number on you.
Yours probably won't be as blindly ambitious,
but she'll have a definite tendency to embellish the truth
of the tea time conversation with friends
during some family stories.
Her Aunt Mabel, who's the hog-calling champion of West Virginia, might evolve into a much-revered
acapella singing Star of the South.
The Lady Goat is a humor challenge as her male counterpart and will moat for days of
any off-handed teasing.
Her jokes wish to set on dim and the only time she really smiled is when an empty-in-the-cookie
jar banged to buy another savings-bond.
Romantically, she may swing both ways, but she's on into swinging from the chandelier.
However, don't confuse Sirius with Sexless.
Capricorn Megas starred Merlene Dietrich was known as a love pirate.
for the shocking ease at which she stole spouses and lovers away from their partners.
Really?
Look what happened.
She expects me to pursue a mood and put in the mood, which may get a bit tiresome after
five or six years.
Tossing a diamond between the sheets is a surefire way to get her into bed, to dive
in bed.
Or if you aren't rich, make it a granola bar.
Capricorn women love little gifts that are always on a diet.
True.
Whether it's the life of the party or the classic women behind the man, keeping up appearances
in long trip security mean more to a Capricorn woman than either a warm blanket or your warm
So there you go, that was awesome. Thank you for reading that. That was that was awesome. How do I send you like
I find it when I log off here, I will yeah, it's on my banner right there, or it'll be much in my chat
I apologize, but
Can you do this can you do that with your eyeballs? Can you are you rolling your eyes? Why are they well white?
Why your eyes all white?
Oh my gosh, you're very cute.
But I was gonna, yeah, I heard about that.
But I was always kind of afraid of you
because I was like, oh my gosh.
And then I was like, and then I was like,
I didn't want to like talk about you
when you weren't here on the channel, you know?
Cause people would bring you up sometimes.
I can be, I can definitely be,
I'm actually searching for my sunglasses
other than talking to you.
I don't know where I put them.
But no, I can be a certain way,
I can definitely be a certain way.
But we all could be a certain way try not to be especially nowadays
A lot of people start fights on the internet, right?
Well, I try to fight for what's right.
And I get drawn into a lot of things that I probably should not be drawn into.
That's really what it is.
It happened on the internet because it's a different kind of place.
It's like so connected and so like...
Yeah, and it's also...
I haven't been willing to admit that I'm a part of a certain community that without a doubt...
I've been a part of, but I don't exactly want to acknowledge, because I don't like the bad
habits of it.
Yeah, I mean, it's like, you don't have to share everything, but it's like, you know,
I don't know if they give it, I mean, people will probably, well, it's your cat's cat's
But I can take things pretty easy.
So I can give it to, like, somebody else.
Get the banner.
The banner.
The banner, Joe.
Okay, so yeah, but Alexander like so yeah, but you're really I know I know you were really open about your you're more kind of an interesting past
I get unconventional past as well. Yeah, you know, and I have no judgment there or anything like that
So I bet I just judge it's okay like flirty diamond came in pretty flirty diamond came in judging like, you know
I'm not gonna speak on her because I'm just not
There's just something about her to where I said something and then she took it very far and I decided it was better
I know Alex actually has morals well. Yeah, so, you know, I'm you know a lot of people to come up
What are the morals really because sometimes
you know, what might be a moral or an ethic to one person.
Well, say now.
You could have attacked Flirty Diamond, but you're being, you're being moral.
You're like, I'm not going to talk about it if I'm not here.
You're being a gentleman.
Yeah, I'm chosen not to say anything about that.
Yeah, but what I'll say is, yeah, but the morals, like morals is like, you know, if like, even if you're even if you're like, and, you know, hardcore porn, what if you like have a child at home, you're trying to like, you know, feed and stuff like that.
Moral.
Yeah.
Well, like, that's something that a lot of people in the adult industry didn't agree with me about is that I feel like if you have a kid that you are immediately.
taking care of, you shouldn't do anything adult-oriented.
Right you shouldn't you shouldn't but it's like I mean some so I mean I'm just I was making the example as in like
You know, there's moral things like what if you have like a sick, you know, or somebody's sick or you need to like make money
It's like I don't have a judgment about sex work or anything like that. It's like, you know, it's fine
Yeah, but it's like, you know, I'm sure there will be some
Exceptions, you know, I mean and that's the thing there's always exceptions to where like you
Like there's been times where I'm standing on my, you know, high horse, but then I see a situation to where the person is just
and whatever it is that they're doing that normally
I wouldn't agree with.
So everything's a case by case basis, everything.
Yeah, yeah.
I'm not racist, no, not everybody, sweetheart,
not everybody.
We wanna, we wanna like, but we also like wanna like,
not just like think what everybody else thinks of us.
I wasn't talking about racism.
I was talking about case by case basis.
I know I thought you said we all like nachos.
I don't know about you, but I like it a lot.
I wasn't talking about nachos.
Oh, sorry about that, sweetheart.
Why don't you speak up a little bit, Alex?
You know, I love you, but I need to hear you, sweetie.
Okay.
Well, why don't you listen more carefully backstage, Joe?
Anyway.
Okay.
It's kind of getting in the middle of the interview.
Like, yeah, so, yeah, so.
I have no judgment on anybody, but it's great.
You know, it's like, especially because it looks like,
it sounds like you like to really change your life
in like a really, really awesome way.
And you're a great speaker and you're like a very charming person.
Do you have a show and like, what's your show about?
Like, I think you do have a show.
I don't really have a show.
It can be my show.
Yeah, it's my Alexandra Mayer show.
I'm on different things on the internet.
I'm trying to get some sunglasses going here
to where I can turn my camera on and go back outside
because I want to have a cigarette
and talk to you on video because you're fun to talk to.
And it's great.
Yeah, it's great talking to you.
I was hoping, like, yeah, so I'm going to tell you today,
I was like, oh, I hope I get to talk to her someday.
I wonder if she ever comes to the show.
I was afraid to talk to you because I was like,
I didn't know, like,
Like like how psychic are you like are you gonna send me like a psychic attack?
Like oh, no, I never do I would never do that
Worst thing I would ever do to anybody's return to sender like if they were to send energy to me
I would like to send the energy well. Do you think that that maybe happens automatically?
Well, yeah, I believe I do have like protectors or else, you know
I wouldn't because I think there's like a lot of stuff
I don't not aware of like being sent at me that I'm protected from because it's like it's just well
Be careful on the internet because supposedly I don't know if it's true or not
But supposedly spiritually when you're on the internet
You're more prone to psychic attack, but you can shield yourself just by like being like, you know, I'm of the light. I'm good
go away evil both of you're gonna have a lot more exposure to like the basically the demonic and
demonic influence like the demons around there and the demons like are like in a different kind of
thing like and so is that you'll have
They on the internet they like can replicate they're like replicated that's they've been waiting for the internet to come out
Basically so they can like live on there and like become electric and like replicate and be all over and get
Yeah, maybe yeah
Well, I mean, I think that there is a spiritual component to the internet and especially to social media and how we
You know interact with each other how we're drawn or even repelled by one another
through social media, because it is energy. I mean, it's actual
literal physical electronics that we're using. I mean, that's
that's why I think we are in the fourth dimension.
Well, the AI is just dealing with the AI is like so so like
powerful than I thought like technology could be like for
the AI to be so powerful. Is it right now that it's like so
fast?
I'm happy with the AI. I'm gonna tell you why. I think the AI is
It's gonna make people's dreams come true.
That's what I think.
Yes.
Oh yeah, already is.
It's like just like, oh, the internet is too.
Like just like, just for me to be able to have a show,
like where I can like have my own show
and design it and make money from it
and be monetized through the thing
and like have fans and stuff like that
to have that opportunity.
Like I would never be able to do that in the 80s.
It's like, I'd have to go to a broadcasting school.
But here's the thing,
like here's where I have to interrupt you.
Yeah.
you're willing to accept help from the AI.
There's people who are super against the AI
and it's because they're not willing to accept help.
They don't want to admit that they need help.
It's like arachnid, you know, if you've heard, you know, reek mythology,
arachnid was like the best weaver and she was like the most talented weaver
and she really was, but then she like went against the goddess Athena
and like, who actually taught her how to weave.
Oh, I didn't know that story.
Is that a reek mythology?
Yeah, it's Arachnian. She was better than Athena, but she like embarrassed the gods by posting. She like put the gods up. She was, she like weaved the gods embarrassing moments. And then like Athena would, it was in a contest with her and like weaved all like the heroic moments. And then so she won, but she was better. But then Athena was still the goddess. And so she like, she was ashamed. She like hung herself. And then she turned into a spider. Athena turned into a spider.
Oh, wow.
So that's Arachnian. Arachnian is right.
It's a good story, a really interesting story.
But yeah, it's like, there's like this perfection
that we can work with, talented people can work with the AI
and make something better instead of work.
Well, it's an assistant.
It's like the best, okay, I can do, let's see.
Okay, I got my cyborg sunglasses on
Yeah, like horrible. I'm turning it back off. Okay
These are my reading glasses. I'm getting a new pair of glasses. Actually, I got this Jeffrey Dahmer style
Like everyone I was in the beef sector started out and they call me Jeffrey Dahmer and so but it's
Sometimes you got to find your inner your inner demon your inner
Yeah, but I'm a lot. I'm a lot better. I'm I don't you know, I'm glad mine is not
But that is Jeffrey Ballmer, but I'm not into cannibalism or, you know, but...
Well, I doubt you are.
I doubt you are.
You know, when you think about it, like racially, you know, racially.
White guys got a bad rap for that because the serial killers who were white guys were good-looking guys
Like that they just were I might have been a sigh. Oh, you know, it might have been part of the sigh
Like if you're a good-looking white guy people are gonna think you're a serial killer
I think it's part of the thing that's part of like the Psyop is like to like make people like fear white people
Yeah, yeah, like I think things you know white people are like what well
I think that's why I've been attacked in a certain way
And it's been because I grew up in a situation to where I never had any racism any prejudice nothing
But thing after thing after thing to where it was undeniable and then it's like you're like, okay
Okay, maybe it's racism, but then like you got a backtrack because you're like, well, maybe this wasn't maybe this wasn't
You know and but you get paranoid because of certain things that I do believe are psyops. Yes. Yeah
Well, yeah, and it's like well, especially like, you know, like, you know, some of these mass
sho otin gs like, you know, I think that's trying to do the
control, you know, and then
Yeah, so and then just to steer the culture in this direction of like, you know, hating certain
things. A lot of times when those things happen, they mislabel the person. It's been a lot of
multiracial people who have done that, but they always by default say white or black. They don't
say multiracial.
Because they always want to like emphasize the black and white because it's such that's like the big
duality, right? It's like the black versus the white, like the checkerboard or the chessboard. Well, it's actually not. It's not like
I can't say it as like a blanket statement, but as a black woman my experience in life
It has been people who you're like, what is that person who are the most racist toward you if you're black opposed to the person who is like straight out of Norway.
And is it whether black people?
Yeah.
I get more racism from people who might be Latino or Latina than somebody who's like undeniably white.
Yeah, I would agree with that. I see it like a lot of racism and a lot of other races like you know
The most some of the most racist people nowadays are Latinos, you know, it's like they're like you mean like
The racism is whites, you know, so it's like so well then on top of that if you're a black person
Who doesn't fit the mold of being stereotypically black?
They're gonna want to define you as something else to where you don't even get a chance to be black anymore
Last time I had my driver's license written in.
I'm a Florida resident, okay?
So like every two years, you have to go in
instead of doing it on the internet, which is fine,
you know, but I went in and I've always listed myself
black female.
Last time I went in, they were like,
what do you want to list yourself, Latino or black?
And I'm like black and they're like, are you sure?
And I said, yes, I'm positive, non-Hispanic, black.
Yeah, well, soon they're going to ask about you.
There are people in my family who listen to themselves as Hispanic or other.
They don't listen to themselves as black anymore.
You should be able to like also like identify as different
is whatever you want nowadays, right?
So they'll ask you, oh, do you want to change your sex
on their driver's license?
What do you identify now?
Because now it's like, we just think it's all about it.
I'm going to be a Japanese male.
Yeah, there was one transgender that says,
I'm going to be a starfish.
She's like, I'm going to be a, I'm a stardust.
C slash urchin or something like that.
I don't know.
I mean.
If you don't feel like you're something, I guess you shouldn't be it, but I just think about, like, my entire life experience, regardless of where I've gone, for the most part, has been black female, that's me.
Sometimes it's been positive, sometimes negative, sometimes neutral. I mean, for the most part, and I travel more than the average person.
For the most part especially being in my later middle-aged years
No one is going to question
The single black female at all. I mean the last time I was in DC even I
Did the tour of the White House and I got and I did get lost from the group because I'm retarded
And I was walking around nobody said one word to me nobody and that's how it is because
everyone thinks I'm somebody's mom or you know that's just what it is no I don't cause
trouble you never see what my demographic is on the news for doing anything we're government
I better pull up the chat.
I hear you now, I hear you now.
Okay, I was gonna pull up the chat.
I don't even know what I do with my device.
Thanks for letting me be on your panel today. It's like I'm no problem. It's pleasure. No, are you?
It's it's uh, well psyche is actually the goddess, you know, the goddess and a mythology. There's a whole myth about her so
But there's people call me both. I like psych too, you know, so it's like is more like a male person. Yeah
Oh, yeah, okay. Well, what is your prediction for?
the United States when it comes to
Financial prosperity for people between now and
Christmas
Financial prosperity. Yeah, okay. I'll pull a card for it, but I do feel like it's like gonna be like really good
It's gonna be better than people think it's like everyone everyone's like fatalizing things but the economy is gonna be fine
Like it's like there's like
I think that there's a lot of stuff happening
like that a lot of our opportunities
are coming up for people too.
Well, that's good.
So like do you think now would be a good time
for people to not procrastinate
and get on top of like whatever their dream
work at home business is?
Right, and I think whatever it is,
it's like YouTube could be a great part of that business
because it's like it is just so.
Yeah.
So great. So many people so great at like, um, so like,
help promote your business or to have like the interaction and the engagement
with your audience and more people should take advantage of you being in this
community. When I really think about it, because like,
I consider myself intuitive in a certain way,
which I'm not going to go into in your live stream.
But do you feel that watching the streamers at times being that
you have the gifts that you have?
that sometimes you feel almost like you're destined to somehow, even anonymously,
warn them about things that maybe they overlook.
Not just from an observer's perspective,
but being that you have your gifts.
Have you ever been frustrated to where you're like,
oh my God, I want to warn so and so,
but they're not listening.
How do you feel about that?
Does it hurt you?
I feel like the people who get the messages they're supposed to from me, they'll hear at
the right time.
We'll be in the same places at the right time.
The card will come up with the right message that will come up for them.
And so I just really just focus on that, like the right message will get to them, or there
is a reason I'm here, and it is to bring messages to people I do believe in.
something I'll say maybe well, you know, I don't know
I just feel like everything's meant to be like how it is like, you know
How I turned out of like how it's supposed to
You know, we kind of like make a soul contract when we get here
We kind of I think we know when we're gonna yeah
Yeah
Our soul knows a lot of stuff and so it knows more than us and it will like always like
you know, if we made it this far, it obviously is helping us out, keeping an eye on us and
keeping us safe, because we're still safe, you know, and we made it through like difficult
situations, I'm sure, and you know, I know you have. Well, I mean, when you think about,
I mean, we all have our personal issues, but just the fact that we're literally on a ball of dirt.
hurtling through the universe at a billion miles an hour.
And we haven't been knocked out by a comet.
That's pretty good.
So I think that we're meant to be here for some reason.
Right.
And I also feel like we all are one.
Like we're all, we're all in this duality.
So we have like a billion different people personalities.
But in the end, we're all like,
we're all the same, we're all different, right?
We're all like-
Do you believe in the multiverse?
Um, yeah, I mean you're talking about like more like, you know, the or the matrix or like the fifth dimension fourth dimension like
Well, like every every choice or opportunity that we have creating another reality
To where there's multiple versions of ourselves
like some people believe that we can even somehow
If you have a strong enough personality, maybe you can leapfrog to a
Version of yourself that's more beneficial than maybe a version of reality where you made a bad choice. Oh
Yeah, oh, yeah, and when that be great, I think it's called maybe hacking the matrix or it's like our
Timeline jumping I think do you think that's even ethical when you think I mean, let's really think about that
Look, let's say there's like a weaker version of yourself that somehow is
In a better position than you are in right now, but you figure out how to hack
um the multiverse and then you leapfrog into another version of yourself what happens to that
other version of yourself did they get tossed into where you were? It's like the back to the
future thing it's like you don't know what's going to happen if you interfere with these timelines
you know it's yeah you can sleep with your own like you know like the guy and back to the future
he fell in love with his own mom or she was him or she was interested in him or something like that
So it's like it is interesting to think about interfering. I think I watch Quantum Leap if you
ever see that old show. I used to love that show. That was one of my favorite shows.
Yeah, and that's why I kind of like what it is. I think that uh,
Realitate Must've Alright, it didn't arrive. It was, that was an old message, but it will be here
probably hopefully soon. I'm gonna get this tape to tape on my tripod. It's, I've just, you know,
used it so much it's falling apart, so.
You got to charge people for your readings mr. Psych because I do very good
I mean thank you that way you can get more money to expand your webcast or your stream or your stream
podcast I do have like um, I do have like you know paid readings or people can of course like you know tip or whatever
But also I have other other monetization things. I mean monetize channel
I also have like you know a couple things on the panel that are monetized like the
Yeah, I think a lot of people would get readings from you.
Yeah, but I do like to just give people, especially for the first time, I like to give them a free
reading and then they can see if they were, you know, I mean, were they similar, you know,
people should just find a psychic that they kind of like they can, they like, you know,
and see, you know, just testing people, but you know, I would say.
I think like a psychic.
is an amplified friend but also a consultant like you you know like we pay
for an attorney in our life if we need that we pay for doctors we pay for lawn
people if you have a house I think that there's a huge part of the populace that
has that that's tapped in you know like more so than some of us are not tapped
And it's a service. I think that it should be paid for. I think I mean you have
politicians who regularly talk to psychics
No, oh, yeah, the Reagan the Reagan's would have a you know
They had a psychic on call that they would plan every every every part of it
No, also the Reagan's what was cool about them were that they were really Hollywood like you know that they were like a Hollywood family
Yeah
Yeah, he was very accurate and stuff. Yeah, and so, yeah, so yeah
Politics are pretty interesting, but it's like we're putting the psychics into that, but the psychics
Yeah, they were actually like really treasure like and they would time everything by the astrology and
It really does work, but it's like and also when people pay for something they do appreciate it more
It seems like and so it's like I like to you know have a good so but I'll pull
I always like would pull a few cars just to let someone test our like for members and stuff like that
But I do I monetize several ways on this channel
and uh and so it's like you know have you ever read for anybody to where like you read their cards
and it scared you um well I can get like weird feelings but I always like try to like look at
things like like the future is not set in stone and so it's like there's always it's maybe a
you know, I never would say someone's going to die if they get the death card in the future position,
right? There might be like a transition for something in your life or somebody,
it could be possibly somebody in your life, but it doesn't necessarily mean you're going to die.
There's nothing that was really going to like...
I don't know. I don't believe in like putting that into people's minds because they can get a self-fulfilling prophecy or they can take
They can see seriously because the psychic is like it does the same kind of service like a bartender or a
You know like a psychiatrist or a life coach or like someone that you talk to
Yeah, you're dealing with the public but also then if people are telling you their problems
And people also want to be listened to and they also want to have their problem looked at and then to have maybe
Someone that's not going to try to like, you know, just give some like skewed advice or relationship advice
They want to hear like what's the real what is there? Is there something I'm not not seeing
There's some are we supposed to be together as a soulmate? There's all these other questions that other people really won't probably address
right when they're
It's like love that goes on on the unconscious when you're dating and meeting people, right? So yeah
Um, you remind me of a little bit is Omarosa. I don't know if you've heard of Omarosa. What do you think?
Are you there?
Your mic might be out, let me see. I don't know if you, hello?
I don't know if you're, are you okay? Are you there? I don't hear you. Is my thing out or is?
Hello?
Oh, okay. Well, that was a pleasure talking to Alexander. Maybe I'll push it back soon. That was cool
Okay, that was pretty cool. So I'm gonna look at my
Email, I think I got I think I'm gonna finish this music video for Alex. I haven't seen him today, but I think it will be fun
Let's have a look if I find the website is okay
Okay neural frames that's what it's called
Okay, you're pulling overheated. Oh shit
Well, pleasure talking to you. Hope you're always welcome back. I'll be um, I'm right here. The panel is open
You and anyone who's welcome here
pleasure talking to you though. Awesome. I love you. I love you
birthday twin
I also met somebody um two like her name is tiger butterflies. She was born on january 7th, but she was born 1980 and then you're now you're 1979
so we got all kinds of uh
All the years, okay, so let me log in here.
I was chat doing, oh, the link, I'm sorry.
Oh, your phone's already, okay, there you go.
There's the link.
I didn't pin that, I didn't pin that.
Yes, you may join Joe, just behave yourself.
I don't know why I didn't pin it, let me see.
Oh yeah, cause I couldn't find my phone, where'd my phone go?
There we go, I didn't pin it, oh, put it down.
Here we go. There we go. Joseph, please, I'm giving a peace sign to show I'm not here for any
I know why you're scared to have an open leg because that gay guy clumsy might join.
I know.
Don't be scared.
Clumsy is not done to be scared about.
He's a little fucking piece of shit.
Don't be scared to him, buddy.
I'm not scared.
I'm not scared of clumsy.
Look, you got terror in your eyes.
You got terror.
Oh, Alex.
Damn, you're looking good, sweetheart.
Oh, my Lord.
Yeah, I don't want to be on camera.
I'm not going to be greedy.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, okay. I'm sorry. No, sorry. Sorry. No, my phone overheated it overheated
Cuz
Let me please talk Alex I joined before you did by one second, but let me just say
Joe Joe psyche, please. Let me get this off my heart
The other day I was on Alex's and she said that I'm such a nice man, it could be the end of the world and I would help Alex and she's right, I would help anybody.
It's true.
And I will always love Alex for that. So let her talk, man.
It's true. I think that Joe, like, like if it was like.
Terminator into the world like judgment day. I think that like
Joe would come running out of nowhere
He would try he would try and the terminators still might terminate him, but he would try to save me
Let me even tell you this, Alex, if it was ever raining, I would take the shirt off my
back and laid on a puddle so you would just walk your little sexy high heels right in
that puddle.
Well, thank you.
Thank you.
I won't get any ringworm.
You know what?
I'll go a step further.
I won't get any ringworm from any puddles.
I want you to walk right over my back.
Walk right over my back.
No, no ringworm from Joe because if there was ringworm in a puddle, Joe would save me.
from that. I would let the puddle and say, Alex, walk on my body. Walk right up my back,
sweet angel. I could do that and I'd be safe. All right. Now, if it was psyche in the puddle,
I'd be like, God, can lighting please strike his ass? Oh, that's too far. Sorry about that.
I love you. What did you say? What did you say, Joe? What did you say to me?
Oh, you're on this panel you're on his literal panel saying I know I'm just
there was a joke great you can't take a lightning joke I don't really want to get
struck by lightning is like he's like he's where it's at because everyone's
on this panel but he's always look at him he thinks he's Johnny Depp but he's
Johnny Depp well he is Johnny he well he's Johnny Depp in here
He looks like a movie star. I'm getting psyched right. He does not look like a movie star.
No, for real, Psyche. You have really good facial features.
That's why I used to say the same thing about Blogger.
You have really, you're like, what's that guy? Hugh Jackman.
You're like
You have
You look like a Hollywood actor who's like tired of acting and you're like I'm just gonna rest and I'm gonna grow
My script and
I'm just gonna, and I'm gonna tap into all these minuscule people who don't recognize me because I'm secretly
a Hollywood actor.
You know Jackie Marlin is from the Howard Stern Show, Alex.
That is just like it.
We've never heard of Jack.
That's who he is.
Alex, listen to me.
Do you know Jackie Marlin is from the Stern Show?
I think that he's secretly a Hollywood actor doing research.
for his acting, script writing debut.
Look at him, look at him, look at him mention his Hollywood face.
That's what he's doing.
Look at him mention his little Hollywood.
Unfortunately, I kind of look like Paul Rubens when he got caught in that porno theater.
I wouldn't go you don't like me you're like a combination of like Hugh Jackman
Who's the other guy Jim Carrey Jim Carrey
It looks like he's between those two actors and like he's
Combined Jim Carrey and Hugh Jackman and guess what you get you get psyche awakens. I love it. Yeah
Yeah, and he's telling us, he's telling us he's trying to hide now.
Look, he's trying to hide.
I know, I know, I blew his cover.
I blew his cover.
You got him.
Yeah, I blew the cover.
Uh-oh.
That's okay.
I don't have a cover.
Like, I'm like really like.
I'm more of like a, I'm more of like a, like a, like a, like a, some kind of spiritual
person.
Okay.
No, they're not really. And other people join or is the only three allowed? I don't know.
Some are paid for the panel. Some are paid for the panel. Alex, I want you to know, Alex,
when I was at work this whole week, I kept playing that clip of how sweet you are to me. It meant
a lot to me. It really meant a lot to me in my heart right here. This is where it hit me, Alex.
I really meant everything that I said and I've known you a long time and we don't always get along
Sometimes we, you know, we've gone at it, but I think that you are a good guy and I
just like talking to you sometimes.
Thank you.
Thank you, Alex.
That's very kind of you to say.
And I love talking to you too.
You letting this panel up.
You think I'd be here with this Johnny deep looking motherfucker.
Yes, you were.
Alex, Alex, Alex, he says that and then you don't know like, you know, I know he's your
He's he's he's he's he's just being him. Well, it's a bloody finger
No
That should be me and alex that should be me and alex kissing can you make one of me and alex?
Oh, you motherfucker
That's not it, look at that.
Oh my God.
Actually, I'm trying to get a boner, actually leave it on.
Oh, look at Kim.
Look at my fucking double neck.
I'm not that fat, I'm actually, oh my God,
what the fuck is that?
What the fuck did I just get?
Oh my gosh.
don't know AI is like gonna like fuck with so many people it's so bad AI is
just I don't have it so it is pissing people off oh it's pissing people off
I want the machines to win because it shouldn't
Seen psyches new pictures. He looks like all Italian with like his hair like he's don't even look like that
Psyche is like blogger they both have that model face they have
We don't have supermodels like they're used to be. I like supermodels
You know what, Sykes is like Marcus Schenkenberg.
He has like a nice sculpted face,
and there needs to be more of them in this world.
I want to see more of that.
He's not even listening to you.
He's on his phone.
Look at him.
Not even listening to us.
He's on his phone.
I'm tired of seeing these Campbell soup kid looking faces.
Show me, show me something like-
You know Campbell soup, motherfucker.
I know, that's why I'm saying it.
I, that's-
Damn.
Oh, don't do that dirty smoking, that face.
whole Hollywood face.
That's what I like.
That's my virtual reality.
Give us your best actor face like you.
Give us your best.
If you had to take a promo picture,
what would your face look like?
Oh my God, that's scary.
No, not that face.
Do something different with your face.
That actually feels like a horror picture.
Do something.
Come on, psyche.
Work your face.
Don't ever do that again.
Show us the model.
Show us the model face like.
Show us the model, first the model, the Mountain Man model.
Your suits, just make a regular face, you fucking animal.
That's what the ladies want.
Oh, the ladies want that?
The ladies want the Mountain Man retired actor writing a script.
The women want Dionysus.
Something like that.
They want cyanide?
Well, so I don't know if they want cyanide.
Not cyanide.
What are you talking about, Joe?
Oh, okay, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it, take it,
I
Mean yeah, I mean it's like it would like women would like to like the game on Amazon warriors
But somebody in your comments that blogger looks like a lunch out of all the notes, I got to give that a little haha, that was pretty funny
Go ahead and leave it back leave it back
I can't tell you how much psyche my week has been so fucking awesome. Just because of the way Alex lit me up this past weekend
My Monday Tuesday Wednesday, I was on top of the fucking world boy
I was on top of the world, but just because of Alex's sweet little comments. That's how sweet she is
So if you got a problem with Alex, you got a problem with me
That's probably gonna last
I mean
I'm I'm I'm I'm I'm on my um I'm on my I'm on my hippie jam fest tour on panels
all right fair enough like my first stop on my tour because I knew he would be the best place to go
so I'm the chat is saying Alex is having thank you chat whoever said that that is so sweet she is
thank you chat see you the chat's loving you Alex
Well, I'll tell you, everybody, if you're able to visit the desert, because if you can visit the desert to reset yourself, it's a good thing to do.
Well, let me tell Psyche something.
Just make sure you're playing gas.
We're going on a horseway, no ass.
What?
I said, I've been through the desert on a horse with no ass.
That's the lyrics, right?
That's the lyrics to the song.
Of course, with no name, I've been through the desert
on a horse with no ass.
Why do you have to ruin the song?
I don't know.
He's not going to ruin it, but we're not going to hear that.
So for reals, tell me more about you.
When do you realize you have the gift?
Well, you know, I'm just like, you know, I'm gay and so I like I always been in touch with my feminine side
I believe women all women have the gift. I believe everyone has the gift
We have a massive feminine side. We have a receptive side where we can like, you know, get messages
I think I'm more open than a lot of other people to the messages
I know our birthday is called the day of unusual interest, you know, yes
Yeah
Yes, okay, so so you think that the gift is more so through the femininity than the masculinity
Well, the feminine is like the magnetic and the masculine is the electric and so they work together
I mean, it's like you could think that so it's like you can be sharing the messages
It's like electrical, but then they're receiving the message is both electrical and magnetic because I'm the magnet and then you know
So it's like different like different kinds of power going through but I've never even get the message. I'm supposed to
There's a song by earth wind and fire called magnetic that you should listen to it would like speak to you because
Yeah, I didn't know about earth wind and fire until like I guess like my 30s, I guess
Um, it was after I left the adult industry that I had a fan who was actually helping to
Get my mind right strangely
And he recommended earth wind and fire to me and to me they sounded like a new group instead of like an older group
so
Yeah, they just they have that sound like it's like a kind of like it's a funky. Yeah, it's like electronica, but funk and pop
Yep, and
There is a very good idea
Do you think that your sexuality has a lot to play into your spirituality?
Well, if you like watch like you see like straight straight terror readers like straight male terror readers. They're very technical. They're very like
Okay, well, this is like this is like did you look at things in a very tech very technical way with exactly what the cards
Meaning is and like it's like they don't like no muster
They don't get the emotions a lot of the emotion sometimes and sometimes women miss like the technical like the very technical part
And they just get the emotion from the car. So it's like I think I have a mix of like both the masculine feminine
It's like well, you're pretty balanced. I didn't know if you were gay or straight until you said so just now
I I was thinking that you have the the feminine energy
But, you're not what I would consider super effeminate at all.
I feel like there's a lot of masculinity within you, but you're in touch with the reality
of femininity.
I don't think that you're into the caricature of femininity, you're into the reality of
I'm not into the drag queen, which is like all like the like the outside kind of like
Mind I think in a certain way like a very I think it's like but I think it's balanced
It's like the right brain left brain. It's like yeah, I'm like I'm a man and a woman
I think I'm born of a man and woman. I was raised by two straight people like they were pretty much in the long the gender lines
You know, you know, so it's very good examples. And so I my parents were always married and so I had the good kind of like
It's so I love street people, you know as raised by some so and all my family
I'd like you know, there's seven to seven brothers and sisters and so it's like, you know
So it's like you're from like a big family. Yeah, it's a blended family the Brady Bunch style
And and so if you don't mind me asking are you east coast or west coast? I mean, I mean a brain
Los Angeles, yeah, the South Bay, Los Angeles, the East Coast, the West Coast.
Well, I'm glad for you that you're West because I think that men who decide that they want
to be out of the closet officially, West side of the country, way more accepting than the
East side of the country.
I'm going to tell you something, I'm in a weird way.
My dad passing is a relief for me because I can openly talk about certain things, being
the offspring of someone who's openly LGBTQ.
And I was always proud of my dad coming out, but if he had been raised in a West Coast
His life would have been a lot more like
Comfortable for him when I really think about who he was as a man. I know he loved me very much. Am I sibling?
But I feel like he always knew that he was, I say bisexual, because obviously he had two children, you know?
But I think he would have been able to be himself more if he had been of a West Coast mentality,
mental state that exists. I agree. East Coast is way different. East Coast is way fucking different over there.
It's mean. I honestly think it's a mean spirit. It's like as much as I will be like, well, this is happening because I'm black.
This is happening because I'm black. Honestly, just forget about being black, but just being a woman
I have found professionally I've gained more ground as a businesswoman on the west side of the country
opposed to the east side of the country because of a level of misogyny, no matter what ethnicity you are.
Well said. She's right, psyche.
I agree
He's doing stuff on his computer. That's why he's all up in the camera
I have a surprise for you.
I'm happy to be on this panel today.
So, Joe, Joe, Joe, I'm happy to be a prayer of my baby, Alex, Alex, for life, for life,
Alex, you're such a sweet angel, sweetheart.
Joe, I feel like you're about to, like...
do something like, are you
and are you being healthy
been working out this in
I do this every year. Tra
started two days ago or w
five days ago. And when t
I'm not a football player
off and I start sweating
and I start popping those
shake that football. That
when it came to be like training time,
that's when you would get into the gym
and that's when you would do your thing.
I'm not that fucking old, I'm 41 years old.
Stop saying when you're younger.
But that's why I'm saying you gotta work out now
because you are getting up there.
Don't be in denial about it.
And I'm talking from experience.
I know I drink a lot of beers,
but I'll sweat every day, I'll sweat those beers out.
I ain't no bum.
Hey, mine.
And, you know, have fun because you got to have balance.
Like, like, I feel like that's the theme of the show.
If anybody come on YouTube, it's less than have fun.
Balance.
I'm not up here for drama.
I'm not up here for fights.
I'm up here for my boy, psych, and my girl, Alex, and that's what I'm talking about.
We're going to be talking about, like, awakening and the tarot, and...
Astrological science, we got to talk about the drama, but okay, I've got a question,
Tarot and like Insight and Astrology-wise, what do you think is going to happen between
now and the end of the year when it comes to the vegan Patriot saga?
or are you even following us?
That's a good question.
Well, I think being a patriot will continue to have Mr. Bigpipes as her managing mod,
and he will be his manager.
He's her managing mod?
Yeah.
Where are you?
Five years.
Is Mr. Bigpipes after you?
He's banned.
He's banned from the show.
because he uh well I actually had him back since he was banned. I'll just shut him down because
he doesn't mean he doesn't need to mess with you. Mr. Big Pikes if you're out there leave
psych tarot alone because he said he put a hex on me he said he said he put a hex on me. Oh so
he's doing magic now he was telling me he was a christian and he wasn't doing any magic.
So he's doing magic now, well, okay, Mr. Big Pikes, why are you lying?
So you're lying?
So Mr. Big Pikes is trying to be a wizard?
Is that what this is?
Yeah, I think so.
He said he was a powerful wizard in a few seconds.
I didn't know who I was dealing with.
That's what he said.
Well, you know, I knew that he was aligned with some dark energy for a while.
I am aware of this.
So Mr. Big Pikes, now I got the 4-1-1 if you're spying on Psych Tarot and you can go to help
because I'm not down with the casting of any magic. No, it's a bad idea. You should not delve
in the dark arts. You say, why you got a beast? He's like, I just want to kill. No, he's lying.
He was he was trying to hit on page and stuff. He was like trying to like, you know, like
Impressed page. He wants to be way more than chill. Mr. Big Pipes is
It's any pictures of his
He's about to have a hard time. I hope he's listening because
Tell you why mr. Big Pipes gonna have a hard time mr. Big Pipes is afraid of time. He's afraid of aging
And he has not been doing proactive things even spiritually to put like a halt to the, you know, I won't call it like evil, but the stalker is known as aging.
The stalker notice aging actually is seductive, but you got to watch out.
I'm constantly trying to evade the stalker notice aging.
That's gay.
When a guy dies in here, it's like over the gay line.
Well, Mr. Big Pies would be jealous of psych because psych is like, it doesn't even matter
that psych is LGBTQ.
men and women, like a lot of women would be drawn to psych because and plus like where
it's like the glasses and he's kind of like he's he's like he's like he's like a he's
like a kind uncle that will help you when you need help with like life's troubles.
and that's why he's jealous of sight. I already know what it is. Mr. Big Pipe's Leave Psych Alone!
Yeah
What I'm not jealous of him he had like
Because mr. Big Pies throws my name around like that was
I barely talked to him barely
And he acts like we're like bffs and it's like if you were really my bff you would talk to me more, but you don't so fuck you
pipes
Well, yeah
Yeah, I think once he's had vegan patriot. He like he like you like, you know, he's like, well, he's in love with vegan
I wish they would get together for real that would be interesting
Yeah, one time he said he's he peed on a jug and he has a jug in the corner of his room
He peed in it and then he like well vegan needs to like if I were vegan on like I don't hate vegan
I'm concerned for her, but I don't want to be her friend because she's not trustworthy, but as far as like
Concern I'm actually concerned for her. I hope that
She either stays with purple, or she finds somebody that is just totally into her, where
she can heal, and because she, I think she has like some medical problems that are not
being addressed.
And I do not want to see that girl die on stream.
I am serious when I say this.
She is living on the edge like some of you may not realize it, but she is really
You know yeah, you got your right Alex. She's living on the edge of death. Yeah
She's okay. I know I talk a lot, but you're a hundred percent right. She's keeps playing a fucking game
She'll be like I really want to help her like keep a trade my trust
Which is why I will not speak with her privately again
But I'll tell you something if something were to happen to her and someone had to pony up some money
I would do it because I am very concerned about her as a person
think that like I don't know what exactly is the reality that's was hard to
figure out about her like what is the real reality what's real what's reality
yeah but I don't want her like like there have been some guys that she took
advantage of okay but some guys she did not take advantage of
And like that one guy, like I know a lot of people gave me flack for going after that
Arizona guy who she was living with, but I don't care what anyone says.
I got a really bad feeling from him.
And I think that she did lie about some guys, but not that one.
That one, that fucking guy, I can't put my finger on it, but something's going on with
that.
Something's going on with it.
I think that he did force himself on her.
I don't care what anyone says.
I 100% believe it.
100%.
I believe it.
I think that he did.
And because he was coming at me through like email and DMs, trying to get me to take
my videos down just, I wasn't even accusing him.
But the way he was coming at me, I was like, uh, you, you're, you are a predator.
I think that he, because as strong as she is in some ways.
In other ways, a guy like that would be able to intimidate her, and I think that's what
happened.
And take advantage of her.
And take advantage of her weak, retarded mind.
And I think that he was in a position to where he figured, fuck it, I'm a guy, and I got
my little house in the suburbs of Arizona, and I have my job, and I can make my platform
eating pizza acting like I'm Mr. Man and talk bad about this girl to try to grow my own channel
even though I know that yeah, I think that he was thinking oh, she's in a vulnerable position
and I can you know make her look worse because she already has a bad reputation
What can I gain off of her?
was looking for a girlfriend. That's what I think he was looking for something else. Well,
but he wanted to be dominant over her. But because he because he knew because he was like a
military kind of dude, he he was in the army or
or he was somewhere in the military until he shows his like
slides, don't know he was in the army. That if he could have
said he's in the army, we don't know if it's like in the army.
Well, he was he because there's video footage but he was always
weird because there's this footage of him dancing around
like he's a backstreet boy or something trying to be like a
karaoke person. It was he's he wants attention. Yeah, but no
he's like an army military guy, he thought that if he could pull vegan who does like appeal
to like like like the military people who are kind of like renegades in a way he thought he could
Arizona is a weird state, especially in the Phoenix area.
It is like a lawless, confederate flag flying.
Confederate state.
Alternate reality of like the Confederacy,
how one, that is what Phoenix and Scottsdale is.
It's crazy.
Well, like they're not going to kill you if you're black, but you better be careful seriously like
I don't know if they're racist or not, but I just would not like you know, there's some beautiful properties out there if you want to buy a home
If you're a person of color, I would maybe think elsewhere honestly
And I please sing psychs my favorite Backstreet Boys song now, Alex. Are you done sweetheart? You are my fire
You bitch that greasy hair
Enough yes enough. Yeah, um, but yeah, Alex. Thank you for being on the show originates. I like some
Yeah, it's me. I'm Alex. No, no, no, no. I mean Joe. Joe. I mean Joe. I was trying to talk
I mean I was thinking about Alex. I was looking at this video, which is Alex McQueen
I don't know. Do you know Alex McQueen? Well, I keep hearing about this person, but I I've never I might do they have like a duck?
Avatar or no, that's that's yeah, he's like he has a good I'm like a SWAT team guy. He's like him
He's like I don't know
Honest, I'm gonna say I don't know who it is
But I've seen the person before and I like I know that people have been like did you do this and I'm like no
It wasn't me
And so I guess there's like another Alex.
Yeah, cause people would talk about you
and I think they're talking about Alex.
And I was like, oh my God.
Well, I'll be, I'll be Alexandra or Alexandra.
I say Alexandra, but apparently I'm supposed to be Alexandra.
So whatever, but I'll be Alexandra instead of Alex.
That way people know it's not me.
If it's Alex, whoever Alex is.
I don't even feel like an Alex.
I feel like an Alexandra.
feel like an alex. Alexander's pretty pretty feminine but uh oh it's a great name. I had a
cat named Halleck. Yeah you have cats like how many cats do you have? Five cats. Oh here's like
little tricks hold on. Okay we're gonna see some cats. Hey hi oh you're pretty look at you
What's this cat's name name is tricks here. I asked hey Trix
What are you ready to go tricks is like tricks are for kids?
Trix are for kids
I'm gonna walk around
I'm kitty cat
Hello
This cat looks like a side of me is in it the way that like his body is
He's kind of aww. He's sleepy
Are you a little sleepy?
Have you been hunting have you been hunting any mice?
He's a little like he this guy likes to cuddle with me
Like he's like always I would always wake up with him and stuff like that, but I have a black cat. He's a cuddle cat
Yeah, he's a very cuddly cat
The momma cat, I have like an orange cat, you know, older cat in Rudy.
You're a cat man.
Yeah, I'm Mr. Cat Man and a cat father, you know.
That's good. When I was younger, I had pets. Like, because I've been, I basically,
I chose like a nomadic lifestyle, but I had birds when I started. I love birds. I like birds,
but I hate reptiles. Like they keep trying to say that
birds
Dinosaurs, but I don't totally believe that look at the feet if you look at the feet they have like reptile feet the birds do
They have reptilian feet so like if you look at I had a love bird named peaches and peaches was bonded to me
Because I did not know that love birds were supposed to be in couples when you adopt them
Yeah, yeah, my mom raised lovebirds actually she raised lovebirds. I also had a conure named Lucy
She's a red-headed conure. I'm sure I had an albino peach face lovebird
Peaches was evil. Okay, not not to me, but any boyfriend I had peaches hate it. It was definitely a male bird
Peaches would bite, like peaches, I could have all the windows open and the door open
and peaches would not try to escape or go anywhere or anything.
I had peaches until peaches died of old age.
Then when I started my journey of self-discovery in 2020,
I had two birds, two parakeets,
but I re-homed them when I was in North Carolina,
because I couldn't stay on the road with birds.
It was a bit ridiculous,
but I found a little boy who always wanted birds.
So he got birds.
That's cool.
Yeah.
So you're gonna be like a famous tarot reader.
Well, I well, I've actually like had some success doing tarot on Etsy like during the you know, the 2020
I'll promote you. I'll talk to you. Thank you so much. Thank you so much. No, I think we're accurate
I mean, and you're not invasive because I feel like there's more you could have said about me that you didn't
But now I'm gonna push you. I'm gonna push you and challenge you. Okay?
That was good and I'm going to engage the comfort level because sometimes I'm not comfortable with things
But then I do become accustomed to and become acclimated to things sooner than you would think okay
okay
when it comes to me as a
46 year old woman
Do you think that?
I'm doing okay in my life just from what you can observe or
Do you think I should shift and if so, what would those shifts be?
Well, I think you're like very strong in your identity and like you've come to you're like really going to your higher self because you've been
You were in your lower self, you know, you knew like we're comfortable. It was comfortable there. And but it's like you push yourself
It was like
It's not easy to get out of your lower self too, because the lower self is just very comfortable to be in.
You're always striving higher, just like the goat always wanting to climb more and higher in the mountain.
And whatever it was, it was just a stepping stone.
Even if it was like something people might consider negative, it's a positive stepping stone that you're in the direction you want to go to,
and not everybody's going to understand your logic and stuff, because...
People were like, why can goats climb all these really steep sides of mountains and everything?
Why are they climbing to the top? It's because they want there's some salt on the top,
and they're going crazy for the salt. So we see what we want when we go for the term and go after
it. And so that's usually some kind of success, right? You are so on point. And then on top of that,
those of you watching, because I'm not looking at the chat, but I just want to interject.
This man is speaking very rapidly and very quickly, so his brain is actually working, I would say, 10 times at this rate to articulate the way that he is.
He's the real deal.
I'm just saying because you're very on point with what you're saying, but you're also going very in depth
And I'm a slow talker because I'm a slow thinker. I'm slow, but you're fast and I appreciate that
So I just wanted to say that sorry go ahead. I'm a problem. Yeah, I just I'm gonna try thank you
I really appreciate that like I am
That's
I'm very skinny you can tell like I'm very like I have definitely a fast metabolism and I always
have well maybe you're operating at a faster rate of time than the rest of us that's why I say I
don't think that time is a real thing because a lot like and I've noticed that a lot of times people
who are kind of like like maybe you're kind of elvish or something you know like like the little
tinkerbell elves in a way and they're all they always have the cute little you know who's like
Well, she wants to be my enemy, but she's not my enemy.
I just wish that she would lay off a little bit.
Trisha Licious, she's a little like that.
She's, she thinks very fast and she's a little person.
She's tiny.
She's like a little, uh, a little nymph.
And the nymphs usually are a little psychic, aren't they?
Yes, I think, well, I think there is.
I think we're definitely like.
Are you in a forest?
Am I in a fourth?
I mean, definitely, and he said,
I mean, you know, well, okay.
So Capricorns are associated with Pan, right?
You know, about Pan?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, he's Pan is considered the all.
He was considered like all the God,
like he's like the great God Pan.
It's like the number, like the earth basically.
Well, Pan was a super great.
I mean, he was okay.
well pan pan was like you know he would kind of uh he he represents personified love really you
know personified love right it's like very lustful he would chase around the nymphs but like he would
never catch them really and uh and he would just run after them they were always so they were always
like you know it was to escape him but um yeah he did chase like some people like searing so he
You know, there's different things like legends of plants and how they were once like the some woman that was being chased by God that got turned into a tree or a plant to escape the God having sex with her or something like that.
Well I think that there's a reality to all of that in some weird twisted way.
I just think so because like if you look at Greek mythology there's so many lessons that you can learn
from just
Right, you know what they were talking about. It was weird. It was a philosophy
It's also like, you know, it's the same story that about the creation of man is basically in
Genesis as it is in the Greek mythology except in Greek mythology is Prometheus and Athena that like molded the men from clay and stuff like that
and brought them life.
And basically instead of Eve, it's Pandora,
they both were tempted by this forbidden fruit
or like the box in Pandora's case
or the jar more of a jar.
But-
Well, you know, what I've kind of realized
about all these different, you know, legends or theology
or whatever you want to call it, maybe fact even,
there's always a scapegoat.
And that's when I become skeptical.
Because-
Okay, in Christianity, who's the biggest scapegoat? Eve. Or the devil, yeah, both of them. Even the devil. Yeah, well it's interchangeable, it depends. Yeah, yeah.
Well, yeah, Lilith is really kind of like you know, a little bit devilish
Well, it's kind of kind of goes Adam and Eve then I correspond with like the lower self is like semi on Lilith
And so it's like that's like kind of their their
Their genitals I think is like the lower self right and so it's like in the genitals that came together the tops didn't really have together
The brain the minds in it necessarily me, but it's so then uh, you know, they're my cane and able right cannibal
and then like you know the first more I mean the cane and able thing I mean a lot of people
they may not like my mom as she told me about this moment but my mom was um in college she was
like one of the first african-american people to integrate um the school that she was going to
was called uh what was it lindenwood university was like a school for girls wow but um there were
a lot of Mormon people at that school and part of their theology is that
The mark of Cain is black people.
somehow because yeah and my mom was like she was aware of it and she rebelled
by not going to some sort of a like assembly that they had that was you
know important for her degree that she was trying to get but because it was
Mormon she was like you know fuck this shit I'm not gonna let these people like
tell me on the mark of Cain because I'm black so
Yeah, they're kind of racist, like that's kind of what, like well known, you know, was like a little bit of a, they're like that, like they explained dark skin was like the character pain and that was like, that was like basically, you know, like the, you know, the
Yeah, well, I mean, I think it's, I think it took their, you know, way of religion, because I mean, there's a lot of things about Mormonism that I think are good, really.
I mean, it's like I think that of a Mormon carpool, you know, it's like I think that of a Mormon carpool as a kid
It's like they're very really. Yeah, but it's like it is an interesting religion. Um, it's also like
You know, it takes it's basically in Utah. It's like it took over Utah, right? But that's like
Now, there's not a lot of gays that can have it, too.
Yeah, it's supposed to be.
There's a lot of LGBTs, for some reason,
and something karma or something.
But there's a lot of LGBTs that were born Mormon.
And then it's kind of like, I think it kicked out.
Yeah, a lot of them.
Well, you know what's crazy?
It's funny that you say that because a lot of Mormon girls
end up in the adult industry.
I saw it when I stopped performing
and I was working for an agency.
so I would do the paperwork sometimes and they were so many were from Utah it was crazy um
I guess that's like rebellion it's a rebellion it's just like just like a lot of the Amish people
they get a chance to like live as like a non-Amish for a little bit they all get on like
so it's drug legally and then they're fucking like to get them sorry I mean a lot of sex and
they can decide whether it'd be Amish or not like a lot of them choose to go to go into like the
I remember the Mormon kids coming and knocking on doors when I got my first
apartment when I was living in South Florida. I always felt bad for them
because like
It was so hot outside and like, I always wonder like who dropped them off because they wouldn't give them water.
I felt like it was like slavery in a weird way. It was weird.
But like they would have to wear their, you know, like their little tie and their little, you know, bun down shirt.
If it was a girl like a similar outfit, but like with a skirt or something.
But it just like it was dangerous when I think about it because I
Don't know what do you think that they make those kids do that? It's like a
Test of faith or it's very ceremonial. It's like, you know, it's just like with like, you know
You know with mason's like mason's will have like the junior organizations to it to like, you know
To acclimate a younger generation to like, you know to prepare for like the the other thing, right? So it's like
It's very similar to that. It's like because it actually is stemmed from that. He was like a he was amazing
Well, I mean when I think about it like I was living I remember I was living in Hollywood, Florida. Okay
And I was near federal highway us one, which is more so
The beach area. Okay
And it's a pretty
It's a pretty integrated area
you see
I would say that the whites are mainly Canadian transplants who live there, but you do have
some white people who just probably have always lived in Florida.
You have a huge Latin population, especially I guess you would call it more so Portuguese
Not a lot of blacks, but then again, people don't want to acknowledge this, but the black population within the United States has started to severely diminish.
I'm not going to say it's a good or bad thing. It doesn't matter to me, but it's mainly because there's so many people that define themselves as multiracial now that you don't really have many.
People who are like, I'm African-American and that's it. There's not many of us
So where I where I lived it was pretty
some of everybody
but we would always know the Mormons when they would drop them off and
It wasn't it didn't seem right whoever was dropping them off what they were doing
Because you could tell that they these whoever these kids were
Even probably from Florida and you have them preaching what they're preaching and they could and sometimes they did the guys
Would get in trouble sometimes
Not the girls, but it got to where the women who lived in that neighborhood
When we saw them get dropped off
We would kind of look out
Because we didn't want to see the girls get traumatized or something happened to them or anything weird
but it's like
Have whatever religion you want, but don't send your kids into
like a potentially
That's the point of it. I mean, it's like the
Parents put the kids into the religion early because that guarantees like the kids will be the same religion as the parents
And so it's a brainwashing process, but also yeah, they also they'll put them in danger situations as well
Yeah
Well, I felt like they were trying to get some of these kids in trouble to where they could be like well
You see these are heathens. These are horrible people. You shouldn't that that's kind of the vibe that I got
from whatever they were doing.
It got to where even the law enforcement in the area
that they were doing something
to where they wouldn't even allow them to be out
like after sundown.
Because it was something weird going on.
But I don't know.
I mean, do you think that the internet
is bringing everybody closer together
or do you think it's creating more development?
It's creating a lot of problems, but it's okay like
It's like we're supposed to I mean it's supposed to happen like that, but it's like it's I mean
it's bringing everyone together, but it's like in a really
Really false kind of way like where it's like people can present themselves with anything they want
it's not to go first
and
You know also like it's kind of like
It brings a lot of people into the internet world rather than the real world, so it kind
of pulls you out of this real world.
Well, okay, here's a sensitive question for you, and you don't have to answer if you don't
want to, okay?
Do you think that as of this particular moment in time, do you think that-
Your spirit is gravitating more toward your online world or your offline world
It's kind of like lawnmower man
It's like we get we get the online world makes us smarter and smarter and it's like it gets more and more
But and we're gonna pull more and more in as we get to virtual reality
That will pretty much pull us in it will be like all of a sudden we'll have the power as we didn't have here in that world
And it'll be just as realistic and so we're gonna prefer that world because we have so much that there but it is like you know
illusion right it's just like illusion it's just programming in it but yeah I
think that we're like you know we will be spending less and less time in this
world but it will also be like a kind of scarier world I think in a certain way
like where it's gonna be like so dangerous it'll be so we're gonna like
look at things very rationally like oh look how dangerous the world is like all
the people have died so it's gonna be like much more safe to like have
everything within like a few minutes and everything safe and everything like all
the transportation taking care of and all the medical stuff taking care of
Eventually eventually, you know, it's like we're gonna try well you kind of evade it my questions. It's a little bit. Okay
I'm sorry. Let's not my main question was you personally you feel that you're more
Drawn toward your online world or your offline world
I'm drawn more to the offline world, but
The online world I'm still in the offline where it's like it's kind of like I'm doing both
You know kind of I mean kind of one foot in it. I've never been fully in the online world
You know, it's like but uh, yeah, you spend probably more time on my waking day online
But I still consider myself in the regular world. I don't know. It's like I prefer I think the we I like to live in my imagination
Kind of more my imagination, but I like to be also the Capricorn. So it's like the world just comes naturally to me
It's like always been like, you know able to like manifest in this world. I mean, I'm sure you understand the same thing
It's like we're able to oh totally. I mean to me. That was a hard question
I I wouldn't have been able to answer the question that I just asked you
It's hard
yeah because it's like how much how much about i'm out in virtual reality i feel that is kind of
like more in the virtual world i consider this is well it's so intermingled it really is at the
stage it's so intermingled and a lot like
My parents criticized me for many years when I was younger about being as
Into technology and the internet and whatnot as I've always been I went to school for computer science before I went to the adult industry
but
Both even my dad before you pass
Acknowledge he was like, you know, I was wrong about what I thought because they were wrong
What I was into is the future
So, it's like, you know, some people might criticize you for being overly, what would
the word be, overly involved or overly fanciful or overly into what they say is not real.
But look, if you're doing your banking through the internet and that's your money, then your
Yeah, that's my feeling about that. Yeah, well, that's mean that that is fiat currency
That's like kind of ruled by Gemini, which is like pulling things out of thin air
You know, it's like yeah, like another like thing that is like not really real because the money is not really good
I mean we I have a lot of challenges with Gemini's
Okay
Yeah, yeah, my father was a Gemini and so oh really
They're the good-to-eat evil twin, but they're they're very brilliant people great communicators great business people and then
the great just like a
They love life and they always want to get their way and stuff like that.
But instead of the Pisces, it's kind of like the two fish, but they're swimming in opposite directions like the duality.
The Gemini is selfish. They're very selfish people.
It's like the twins egging each other on.
They are two people. They are not one person at all, ever.
Very interesting like I find astrology very interesting. It seems like but yeah, Trump is what Trump is one and
you know, like a lot of
Business people a great business. Well, how do you feel about astrology and how astrology intermingles with Christianity?
with Christianity? Well, yeah, they have like, you know, they have all the same things like
they in the Bible, they will mention like, each astrological sign, like, I think in
revelations, they'll make reference to all these, like someone holding the scales, there's
someone holding, there's, I think there's going to be sheep, like the Aries, there's
going to be, you know, I don't know if there's two twins anywhere, but you know, there's
There's almost all this stuff and almost everything to do with astrology is in the Bible too.
Yeah, I mean, what I think is interesting is that they say that the Watchers or the Fallen or it wasn't the Nephilim because that was the offspring, but the angels who led to taught humans.
Look, I think that there's a lot to astrology. I think that it's like basically in a weird way like a guidebook.
I don't think it's an end to all, but I think it's a guidebook.
There was an angel in the book of Enoch that, I forgot, I think Bart Zabella or something.
I think he talked to people about astrology, also a lot of medicine things.
Yeah.
And metalworking, root work, different kinds of magic, witchcraft, probably, and then knowledge
you know, the metalworking so they could create weapons and like all that.
And something with the clouds, I've always liked it.
Nephilim, that means Nephilim means the cloud.
Nephilim means like, Nefell is like Greek.
It's like Nefell was like this woman that turns into a cloud to run from Zeus.
But her name was or they or they made like a woman for Zeus
and they made her name was Nefell because she was just actually like a fake.
I think one of his women or something said to oh that's interesting. Yeah, so
it's a nephilim is from nephel or also I've heard these different things like but uh
yeah there's just something about the book of enox that goes over all the names of their
of these demons one's name is samyaza and they teach all they teach man or they sleep with the
women actually then they they uh they taught the women in exchange for the sex they teach them like
Yeah
Then all the children are the offspring of the giants and the women. Okay, so it's a that's what we involved from
We were probably some kind of like animal like we're probably like in the maybe a different set of theater evolution, right?
where we're and then they
Mix with the, you know, the, the ape.
I think a lot of us have a lot of things in us.
That's what I definitely think.
Every animal.
Yeah.
I think we're everything.
We're the Lord of the animals, right?
So it's like every animal is within us.
They have every animal is like some kind of like trait.
I don't know about every animal,
but I think that like pretty much everything that ever,
you know.
was since Adam and Eve, there's a lot of us
with a lot of things.
And I think that's why you have like certain anomalies
in people, you know, you have people
with all kinds of special abilities
that are born from time to time.
I think it's like, you know,
some sort of throwback DNA that's activated.
You've seen that Prometheus?
That's kind of reminded me of it.
Yeah, I saw that.
genetic experiments with like by the Anunnaki and things like that they would you know mix
They were trying to create a race of slaves basically to dig the gold because they didn't
want to do it. They were like, well, they're kind of like the elite of their galaxy, right?
So like, we don't want to do work. And so they created these, they took the most intelligent
animal they could find on the earth, and then they mixed it with their DNA, and it started to
create. I think, I mean, that seems to be the dominant narrative about what like the ancient,
Ancient astronaut theory is they're always trying to say that all of humanity initially was a slave race, right?
and that right but i mean i think about it like that like what what what it's like weird to me
and maybe it's only because i'm african-american but like i hear these ancient astronaut theorists
like on history channel right and they're like oh and our forefathers they're gonna come back here
and invite us to be with them no they would not okay here's the reality
If you have this group that is supposedly our predecessors that, you know, somehow injected their DNA in what's supposed to be the rudimentary form of whatever was on this planet, right?
They're not going to look at us like they're equal. Maybe they would, but I don't think that they would.
I just personally
Until we caught up with until we caught up with them intellectually, maybe and when we do that
Maybe we'll finally meet them or something like I don't think we're caught up
If they're contacting us
And we're not already at light speed
But like as far as like being in a starship and you know going to other
Planets and doing all that kind of stuff then we would be below
Well, do you know about Star Trek and when the Vulcans in that fictional world made contact with the humans?
Like, whoever gets in contact with us would most likely be on the level that the Vulcans
were opposed to the humans in Star Trek, if there was some group that contacted us.
But they would be like, they could kill us instantly if they were not good people of,
you know, certain ethics.
Do you think that's already happened, maybe?
Like like what? Extinctions or like the killing of the aliens contacting us who are like the Vulcans. Oh, yeah
I think that they're like a lot of them are like
actually
What is it like they're the clairvoyance?
they're like they're able to like do telekinesis and things like that and and
So telepathy and I've been communicating with certain people certain people have talked to people that have given them diagrams with ships and all kinds of
Things that they are working. Have you seen have you seen any aliens?
Have I seen any I think that we're mixed with the aliens. I think where we are aliens and like we don't realize that we are
Have you see how like have it has anyone tried to abduct you?
When you have an alien in your apartment
He's right there, and he's got your cat. Maybe you're the alien. Are you the alien?
Maybe the cats are the aliens.
The cats are the aliens. They are little aliens, yes. Without a doubt, the cats are the aliens.
I will never encounter you on that. They are.
I think the world is like a zoo for like the whole universe. Like the world is like all this life from everywhere is here.
It's like it's like all kinds of stuff from everywhere.
kinds of different planets or maybe there's planets just a black people plan just the white people
I mean who knows I don't know I think that there is you know there's this like I
Before coast to coast AM before guy MTV when I was really young I discovered AM radio and I was
listening to the art bell show I'm like a when he passed away I was like oh my god what the hell but
I think
that anything that we think could be is,
but people do use like the ET alien thing
to push very segregationist agendas,
but if the aliens ever were to be like totally like out
with us like, hey, here we are,
nobody would be racist anymore,
because
there would be aliens and you would be like
That's a Reagan said that right he said like oh, yeah an outside threat
They're good like aliens and we'd all come together. Well, yeah, that's why they have to try to manufacture it
But then they can just always say it some group in America like they have like that's what they always
Is it like aliens were kind of like so so too smart till I really believe that there's gonna be aliens worried about that
so it's like they're trying to like they'll probably just go after another group again because
Don't find some group acting like these aliens are totally real at this point
Like if you look at some of these videos that people are putting out. Yeah, I mean, I think I
Mean
It doesn't really matter to me if they're real
Completely real or not, but do you think that people are gonna really freak out if they if they're like
Hey
I think it's gonna be a it's like fake. It's gonna be fake
It's gonna be get some people in masks or like some kind of like no CGI or something like that and like
Just look at the movie. They're gonna have some movie director
Just put some CGI thing have it on the news and it will be like another like you know, please
Because people believe whatever they watched how many people really question any news story that there is right?
Like nobody really questions the news story. I don't really think that the aliens would want to come here
Not really
No, I feel like maybe if they wanted to see like nature stuff, they will like see that
They probably like just wanted to get all the golds like they took the gold and then they left
You know, that's all they wanted to do. They wanted well, they already took the gold
I mean, haven't they already done that? Yeah, they did that
There's all these african these big gold mines in Africa these ancient gold mines that where they would actually that's where they got
There's other planets that are supposed to be like all about like, you know different minerals and stuff
They're probably everywhere
Yeah, I mean there could be like billions of earths, and I don't know if that's the multiverse
I think that they're probably honestly I
Okay, okay, this is gonna sound crazy to you, but here's my theory. Okay. I've been thinking about this for years
I'm probably gonna make a whole YouTube video based on this. Okay, but here's what I don't understand
Think about the way that they've always told us about our solar system. Okay?
Meaning, the sun is in the middle, then you have Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, and then
the gas giants, then you got like Neptune, Uranus, sometimes Pluto, they want that to
be a planet, sometimes it's not, whatever.
But all these orbits of these planets are plainular, meaning they're like a record,
How come an atom has a nucleus and then the electrons and the protons
orbiting in like a north south east west north east south east sort of orbit
But our planets and our solar system don't do that to me. That doesn't make any sense
I want to know what about the planets that are above and below us because I think that there's probably quite a few.
Okay, but now I don't hear you.
I can kind of hear you. Maybe it's my volume. Let's see.
No, it's your volume
All right, talk now
Can you hear me? Yeah, now I hear you great
Okay, good. Yeah, I had trying to switch my phone out, but it's like it's not working. So
No, you got it. So, yeah, okay perfect
Yeah, I don't know if you've you so you never met the other Alex, but I have like it's every treat for the for the chat
Because I made a music video
You know you've heard I've been making these AI tracks and I'm looking at AI
No, I like doing the AI music and music videos too. It's fine. Yeah. Yeah, I made it like IPT music
But yeah, it's fine
Yeah, and so I just think I just made a a video
I made a video, but I don't know if it's
Three three-and-a-half minutes and how long is this one? Oh, yeah
You're ready to see it. Okay. I'm gonna premiere it for everybody. Okay, so this is um, so that but it so there's um pages in my chat
She's a terror reader as well, and she's actually great. And so then I know this guy named Alex
He's like a cop everyone says he's a fake New York cop, but he might be a real one
Who knows and so he like had a dream about her. He's in love with her whatever he's like
I'll make a song about how I'm in love with page. Okay, so
Then I know I have a video guys do it. So here's a premiere of the video. I hope you enjoy it. Thank you
Alex walks the beat in the city light flashing blues under New York night
you the one I've been missing in my sleep
She's gutting trout. He's eating steak somewhere in the middle. They both take a break
He'd trade his nightsticks for a fishing pole chase her laughter like it's his patrol page
Don't you know you're the catch of the day and this cop's got one hell of a line to say
It was like the guy character merged with the girl character
and they became one character.
Cause sometimes it was like...
I don't know that Peter Pan was in the woods,
like what stalking, I don't know who that was.
Yeah, sometimes it's like,
it was the guy's face with the girl's hair
and I was like, what is that?
That's their spirit child,
that they had this spirit child.
Yeah, that was their androgynous offspring
and that was different.
But I mean, it's amazing what AI can create.
I mean, the guy was hot, the girl was pretty.
It looks like Paige, I mean it does look like Paige, I don't know how they got it, I don't know,
and no one knows what Alex looks like, I think it's fine.
I've never, yeah, I don't know what Paige looks like, I don't know, I mean if that's what they
look like, they're hot, they're a hot couple, they need to get together.
Oh yeah, they are a hot couple.
They need to get together, quickly.
But yeah, that was that was I thought I like the fall colors like I'm a sucker for like the whole New England fall
Like you know colors of autumn. It's beautiful. I was like, oh, that's nice
But I'm happy to be the summertime I am happy
And let's see, so we're looking for,
how's the chat doing?
Oh, we have everybody in the chat.
Yeah, what's happening?
27 people in the chat.
And now we get some people, you know, maybe.
Kick me whenever you want.
I mean, I'm here to bother psych.
Oh, no, no, no.
Everyone's welcome, it's an open panel.
So anyone want to come up?
Talking about, he's playing music videos.
He's talking about spirituality.
What else can we talk about?
Well, that video I just did,
Over $20 to make because I thought it was like
Runway because I know runway it's called
neural
Neural something neural. It was a cool video. I mean, I like this like people just the AI music
I don't I think the AI music is just as good as regular music sometimes
Neural frames and it was done by a chat GPT neural frames and one called AI music generator and then uh, was the AI generated lyrics?
Yes. Well, actually, I mean, I generated them based on what I said. So I came up with Paige. We follow your lyrics. Okay. So, yeah
But there's or the information
Look if you contributed to it and you're the only human then it's your song
There you go. Yeah, people were saying, oh, this is not talented. I'm like, and I know certain people that are like
I love doing the AI music. I've been doing the AI tracks sometimes diss tracks sometimes fun flattering tracks
But the AI music is I mean
It can make your dream come true. Like if you always wanted to be a pop star and you wanted to do like a pop song
You can make an AI song and put your own vocals over it and
You know, you know, I talk and then you have an audience and all of a sudden you're like you can be famous on yeah
You can be a pop star
Yeah, even if it's like if it's like just like because there are people that you know
We take eight or how many people six billion people in the world. There's like gonna be
Probably like literally a hundred million or more that are going to be interested in almost exactly what you do
I think they'd be fascinated by it
They just can't find you right and so it's like if you put yourself on the internet and make a better chance of being found
Around the world by people that are looking for you. Okay, very true
Very true like like sometimes you don't even realize it, but you might have a look
That's popular like in some country that you never even thought about
and you could blow up white people are like kind of like in japan like white people are like
kind of like they'd be kind of like well you're fetishized in a weird way and like uh like it's
good but it's it can be good but it can be bad
Yeah, like when they put it to make the japanimation like the characters are kind of like Americanized
I've always thought that the japanimation care like sailor moon
It looks like skinny skinny little white girls like in middle school
It is you know, I think they kind of idealize that look even though they but they are all like, you know
All the same color eyes and same color hair basically the homogenize culture very homogenous
Yeah, it's like anything. That's like different to them. They love because they all look
Very similar
Have you seen this one here's another I make this video somebody else made this video, but sort of diamond just recommend this one
There's already diamonds out to get me. I hope not
Yeah, it's gonna get me. This is also Alex. Hold on one second
Alex
We need what are you gonna do to me if I you pull me over and
I've been speeding on the freeway. What are you gonna do to me? I'm gonna say sir
Last registration. I'm gonna pretend it's bad
I'm gonna say step out of the car and I'm gonna throw you in the bushes
In the bushes. I'm gonna fuck the shit out of you in the bushes
Okay, my god, I'm gonna end up in the trees on the side of the highway
I'm gonna fucking just give it to you. And then that's it my man
I'm gonna make popcorn and just fall my way I
Don't really understand the point of that video, but that's how else and I have a house and I have a very um
It's kind of a relationship.
It's like, we're like, we always hit on each other,
but it's a very straight New York cop though.
Maybe it's not.
Maybe like his fantasy is being that energy,
but being seduced by you.
Are you seducing men on the internet?
Yes.
Well, I'm like a black widow though. I'm very dangerous.
It's okay. You know, just be careful.
My bark is worse than my bite.
Well, bow, wow, wow, yippee-yay, yippee-yay.
Wow, wow, wow, wow. I know this summer's going to be so much better.
well yeah well we'll see okay so what's the next move going to be for psych going
in next move is this like I'm already doing my next move my next I'm just like
doing what I'm doing it now I'm doing the show I'm gonna do the show as a lot as
long as I can as long as I'm able to I'm just gonna be here are you gonna go like
on you know it if you decide to do like
Going out and about streams like IRL or something you should go to like spiritual
locations like Sedona of Bore, Texas and
See if like you can
Find any more taxes. I've been just I've been to Sedona. So but Sedona is absolutely gorgeous
it's like yeah, they have these some the red rocks and the spirituality and like the
The energy there is just amazing. I feel like that's a beautiful I agree. Well, well the desert the desert has like like the desert calls you sometimes and
In the desert, you can relinquish a lot of energy, but you can also absorb a lot of good energy if you allow yourself to be open the sun if you need to do is find a little like, you know, shelter but all there is to eat there is reptiles though, pretty much right
Um, well, you know, like I believe in Walmart as far as like ordering your groceries and
picking them up because that's what I've been doing like where I am right now.
I'm in the desert, but there is a Walmart in driving distance.
So you know, you order your groceries, you pick them up and then you don't have to eat
Uh-huh. Yeah, well, yeah, I mean, it's like, well, I mean, frogleys aren't bad, right? But yeah, usually it's not.
Some people like frog leg, like if you're Cajun, you know, like in Louisiana, it's like a delicacy, like, um, an alligator or a crocodile or something, like, in Louisiana, people will eat, um...
Reptiles it's not really for me, but like if I had nothing else to eat and like it was like
The end of the world and the person saving me was like you need some protein and all that there was was
Frog legs I would eat
Well, there's just cockroaches left, and they can make, oh, they can make roaches and everything.
Well, I, like, like, I was thinking, like, you know, it's the end of the world, and somehow
I get saved, and, like, I'm injured, I'm bleeding, you know, I've been through hell
and all that kind of crap, and all, all that there is to eat is, like, reptile.
That's what I would eat because you know, you got to keep going. Oh, yeah
We have a survival instinct and that's better. That's all the reptilian instinct
It's the fight or flight to get away from dangerous situations or to strike or to and it's about survival
It's about hunger, but it's like the lowest form of it. Yeah, I wouldn't like like it's not my food of choice
But if I had like like if it was like life or death, I wouldn't be like, oh, no
I don't want to eat that.
Sure, you get hungry enough and it looks fine.
Make some nice snake soup or something.
Yeah.
Sometimes you got to eat what you don't want to eat.
Dinosaur. Do you think they used to eat the dinosaurs?
Or no.
I think that those dinosaurs,
look, honestly, I had a conversation
with somebody about this recently and they thought
I was insane, but I don't care.
I think that
there was a point in time
where humans
interact it with something along the lines of those damn velociraptors.
Those dinosaurs are what scare me the most out of all the dinosaurs because they're people's
size. So like if you run and try to hide, they can follow you.
You know like if it's like a Tyrannosaurus Rex or an Allosaurus like they're really big
So like you could hide and they would have a hard time finding you but a rafter
That's like a person-sized creature
So wherever you go, it can go also
That's way scarier to me and I think that they have created those creatures
maybe it's just amazing special effects but I was watching that last I don't know
if it was the last Jurassic Park but the one where they're like in Africa and the
raptors are chasing the people and they're like running through like this
plaza that was so realistic it was crazy but I'm a sucker for the special effects
I love sci-fi
Yeah, especially if I'm sorry, I don't mean to say yes, special effects. You love special effects
It's like very easy to fool people with special effects, especially with yeah, that's why they were able to like, you know show
you know when the TV came out during the wars there it's a very powerful time for TV to come out
because that's like the public very true i mean i i just really hope that they never make this
dinosaurs like for real oh i don't think they will i mean why would we want those back i mean come on
there are someone with enough money he's a jerk they would be like ha ha let me make some raptors
and relink and release them and i don't know like where would they release them somewhere
Just probably some probably some like Epstein Island or something. You know, it's a return to the state Jurassic Park
too or oh
Probably not but you know what there's probably someone super evil with a lot of money
They would release them in like a college town
Where people are streaming and young people and they would make like their own personal
horror
reality
Movie
That's what they would do
That sounds good
Don't say it
Survive what if they do like a reality movie where they actually
Well, I mean it would it would be the ultimate IRL
Well, it would be IRL to get killed. I mean, yeah, it's to die. You're not allowed to it's against TOS to die on your stream
Or even like I don't want to show a gun. I mean, so it wouldn't be that if it was if it was real life
genetically created
dinosaurs
That were suddenly live streamed on
YouTube by a bunch of college
unsuspecting
college kids
In like, um, where would it happen? You know, it would happen like Gainesville, Florida
Okay, because it would be like the swamp. Okay, so like got all these like FSU students
They're having a good time
Everything's cool. It's maybe a bonfire party and all of a sudden there's a rustle in the trees or the bushes
And they're like, what's that?
And then all of a sudden Raptor's YouTube would let it go at least 15 minutes before they cut the feed
Mm-hmm. Oh, I mean they would cut the feed, but it's like yeah
They won't let it go at least 15 minutes because it would be something that's
It would be something that's never been seen before and, you know, it is still humans who
right now the AI shows like the same kind of thing that can show like, you know, dinosaurs.
But the AI wouldn't think that the dinosaurs are real because that's it doesn't compute.
If it meant unless it's like so realistic and it recognizes like that. Oh, there's the dinosaurs
It would think that is Jurassic Park
Yeah, it would but it might be because it probably is not ever gonna happen like they're not gonna like make they start breeding dinosaurs
I don't think they can have enough good DNA of the dinosaurs, but maybe they'll get it
You know, of course they do all the god do is like what they saw in Jurassic Park
They just need like the dinosaur bone marrow and yeah, but you think mosquitoes could like
penetrate the dinosaur skin. I don't think the mosquitoes were right.
Yeah, they were big mosquitoes. They were like Jurassic mosquitoes.
Oh my god. This sounds like it sounds really farfetched to me, but maybe I think they just
had a bunch of bones of different animals put together and said they were Jurassic mosquitoes
and their needle could pierce metal because they were Jurassic.
thought that there was a drastic miscarriage with like, with like, they just got to get the amber,
the amber's were the DNA. Yeah, but I know that makes sense. I mean, but if there were like,
but there's not, there weren't drastic miscarriages. Of course, all the mosquitoes,
the mosquitoes are always around. They're just tinier now. Well, maybe they were tinier then
In a movie there were, but I haven't seen any real mosquitoes from that. No, if you go to like the natural history museum
They tell you the
That's a thing they tell you a lot of things like that's a museum city that they're there to program the population of some what's real
It's not a you know thing. It's real
Lot of I think I don't think a lot of things in this world are real, right?
Well, do you think the dinosaurs were real?
Maybe they weren't real.
Now, now they're trying to say that.
I don't think they were.
I think it was a bunch of bones of different animals they put together and said, oh, here's
like a freaking Komodo dragon.
Well, now they're trying to say that the dinosaurs had feathers.
Yeah.
Like birds, right?
Because birds evolved from the dinosaurs.
They kind of, because like those flying dinosaurs.
Yeah, that's what they're trying to say.
Like, there's a whole bunch of.
What about flying videos? They're supposed to be like accurate dinosaurs and they all have feathers. It's weird
Yeah, accurate dinosaurs. They have feathers because they're birds and they used to fly
But how did it fly? It must have been really strong feathers if they're gonna put up a million pound dinosaur
It's just this doesn't seem well if they had if they had like proportioned feathers, they could fly
Yeah, it's a airplane, right? It'd be like yeah, I don't know. I don't know. I mean, I can't imagine like I don't know
Flying dinosaur. I know it's just things to think about, you know, but what are the uh?
Teradactyls teradactyls were dinosaurs that could fly
Teradactyls again, are these real animals or yeah, teradactyls or the flying dinosaurs that they have
Oh like Terry from Pewee's Playhouse. Remember that guy Terry?
No, well, maybe I think there was a dinosaur on Peewee's Playhouse. Well, I didn't know that was his name
But yeah, Terry. Yeah, exactly. Yeah, that that was a flying
Sort of dinosaur. They had a head kind of very angular
kind of snout and
Then the back of their head was angular also
I'll show you what you look like. This is Terry from Peewee Peewee's Playhouse
He was a pterodactyl and he was here is
Recognize him. Oh shit. Oh, I made it
Vaguely I vaguely recognize him. Yeah, but that's definitely a pterodactyl. It's a toy
Yeah, that's what remember that there he is
There he was, I want that genie, there's a genie in his head, I can draw him to his head.
A genie? Do you think that the gen are real? Some people think they're there.
There's like, we might be them, but it's like, you know, the gen were like created before man and never made a fire, right?
And so there are these fire spirits, and so they're fire, and so...
Then God made the humans and he told the gents to like bow down to the humans and other gents were like
Well, we're older. We're made of fire. They're made of like the clay of the earth
And so then God like their leader Iblis got they kind of like kicked out of their guard
It's kind of like the Satan story again, right?
Well, God kind of set a lot of enemies against humans when you really think about it
Please
There's some other books of Adam and Eve, they're called like, there's like secret books of Adam and Eve and there's other versions of it where it's like, they're just relentlessly fooled by the devil because the devil kept dressing as an angel and stuff like that and they kept getting so fucking confused and God, they're like, how do we tell the fucking difference between God and the devil?
They're just being talked about by a bunch of weird angels. It was like very overwhelming. So they didn't know who to trust really, right? But yeah.
It's almost impossible to...
Well, they kept they kept on aliving themselves and God had kept having to breathe it breathe life back into them to keep waking
up because they kept
That's why God had to go into the New Testament with the whole Jesus era because
I'm convinced of this
Okay, I've been out of control. I got to be yeah, I'm fast for a bit. Okay. I don't know. I think they're very
I'm gonna forgive all of you
What is it like?
So the original God was like Kronos, right?
It's like Saturn, right?
Saturn is like the very judgmental,
the harsh, you know, Jehovah is like, it's Saturn, right?
And so Saturn, and then it's like Jupiter.
And so what happened with Kronos is like Jupiter or Zeus,
like, you know, overthrew him.
And then, so that's what happened, like,
basically with, you know, Jupiter and Saturn here.
Like, you know, we were throwing the sets the golden age of Saturn, we're in this like Jupiterian age and, and so the Old Testament God is like the Saturn and the New Testament God is Jesus is like, you know, Jehovah or like Jesus is like Jesus, Jesus, you know, Jesus, Jesus, basically, basically, it's like, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus, Jesus,
There's there's so much to it
What was what was like Jesus Jesus was love right and Jupiter?
What is Jupiter Jupiter is like love and expansion and like, you know
Saturn is all about restriction and like difficulties, right? It's like there's two different
That's why we're under Saturn right capricorns. And so we have a really tough tough ruling planet
You know, he's like the taskmaster. So that's what we get really disciplined sometimes or like really like at least like
You know, like you know, we get punched by karma sometimes sometimes we're like able to like, you know control the karma because
Being a Capricorn is honestly and it's only my thought. I don't like to put this out into the universe very much
But I think that being a Capricorn is literally being the parent of everybody
We are the oldest sign of the Zodiac, we just are.
It represents the father.
It's like, I don't feel like I get to have enough fun
as a Capricorn, and that's what pisses me off
to where I will go into like where I am right now,
which is my reclusive face, like I'm talking to you,
but here I come to find out
we have the same freaking birthday.
So am I really talking to you or am I talking to myself?
Hmm.
Exactly.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you for talking to me today, though.
Seriously.
Thank you.
I'm another you.
You're like, you're like, thank you for just like existing.
You're awesome.
You're beautiful, funny.
I knew I would like you like when I saw you at I was like, oh, but I was just waiting
for you to come here because I wasn't going to go.
I'm glad.
Well, thanks for, thanks for waiting for me to come over here because today's been like
such a fun day because I'm in like.
a really cool place where I'm going to like just chill out for like the next few weeks
and your energy just like vibes with where I am and I'm just like having so much fun talking to you
and thanks. You're welcome. It's a pleasure.
Do you know, have you heard of Elisa Jordana?
Are you familiar with her?
Yes.
And, you know, a lot of people have, like,
tried to bring her up to me.
But I don't have anything negative to say about her.
I just, I think that it's like she's
on the cusp of doing something to where, like, suddenly,
everybody knows about her.
That's what I've always thought about her.
She did pretty much last year like everybody pretty much knows because you went viral, you know last year really big time
And so like a lot of people that I've talked to you know from just from that like most people
I wish that she had never had that captain content experience
That's my only you know because I didn't even know I never knew about her, but I like her. She's fun. She's like
She's kind of like the kind of woman that I'm friends with like when I look at her
I don't really know her or know much about her, but she's pretty much
pretty much like, like, knowing.
I called in a few times, I started like, you know,
sending some songs into her and calling into her
and I did readings for her and for several months.
And so she's been really nice.
She also like, like promoted my show a little bit
and like was super sweet to me.
She never did anything like,
no, no, no negative interaction with her ever.
Cool, I think a lot of people have her wrong. That's what I think happened because of like the whole stupid IP to stuff
I think that that guy was like he was out to get her
But she's interesting I like that she does like
controversial stuff, but at the same time it's like a talk show
Yeah, well, she's like our opposite sign like she's a cancer and so Capricorn cancer or like are the opposites on this on the Zodiac
Interesting. Yeah, that's interesting. No, I've dated a lot of cancers, actually
Yeah, the opposite the track kind of thing the opposite the tracks but sometimes yeah, it's gonna be a little bit crabby and Capricorn can be a little bit too much for
I feel like I I think a lot of people get jealous of her. She's got she has
Like if I had to give her any sort of spiritual advice,
be careful of women
because a lot of women get jealous of her.
That's what it is.
That's why I think she hasn't like broken out
because I've seen her try to befriend other women,
but that's what holds her back.
She should only be like male
until she gets where she wants to be.
She does have a big body count of a,
Former assistants and they get up past well
They just she shouldn't work with with women or even somebody who has like a super feminine energy
Doesn't have to be a woman. Maybe it's a guy who is like it has like a very feminine energy
Because she has like a very um, she's very strong. That's what I like about her
I have seen her deal with like, you know what? I think was wrong
Everyone was like dissing her for this
But not me because I think I know what happened in that situation and I'm not even gonna like like um
You know explore what I think but remember that guy
Who um pulled her hair
Yeah, I think that he should have done jail time
I feel like he tricked her. I think that people were misogynist and just like evil when they were like
Oh, she deserved it and stuff. I don't think that she did deserve that
I think that he probably was abusive toward her verbally for a while
And then all came to a culmination that day
But still she should not have gotten in the trouble for that
That is when I really started to like her like more than I liked her before
When I saw that happen because she's just trying to like make her stupid
You know, I won't say stupid, but you know, she's making her show her
Content YouTube thing and he didn't and he did that on purpose to humiliate her and when guys do that mess
Because I've had guys do that shit to me not to that extent
But guys have done stuff to me and that's what a lot of people like maybe they don't have empathy because they look at her
They're like, oh, she's pretty she deserves it, but no pretty people
get it worse than somebody else because everyone's out to get the pretty person.
Sometimes yeah, but sometimes like the pretty person's out there looking for like the like I think at least some mobs every place you go
Which it means she's a beautiful woman. Well, she does look for attention, but she wasn't looking for that
Right. Well, he gave her me if he donated over a million dollars to her cash
Yeah, but that didn't give him the right to do that
Right, but that's but that's what that's why he was like abusive to her because it's like he was like trying to get her like alone
He thought he paid for her like basically to be alone with her and she would knock it off her
To her stream because she didn't know she didn't want to have sex with him probably that's probably what he thought he could buy her
right
Okay, I don't think I don't see like and there is no right or wrong, but do you think that?
she
misled him if he did go in that direction or not either or it's like if
she did he deserved to be misled if she didn't but it's like I mean it's like
you know she's just like she just she's with herself another country he also
nice yeah but you know he's from a Los Angeles his family yes families from my
piece I think he's from I think he was from like the the Emirates the United
Yeah, I did too. And it's like, and she got like a lot worse than he did, right?
These are the kind of fallouts with most everyone.
I just, I don't have anything bad to say about her. Like, I feel like sometimes people
try to get me to say something bad about her, but I don't know.
No, I wouldn't. I wouldn't. No, I'm not saying that you are, but people, people do try to get me too.
And I don't have anything bad to say about her because I like the way that she like created her
YouTube presence. She definitely figured out how to make money on YouTube, definitely.
Yeah. Oh yeah. I mean, she's not even monetized on YouTube.
Well, she gets the donations.
Well, yeah, and exactly, but she, I mean, she's monetized, but she doesn't even like, you know,
she doesn't have a membership where she doesn't, I ask for super chat. She wants everyone to go through her,
um, through her, um,
you know, TTS system, which she has, and that's like, works better than in YouTube.
Well, that's, I mean, I could never do the TTS, like, I mean, as people can say anything to you,
I am so mindful at this stage in my life of what I allow to be input in my mind.
yeah about you know just what people even think about me like i know it doesn't matter but
it can affect you yes and um i go into like reclusive phases to where i'm like i don't even
want to know what you think about me yeah i mean i mean people can be very uh cool nowadays and like
Backstabbing now it is it's like you have to be careful you trust nowadays, right? Yeah. Well, I mean it depends on
You know what experience the person that's out with you, too
You know or what experience you've had with them somebody can have a completely different experience
With somebody
Yeah
Yeah, they completely different because it's like people will be different to different people. They are different
We have all kinds of different relationship with
Somebody else, right? It's like for different people. It's cool. Well, that's like like the best advice
I ever got and I give this advice to other people when it comes to like getting over somebody
like the person that you dated or
Were in a relationship with when you break up with them
they don't exist anymore and
I kind of
I think that's why even though I've definitely embarrassingly acted out when
it's come to, you know, my family members passing, when it's come to most exes I've
had, I look at it like a death. I look at it like, well, that person's gone.
Yeah, I mean that but it is like a death
But it's like they can be back from the dead sometimes though because sometimes people will come and Hoover you you know
They'll come and bring in I've done. I've only done one like second go around in my life with like a long-term
Relationship I've only done one second go around and it did not work out
Yeah
Yeah, well, that's good. That's good then because it's like
I've dealt with a lot of narcissists in my life written a like have a specific pattern of behavior
Were you raised by a narcissist?
No, not really. I mean, I'm but you know, I was raised by very
beautiful, but I'm not a narcissist like not like a
Not like someone competing like a lot of narcissists when they have kids they they compete with their kids
Or they like they are jealous of their kids and stuff like that or they try to get the kids to live through them
I know it's like my mom or something like that
I don't think she was but then again everyone has like a little degree of narcissism and like, you know
It's called just helping self-esteem sometime
Yeah
I think it just depends on how far it goes with the person, yeah.
Right, because there's healthy self-esteem and then there's like malignant narcissism or like,
where it's like you're trying to hurt people, you're trying to like see other people as like animals or...
Yeah.
And then you try to like just like drain that like it's like a vampire is a kind of thing
Well, the narcissism I I mean the the the trait is kind of glamorized. So I think that there's like more
Narcissist or at least people who embody the trait than ever before
Right because what's glamorized so it's psychopathy. So is like criminality like a lot of stuff is glamorized by the society right now for
And that for the courage. Yeah, encourage
And why? Just to fill prisons or to support this idea of a certain kind of culture?
And it's kind of interesting.
I think it's a lot of things that I think that like, you know, in like today's age,
if you want to look at it in movies, like the movie like American Psycho with Christian Bale,
that pretty much turned a lot of women on. They're like, ooh.
He might kill my friend, but at least he has a really good job
Women did you pay prisoners are attracted to prisoners for some reason right? It's like yes
That's well. That's what um, what's her name? Kate was talking about how she's dealt with like like would draw would drew her to
Barry it was having communicated with her ex who was incarcerated
And I was like, wow.
So you have like a lot of women who are like pin pals
to the prisoners.
That's, I've heard of it.
That's something that's pretty alien to me.
We're not falling in love with serial killers.
It's like falling in love with a celebrity.
They're like, they're kind of an attraction.
They like want to get married to them in jail
and all kinds of stuff.
Pretty crazy.
I think it's the whole good girl, bad boy dichotomy.
Right.
I think a lot of women who are good girls, they're very attracted to the bad boys
and they seek it out.
It's like Charles Manson's like the Manson family these girls were like most girls from like wealthy families
You know and they're just bored with their perfect lives and they're like and then you have like
Good guys or guys there. Well, they're not really good, but they think that they view themselves as good
Who are attracted to what they view as like the girl from the bad side of the tracks?
Yeah, you know, huh? Yeah, they like the
the bad girl, right?
But it's like, a lot of times the bad girl
is just like, they like to sleep with them.
And then like, you know, kind of like,
that's the bad girl is kind of like, you know,
known as like the-
Yeah.
Framiscuous sometimes.
But sometimes people are attracted to that, you know,
there's a really good movie called 58 Kill,
check that out, or 68 Kill.
And it's about this bad, very, very bad girl.
And then she gets her,
she's kind of a dorky boyfriend and she gets them to like,
get involved in this like this criminal lifestyle.
It's pretty interesting.
So.
Well, he deserved it
Well, yeah, he deserves it. She tries yeah, yeah
durations, you know, yeah, but
Yeah, so but you know, I want to spoil it. Let's see. Let's see that movie
Okay, let's see how the chat doing thinking of making another
Yeah, but I'm like, I don't know the last one's so expensive and that wait for a while. Okay. I'm waiting for my package to here's my cat
There's my cat Lola
Speaking of packages, I'm expecting an Amazon package today
Go and look for it. Okay. I'm gonna look for first time to do this
I hear birds, huh that bird
Yeah, I'll walk back over here. Oh
Right my tape is here. I'll be back when you grab my tapes
All right
Oh, I got two packages.
Okay.
Hey, what's up, people around the home?
Let's see, who's in here?
What's the last comment?
Where's everybody?
Well, that's good.
You have yours.
I don't seem to have any packages
unless they put them somewhere else.
So, I'm going to make a cut with Amazon apps
because if it's possible, they could be somewhere else.
Have you ever seen that?
What is that? Gorilla glue?
Gorilla tape.
Oh, Gorilla tape.
Yeah.
I've seen Gorilla glue before, but not Gorilla tape.
Hopefully it works good.
I have to tape my tripod back together.
It's not staying on me.
So I'll fix my tripod.
Then I'll be able to have a camera on it.
Maybe it will be.
Ah.
Hmm.
Oh, shit.
It says delivered, but the question is where.
So you don't have a boyfriend?
Or what's the last boyfriend you had?
No, no, I thought I had a boyfriend, but we met in person and it did not exactly work out.
You meet online?
Well, here's the thing.
Okay, tell me what you think about this.
He initially told me back in 2023.
That we'd met, okay? I
Don't recall having ever met him
At all
Yeah, so just recently I flew out to his area to meet him. I felt zero
recollection of having met him
And I think that he did misrepresent himself to me in a lot of ways
so
Yeah, I can't trust I'm just not gonna talk to him anymore
Yeah, that was a bit much
Plenty of fish in the sea though. I don't know but you're not like really
I'm sure you could find a guy if you were looking for one. I'm not yeah, I'm not really like
Yeah, you know, I was willing to give him a chance because I felt like
You know, he seemed to know enough about me to deal with me
but I
Wasn't like
Gung-ho about it
So even though I'm sad that I'm not gonna talk to him anymore. I don't feel that bad
So, yeah
Yeah, you know the right one you will know if it's the wrong one you don't want to waste any time
Yeah, and that's the thing. That's why I wanted to meet him in person
I think that he wasn't really ready to meet me in person because I did kind of you know
I was proactive about it. I didn't ask him to pay for the ticket or anything like that
I have my own you know hotel and all that kind of crap
All he had to do was like, you know show up and he was all right
I won't say and you know it. Maybe it was just me
But I'm not like
Devastated like I did act out. I feel like if I hadn't just lost my dad
I wouldn't have reacted as badly as I did because it was like, you know a stacker kind of
Situation
Yeah, I just kind of look at it like, well, in a way, he was, you know, a good kind of
rudimentary sort of therapist until I met him in person.
But he didn't even look in person like he did in his pictures.
You know?
I mean, we hadn't video chatted that could have maybe, I probably should have done that.
That was in the pictures, but substantially younger, okay? Yeah
20 years ago picture probably yeah, you know, it's weird like
didn't rent a car like normally when I travel somewhere I rent a car but I
only went out for like two days okay so I figured you know I'm all I'm gonna do
is like have lunch and dinner with him so I don't need to rent a car if I need
to go anywhere I'll just get like Uber or DoorDash or whatever but
he was like, oh, I want to show you where I used to live, right?
And I'm like, okay, whatever.
And this is the Laguna Beach area of California.
So, you know, we drive up into like this hilly area,
which is a neighborhood, and I guess that's the neighborhood
that he grew up in that he wanted to show me.
But I'm not so certain that he actually grew up there.
And the reason I think that is because when we were coming
down the hill,
He was acting so paranoid driving down that hill, which was a steep hill, but still if
you grow up somewhere and you've taken that drive, according to him, when he was in high
school, he had his own car and he would, you know, drive himself to school and whatnot,
you wouldn't be all freaking out driving down a hill.
So I I won't say I was catfished, but like maybe minimally in a weird way
This led yeah
So I had that happen, but I just really I
Don't think I want to date anybody for a while because I'm really like I have a good job
don't want really any like crazy drama I don't want to be an adoptive mom to
somebody else's children and that's really like I like I don't have like
I think I still need to wait a few years before I can date and find somebody who's going to be, like, a long time, like, year, like, multi-year long companion, because a lot of guys who are my age, they're in, like, this arena to where if they're available, they're in the midst of, like, a divorce.
or it's something else to where I've already surpassed
whatever it is that they're dealing with
and I don't want to be a part of their process.
Yeah.
You already know about it, but you're not gonna say Queen of Swords energy or is that you already know about it?
So you're willing to cut it off before doing it, right?
Yeah, like I'm fine. I'm fine on my own like, you know, sometimes you think to yourself
Oh, I'm lonely, but you know, I have friends that I've had for years. I have family
It you know, it's not always the same as like an exciting
romantic
whirlwind sort of relationship, which is like my favorite sort of thing, but you can't always have what your favorite sort of thing is and
you know, I'm grateful when I really think about it, like as much as many mistakes that I've made in my youth
that probably are viewed as mistakes. I
was so blessed when it came to dating really hot exciting guys seriously like I have had some freaking amazing romantic experiences which is like my favorite thing like that's what I'm better about now is that.
They're not as frequent as they used to be, but I still get them on occasion.
I get them on occasion, but not like like 20s everywhere, 30s still there, 40s slow down
sucks, but as far as like those exciting knock you off your rocker, you know, kick you in
romance kind of experiences. I've had more than my fair share. So
blessed about that. So happy about it. Because I don't think
some people ever have it. I really don't. I don't think some
people ever get it.
A lot of people don't and 50% of people that think they do like they'll get divorced and stuff like that. And so it's yeah
Yeah, well, they don't ever get anything like like I've just had like the really cool
exciting, you know, almost like
stereotypical kinds of
Relationships to where it was like whoa that guy broke my heart, but he sure as fuck was a hot guy
so
Yeah, I don't, um, I'm not that mad about certain things.
Some guys are like, I don't care if you cheat on me so hot, you
know, it's like that.
You know, the guys who do that, like, you know, they always
come back at you 10 years later, they do clockwork. They do
come back and then you see them and you're like, ew, glad I
glad that didn't work out all the best.
Bye!
Things work out or don't work out for a reason.
Yeah.
For real.
You can learn the lessons.
A lot of times it's past life stuff and you get caught with these past life partners
that you're supposed to finish up the lesson, but if you finish the lesson, that's cool.
I believe in that.
Look, I totally think that and maybe if it's not like a full life somehow, it's like the
energy that's attached to you that you got to confront and deal with.
and be like, ew, I have to vanquish whatever that cringe energy is that's exuding from
you upon me. But if you vanquish it, if you confront it, it doesn't come back.
Yeah, but it's like if you like if you keep you like there's a saying in the Bible
Like if you like kick out a demon out of your out of your head or something like an unwanted demon
And then you let it like another one. It'll come back like three times worse
You know it's like you have to like know that that that definitely I do feel like I
Think that has to do with that like, you know the rules of karma also like and not being a hypocrite
You know I have to check myself on that quite often
Yeah, we are
human beings. Yeah, because, you know, we are these dual beings. And so it's like, we can
always believe two things at the same tube, conflicting beliefs, we can hold them at once.
And then it depends on who you are that day, you know, and I'm not saying that that has to do
with, you know, a person not being consistent. But some days you feel mellow, other days,
You might feel a little mischievous, and you might say to yourself,
I feel like adding into some gossip today.
I feel like doing this.
And if you do, you do.
That's just where you're at sometimes.
Yeah. I mean, I'll make mistakes too,
but it's like, especially people relapse and they do all kinds of things and make them.
You know, they kind of go backwards sometimes, but we can always like, as long as we like have a knowledge of our higher self, we can always move toward the higher self move away from our lower self, you know, just kind of be in the lower self sometimes it's sometimes more fun.
Sometimes you got to change locations to at least even touch ground with your higher self. I'm that kind of person to where it, you know,
Meaning you can't do it where you are and be like too distracted for it. Well, what I found when it's come to
Me keeping certain addictions where they need to be as far as drinking
Change of location if I find that I'm indulging too much. I
Need to change locations and that does help me tremendously
Right now, I'm being real gentle with myself, but just as far as forgiving myself, as far
as not being perfect, I'm doing a lot of that, and you know, I gave myself, I thought I only
needed like three months to get over, you know, what I've been getting over, but I'm
I can't afford me to daylight, so I'm doing it.
Especially if you dated like a narcissist or somebody would make a talk to personality or something.
Or like a catfish or whatever he was on, it's a contention.
Oh, I was talking about the death of my dad.
I wasn't talking about that.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry.
No, it's okay.
No, the guy.
I'm already over that.
Okay.
It's okay.
Yeah, that was weird.
Well, you know what?
He knew I had just lost my dad, so he kind of like bonded with me on that.
And I'm not saying he was doing it maliciously, but he just wasn't in-person who...
thought he was like, you know, he sounds a little opportunistic or something
like that like you know yeah yeah it was a little that was that was weird but
I've already kind of like just
You know, I wish I hadn't said anything publicly, but you know, maybe I need to be more accepting of myself when it comes to that
Because you know what maybe sometimes I want some attention. Ha ha ha ha ha. Here's my attention
I'm on Slyke's panel and and he's
Psychologically breaking me down. I
Wouldn't do that, but I do like to like
You like to like help people work through some things because it's like I might say something that will like
That will like ring true or something like that or something that I feel like sometimes
You're a good prompter. You're definitely a good prompter when it comes to just like you know keeping the conversation going
Where'd he go come back psych I
Think his internet went out give him a moment
Hope everyone's having a good weekend. I definitely am feeling blessed
Feeling blessed
Carefree at this moment, but as they say never relax
I should relax let me think is there anything I shouldn't relax about hmm probably not
Probably not
Might try and make a bonfire tonight
might
I might not
I'm not exactly experienced in doing that
I probably shouldn't sorry about that. Oh, it's okay. I
Was just musing about if I should make a bonfire tonight or not
And I was thinking being that I'm not experienced with that probably not
Here's the link. I'll put the link up.
Probably not.
Be careful. If you light a fire, you know, make sure you keep it on.
Yeah, well, there's a fire pit, but I'm not experienced with doing that.
So I probably need to watch some YouTube videos before attempting that.
If I attempt it and I might not attempt it.
If I see a neighbor, I'll ask them for help.
We'll see might pull Lisa Lopez. You know what that means. Lisa Lopez. What does that mean?
Yeah, but she's like left-eyed. Remember she burned out her boyfriend's house? Oh
God
Yeah, no, I don't want to do that. I think it's Andre Rice. No, no, not doing that. Not going in that direction
This isn't my boyfriend's house, but I'm a person's house. Yeah
I sort of
Well, sometimes you got to bring your man's house down sometimes. Well, he was cheating on her. Maybe. I don't know. Yeah
I think Bita is gonna come up with this.
Maybe she paid for that house.
Maybe she put money into that house
so I don't even know about that.
He was a football player.
He was like an NFL player then.
And so he designed the house.
Well, he deserved it, yeah.
Well, I don't know.
He happened because he was like,
I think he came home at like five in the morning
after they fought from a club.
And then she saw him coming.
She saw him come out of the car smiling.
She said, if he had a good time,
I'd drive this fucking here.
She'd gathered all his shoes
and then she'd put them in the bathtub,
set it on fire and brew it in the house.
Wow.
Well, TLC actually, like, you know, they didn't make very much money, they pretend a really
bad contract.
Yeah, there's like a lot of deep dives into TLC on YouTube, actually.
And they all got a lot of, like, fame, but.
that they didn't really get any um real royalties or merch or anything
The record company signed most of that, you know, they
Little bit and everything they got they paid for all their like, you know, video music video shoots and stuff like that
So there was like not very much slept, which would suck if you're like
You two are like bonding. I took a nap because I was up last night, you know, I did a stream. I was drunk
well i wasn't drunk i was buzzed and then it's okay and then i was like oh my god uh psychy's
still alive with um alex so it's so cute i was on and then i and then i left because i ran out
cigarettes and i went to the store and then i came back and i i love in talking to psych because
psych is psych
Yeah, he's he's calm. He's like very chill. You know, and he's he's in the psych that the psychomatrix
Psycho I'm in a psyche verse. Yes, the psychiverse
He's very addicting. Um, you know, I really like psych and then sometimes I get mad at him and then I always come back, you know
Yeah, he's an addicting one. He's very sweet. He's got a good heart
Yeah. Did you see his modeling pictures? No. The AI one shorts Alex. Okay, let me see if I have them in here. Yeah.
I didn't mean to interrupt you guys this conversation. No, I'm happy you're here girl. I'm just, I am high today. I'm a little intoxicated. I'm eating some cheese right now.
and that's what I'm doing today.
That's good. That's good. Just relax. You deserve it.
Well, you did too. How are you doing? How are you feeling?
I'm good. You know, I'm good. Um, I don't have to go somewhere like
at 8pm because I'm in Cali, right? So I was like an hour in house.
I have to get ready. But then I saw you guys. I was like, oh, it's so cute.
I couldn't resist that to come up here.
I'm happy you're on here I'm happy always to see you Alex you I'm very grateful to you for
a couple of things that you did for me when I was having a hard time you want me to take that last
thing down because I thought like no no whatever you do it's fine with me I don't you know but um
like just be careful please seriously okay because
Some of these people are way more serious than you would think.
Yes. It's a lot.
If you connect the dog, you'd be very surprised,
but that can't be much, you know what I mean?
Like you're stationary because I was thinking about this like you're stationary and I I blame myself
For what happened to you in the one. Yeah, don't ever blame you have nothing to do with it at all
I think it's linked in a way to
The everything that I was saying about Zaya
That's what I think no no don't ever ever blame yourself. I think well, I think maybe not completely but in part
I think it is
And I think like maybe if I hadn't brought up something that wouldn't happen
So no, I was happening before I like like it wasn't the first time it happened like a week and a half ago
and um, yeah, I've taken care of some stuff, but no, I
Don't ever feel like that. It has nothing to do with you. Do you have like a security camera? You need a security camera?
Yes, and I got an extra one now too
Yeah
I took some pre-crushions
Okay, but I live like in a very safe neighborhood. Um
But it's still you know, it's like still you don't really want to know like somebody knocking on your door when you didn't order anything
It's like they're just coming on
I saw that video and he came back
three times yeah that I think that that was not what it appeared to be I'm still
really confused about it because he wouldn't tell me what delivery system it
was and he was like avoiding it and he just went out and then he came back and
he came with like weed so I was like
Why is he offering me weed? I have my own, but then I thought maybe he smelted, you know, at my place and he was like, Oh, that's see, that's weird. If you live in a and I'm just assuming if you live in a decent neighborhood.
That's not going to happen.
It does.
Yeah.
I've never had a delivery for somebody.
I think somebody sent him to your house using different like guises or tactics.
So just, you know, don't don't pursue the person.
Like I was scared when I saw in the video that you and like, I don't blame you because
It was my spider flight. I don't know the third time. I just you want to you like your territory. I get it
That's what you're doing. You know, you're your inner instinct was like fuck this shit. Yeah, you know
I'm gonna this is my house because I get that but just the timing of some of that. Oh
Cuz because people that some some people
They don't quite
live in
Like a world of boundaries
So you gotta
Just be careful and if it's somebody at your door and you didn't order anything don't answer the door
I won't I won't okay. I think I was just drinking I was on live and
I was more like hey you want to see what's really happening to me over and over and
That was your exciting moment of
Okay, like I was even saying I think it was I went into someone's chat. I think it was Sam as chat the other night
And I was like, that was her moment because it was, that was your IRL.
No one can ever say that you have not done any IRL over the past few years.
That was your freaking IRL.
Me running down the stairs.
Yes.
We saw your painted toes.
We know you got red painted toes.
We saw you running down your athletic.
Lady Gypsy.
You're running like a gazelle.
You're like a gazelle in the Sahara Desert galloping along and you're going to do something.
But, you know, then then you got your wits about you and you're like, no, let me go back inside.
And that was good.
Yeah. But that was your moment.
So you got you represented for all of us women who are over 40, still trying to do our thing.
You did your thing.
Oh, thank you, Alex.
You don't have to do anything else until 2028.
I'm in my fifties now, so I'm now 50.
Enjoy your, you know, forties.
They're sunshine.
Yeah.
Actually one of my best ages was like 48, 48 was a good age.
Oh my god, beat up, beat up, beat up.
Do you know that me and Psych have the same birthday?
But yeah, I was listening in the chat
because I was like going in and out.
I was like modding for this traveling gypsy, Psych, you know.
But I was listening.
I was like, oh my god, that's so freaking cute.
You guys are both capricorns and this is why you're bonding.
You guys are like new besties now.
Good co-host good co-host, but he might hate me soon. No, he won't
He actually doesn't have a hateful like born in his body. He doesn't really I've never seen him hate anyone. I
See them get agitated and bitchy. Oh that side of them when he becomes like bitchy, but it's still not that bad
It's not as bad as when I become bitchy
But that was your IRL, so well you've had many of them you are you know, you are
I did my IRL for the year. I look I did too much no more. Yeah, it's dangerous for you too.
Very dangerous for you as well. Very. No more. I gave you international drive and getting kicked out of the bar.
That's what I got. Well, the part thing is like was fucking not fair. That's just, you know, I mean, I get it. You can just be like, you okay. And then maybe just like, you know, just wait for them to, you know, be able to silver if I'm not saying you were drunk, but you were emotional. But the other
I am so grateful. I did not get arrested. I didn't have any sort of, you know,
weird interaction. I am very blessed that the Uber arrived promptly. I don't even remember
doing the app to call the Uber, but they appeared. So it's like, you know, I got back to where I
I feel like, okay, that was my moment of weakness.
I acted a fool, fuck it.
That's my 2025 IRL.
I'm sure a lot of people at the bar,
you know, do crazier stuff.
So it's okay, just they were probably a little prissy,
you know, and everything happens for a reason.
Well, you know, I needed to do something.
I hadn't done anything in a while.
So no, it was reality, you know, it's reality whether it was, you know, bad, um, I felt so bad for you like that date when you were up there.
I really wanted to just come up there and like hug you, but I just, I know when you're in that zone, you don't want to talk to anyone.
I went on a rampage and I'm still kind of on the rampage, but.
I am also realizing that a lot of that rampage rage
was misdirected energy when it came to, you know,
some other stuff that I was, you know,
innately suppressing.
So, you know, but somebody has to be middle-aged
and act a fool on the internet.
So...
Oh, I do it all the time.
I do it all the time.
I think I'm on the top of it.
We gotta answer the call.
Yeah, I think I've cried like probably 10 times on the panel in the last like couple months
So I don't know maybe it's just taking a toll on me and like alcohol is kind of a depressant too
Sometimes I'm just like in the greatest mood having the best time and then sometimes it's all added up and bottled up
And I get emotional so at least we're just being real, you know, it's not a script. It's really our feelings. It happens
Yeah, yeah
Well, that's why I like I've been trying to toggle more so from alcohol to THC
But you know, I just kind of forgiven myself and I've kind of said to myself, you know what?
Let yourself be a little fucked up for a while. Let yourself deal with certain emotions
Let yourself be a little sloppy and that's what I'm doing
Am I here I like to meet I like your energy and whether it's like then you know a different area or whatever it is
But you've got your just energy has changed a lot
Whatever you're doing just keep it up and just keep getting getting better and better and better and stronger and
You know your talented. It's a lot of weed. I'll be honest about that. It's a lot of weed
Yeah, shut the fuck up. We're gonna come take your read Joe. You're just too far away
Nice to meet you, man
Joe made it to the panel you damn right you better be nice to psych
Kick him out will
But I did have a bottle and I seem to probably break that bottle over
It's okay
He meant he means on Minecraft
He means on Minecraft
Jo has such a crush on you
Jo jokes with me all the time
He is crushing on you girl
He is crushing
Jo has a crush on Psyche too
Kind of everybody and you and where do you go? Yeah, bring him back. It's okay. I think he he meant like, you know
In a in a video game. It was a fucking little joke psyche. God
Don't be on here acting like a weirdo
Don't tell jokes. You're right. Don't even tell any jokes. No, but sometimes you're
Cuz you sometimes I'm what Alex sometimes I'm what sometimes you're
you're a jerk sometimes excuse me excuse me bitch excuse you bitch joe that's kind of a bitch
were you mad because you weren't like allowed up for a while excuse you bastard
See, I'm not even seeing you
That's why people don't like you because you're all nice and then all of a sudden you call me a bitch
And I didn't even have a like a retort
And I'm gonna good and I'm in a good mood and I'm feeling all like
And you're just like, like, did you have like stuck in whiskey, because you're not on the cannabis level, you're on like, what are you doing, whiskey?
I
Can hear my windows
Oh, it's Kim is over there. Okay, so you're
He does change when she's there yeah, I like him, but I
Change I will take care of any woman. There's a woman you're talking about. I'm a real man any women that needs help
I will help them. Well, that's good. I'm not against Kim. I just know that you're different when you're there
No, you're scared of Kim. So then you get aggression and then you take it out on other people. Yeah, I mean
That's kind of weird
We should go on though we should go on
Why what do you want? I got shit to do, man. I'm not fucking
Yeah, we was talking badly about you when you weren't here. Hey, Kim
What do you want man, I don't got time for this games we got time all day
I brought it to my brother psyche. He's like a brother to me. He's like a long hair gay haircut brother to me Kim
There she comes. Here she comes. Listen
Hello, what do you want?
No, I love you. I don't want to make it all about me. Alex is here beat is here two of the most wonderful ladies on YouTube
No, she's not in the door yet. Here she comes. I'll lock the door. I
Gotta stick hold on I gotta stick on my door. Look. Can you see the stick like the thing that like holds the door closed?
No
Like her extra security
Like a brook
Yeah
I'm up here my friends like he and Alex and there's no camera
There's someone over there. Oh, I hear. Oh, yeah, you're right
Kim we were we were defending you he was talking shit about
Team team Kim
You mind if I turn my camera off for one second
I wasn't asking you I was asking Alex Kim
Well, you know what you get the hell out of here get out of my house get out you guys okay?
No fucking talk to me like that
I
She's saying I do too much like you. Do I do too much buddy?
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, you're very obnoxious
Be nice to him Kim's like his hair and she'd be like that looks like Rick Springfield
Be nice to Kim. I
Wish I had Jesse's bitch
No
Yeah, call her back in a little bit. She gots real men to talk to you. You shut the fuck up
I think Kim and Joe could have their own reality show together.
This is a stream.
I'm not even going to say it because I'm going to be rude to you, Bita,
but there's a lot of things I can think you can do.
And the first one will be, I'm like, let's say it.
Don't say it.
Joe, why don't you make a stream with you and Kim?
It can be the Joe show.
I'm not going to make it
But it's funner just to join Alex. It's too much pressure
Like to go live and like have to know who your mods are and like shit like that. I just can't do it
So I just like to join and I don't
Come here look at psyche's hair
Psyche is a movie star
Oh, thank you.
Oh, my God.
Does he look like Rick Springfield or not?
Come here.
Look inside you.
Does he look like Rick Springfield?
Who's Springfield
Springsteen, but I don't know
I'm on a panel. I don't need your interruptions. Look. It's like he's here. Yes. Yes
We want to hear Kim, yeah, let's talk to Kim
She's like and she's in my freezer, by the way
No, she's in my free. I'm not fucking joking. Oh, you're getting a soda
Hi
What are you doing? This is the page of Alex
She's a page yep, I am hi
What are you guys doing?
We're tolerating Joe's behavior right now, and then I came up here and
Psyche and Alex have been talking for hours bonding like 20s and
Yeah
I'm just closing up. I'm going to go golfing, but I thought I'd pop on and say hello because
I didn't really last night much, and I won't probably snipe a little bit later, so.
Okay.
Last time.
I'll send some balls to outer space just for you.
Thank you Paige.
Please do that.
Bad, hopefully.
My golf game is getting better, but I still, I'm not great and everybody keeps reminding
me of that.
He's honest. Yeah, I see you. I see you're like you're getting you're becoming pro your positioning and everything. Yeah. I think you're going to be like, you know, so much.
Technique does know some things, Joe.
They just fucking look at a real damn good.
Can't make this company
Golf stands for gentlemen only ladies forbidden original really are you serious?
Alright guys, I'm gonna hop down. Alex, it's so good to talk to you as always. Paige, love you, love you.
Psyche, we'll talk to you later. You'll be nice to Cam. Don't be a brat. Okay, I'll see you guys.
Okay, love you guys. Bye, Alex. Bye, Beats. Gentlemen, what?
Good bye, Beats. I'll be the left. Oh, I thought Paige was leaving. Dammit. I am gonna be.
Gentleman, what was I saying?
It's a gentleman, what?
You are like Gatbird Center,
and it's like, you're that little Spencer thing.
Oh, gentlemen, only ladies forbidden, ULF.
is that what golf really stands for yeah no it doesn't really it can't I'm gonna
I'm gonna Google the origins of this look it up too hey I really did enjoy
watching you hit those golf balls I I watched it and I rewatched it and I
left like a perfect golfer with her little hat on and everything she's gonna
go here she's gonna go she's like sexy woods
Here, maybe I'll pop on when I'm golfing and then you guys can be the judge of that.
He's a golfing girl.
I'm gonna hit that one right there.
It's my favorite one.
Okay.
Yeah.
I'm gonna shut down and then I'll pop back on in a little bit, okay?
Bye.
Love you.
Bye-bye.
Okay
She was out there on the golf
Shows like her horse hair
She looked cute that that look at the good funky derby
What's your problem? What's your problem?
Why you eat my friends? What's wrong? It's like why you got your face like this in the camera come on
But I'm just laughing. I'm just laughing. I'll fuck with you. I feel like the golf girl made you angry Joe
Like is it are you mad?
I wish I could hear you Alex say it again, sweetheart. I think
Because she's like
I feel like she made you angry cuz she's like happy
That's how you cuz you you're like your attitude to like this dark turn
Saturday night's all right for I think he got mad because the rock girl is happy mm-hmm
That's what I think
That's Paige. I think he's in love with Paige maybe and we'd like to yeah, well, I mean cuz she's like if she's like
He's running around on the golf course fresh air, you know happy with
The other golf people who you know, I guess she would have to like what is she doing driving the golf cart? Maybe I don't know
I feel like that was like
the equivalent of having like wintergreen tic-tacs.
She was super refreshing to watch.
I'm gonna take a picture, come here.
Let's take a picture together.
She was super refreshing.
Come here, take a picture with me.
We're gonna put our heads together, here we go.
Or no, put your hair on my head
to where it looks like I have hair.
Hi Alex, Alex, I grow my hair down for you.
No, come on, Kim, get over here.
Look at this, this is my best friend you're talking about.
Oh, that's all you get. That's all she wants to do
Where's your friends like me? Oh, that's right, you don't have
But you're on because I'll tell you right now if Alex was here
I will fucking throw Kim in a fucking river
But if I could beat Alex if I could be my sweetheart Alex, I will fucking I would hand I would handcuff Kim
Fucking drop her off and drop her in the trunk. Don't worry. I'm not gonna. I'm not gonna try to meet Joe. It's okay
I'm just kidding Alex. I would never do that. But the other day came out and say I was the greatest guy born
Well, I think you are I think you're okay, but be nicer to Kim
All right, I'm just fucking around. I'm only messing with Kim. Look at her Kim. Look at me right now
All right, where are you?
Where are you?
There you are.
I'm only messing with her.
She knows, have I ever treated you wrong?
Yes or yes?
Yes.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
Have I ever treated you bad?
No.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Do I always let you take every roll of tool of paper
that is in my house?
You don't let me have anything else.
Thank you, Alex.
Okay.
You need some Starbucks right now.
Woo.
You know what? That's generous to let the person have all your toilet paper.
Oh, you're a professor. You've got real wide wallet.
Realizing that you need toilet paper, but not having it.
I literally was looking up and just looked at my eye.
Get out of my house.
Now you're looking at my wallet. Get out of here. Get out.
I'm trying to have fun. My friend Alex is psyche and all she care about him is money
Take all his cash
Stay the slice face. You're the one that's like spacey
Take all his cash and she said her cat is like cat hair. Let me see your hair. No, that's cat hair
What's wrong Alex, what's wrong sweetheart?
Nothing. I'm like I I am just happy to be on a panel
Yeah, if I met Alex like a real man. I like psyche. I'm a real man. I could say care about like psyche
So I don't fucking I'm okay fuck up motherfucker back the fuck up. I I know I'm I'm okay
Look at you through the camera back the fuck up boy
Alice is a sweetheart I don't give a fuck what anyone says they talk about my baby Alex
they're talking about me and I got her back and that's fucking it that's the last thing I gotta
say about that that's a scary thought yeah we are scary thought fuck you no I got her back to the day
I died you don't know Alex like I do you don't know her yeah scary thought you're a scary thought
You ain't going to sit around and tell my friend Alex. Sorry as you eat my Pringles by the way as you eat my can of Pringles
Oh, you're attacking me. Okay. Well, you know what get the hell out of my house. Get out
Get out
I got to go and come back because I got to figure out where some packages are.
I got you.
See you later.
Bye.
Thank you for talking.
Good times birthday should lie 23rd boy. You're over talking. Good times birthday. I don't care when your birthday is 23rd is not going to be a link down there.
Someone was asking for a link.
I'm sorry, I got it live. I love you. Good times from Michigan.
You know what? Guess whose birthday I'm going to be celebrating, psyche.
not Kim's. I'll be celebrating good time today.
I'm going to be in BG County.
All right, well, let's talk talk.
Is that your sister, Joe?
I don't know, is that Scotty?
What up, Scotty?
Go ahead and talk to her, man.
That's good.
That's not your sister?
Scotty, got something to say to you, Kim.
What do you got to say to her, man?
You his sister, Kim?
Of course, yeah, that's what we do in the whole time.
She's my sister.
We tricked you guys.
Shut the fuck up, Donnie.
Get out of here.
I'm not his sister.
Oh, you want to bet you ate.
You could buy the name for a dog, but if you want my brother.
I was being nice.
She's not my sister.
She's my sister.
I was being nice.
Salt and pepper.
It was either your sister or your mom, Joe.
What do you want me to do?
I was being nice.
She looks like my mom.
Not even talking about my mom, Gotti.
You're banishing.
Get him out of here.
It's like, you can salt my mom.
Yeah, it's like, get me out of here.
Thank you summer at least a real woman is here. These are
Thank you. I have to get a little grace time on my panel time because nobody came up until like 30 minutes ago
You did no she did it was like you gotta pay ten dollars to join this summer fucking. Thank you summer sweetheart. Thank you, babe
Thank you. You made us pay to join in summer paid. Therefore,
let's make you do anything. I was that summer. We didn't make me
do anything, but I don't mind. Yeah, I opened the panel up
for everybody. Thank you very much. Thank you very much. I
appreciate it. Thank you very much. So, we can have some
Friday night. Listen to you talk like that's fucking gay.
Yeah. Well, I'm too bad.
I
That one up
So that one woman that was on she was on for like I I don't want to admit this I plop in an hour for like
Real quick, you know, she was on for like four hours, dude. I took a nap
I liked watching her and psyche bond and everything, but I was like I don't want her to ruin her man
Like she was on for a whole fucking six seven eight hours. I don't know. I'm just worried for her brand
This fucking Joe guy, I told him since day one. I'll give a fuck about him. He's a he's a bubbling idiot
Yeah, I don't want to shit on everybody here, but this Joe fucking I said this is day one. Did I know what?
Hello, how's everybody doing tonight? I'm out of here
We're doing better than psyche obviously
I like that piece of food
There we go. Yeah. So, there's
psyche. Does Alex read card?
Is Alex what? It's not your
business. It's not your business.
Alex. He was asking does she read
cards? Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
no. I've already said is she a
retard? Sorry about that. No,
I don't know her but like I said it was a good conversation with her and psyche
I just wanted to make sure I could get the panel touched out a little bit time-sponsored close
Yeah, I got you. Oh, I got you. I think everybody was enjoying your conversation and letting you bond so they didn't want to come up and bother you guys I
Can't believe that she
You get drunk what
You're what I said
Like, I'm not bad.
No, you look like, uh...
Who do you think you look like?
You look like a guy from Haven, Kim said.
I've never seen that gay movie, but you look like a guy from that.
What movie is that? I've never heard of it.
Haven?
Look at these sexy whispers.
What do you think about that?
Mine? I am sexy?
Thank you.
I don't know. No, I don't think anyone agrees.
Beautiful.
Give me that. Give me that right here.
Very good.
Would you let Psyche hit Joe in the back like that?
No.
I don't want to hit Joe.
So I'm fucking with you. Let me hit him first.
My dad you fucking bought it
Fuck you I hit it now. Don't put it put it
Oh, you got your pay
What does she mean she got a good day she can't say my mouth
Do what I didn't say that
All righty freak. I'm going summers here. At least a real at least a real human being is here a real person
Mmm. Yeah, I went to Zach's music got me a salad and some fish fries
I just woke up. I was fucking salt your salad summer. That's all said salad round, baby
That's all I have on this man. I said I wanted to give summer a kiss on her asshole. Really psyche
Throw off like
God I wanted to kiss summer on her fucking tattooed asshole is that so fucking wrong?
Assholes not quite tattooed, but cheeks are all right. Well your ass cheeks about
I don't know what I'm saying.
Look at Slaggy looking up shit.
He don't care about us.
He's looking up.
I believe somebody listens to me.
Can't heard me say it.
I'm listening.
No, I wouldn't say it.
I like that psyche.
I was...
I'll turn my camera down.
You're good.
Turn your camera on.
You're a sweet angel.
Turn it off.
I don't even know where a little fucking piece of the bong is, I was trying to smoke weed but I need to hit her piece and Kim, oh there it is, sorry about that, here it is.
I'll knock that for like $2.00.
Summer, be quiet.
Yes, no.
Yes, no, yes, no.
I don't want to be black so that was good
My house came I know what you're doing up there. She's going into my room and trying to look for my savings
Yes, you
Well, say hi to strongman say out of my best friend summer boy
Oh, you're going to the banter for 17 minutes. That's not clear
Why didn't say you 18 minutes to piss
Yeah, you know Tommy when I'm pissed. I'm the same like stay the fuck out of my biz
That's my business you're talking about boy
I don't know. I would see summer. Oh, she actually has a slingshot. All right, look at this
Give it to me. Give it to me. Crack it down. It couldn't be jealous of this
They can look at that boy even as buttons or oh my lord
Breast. Breast. Breast.
Summer why do your breasts have like the Bible written on I'm like, I don't I never knew how to read and I'm not gonna read your tits
I
Don't have the bad laugh
I have a black little on my kids
Looking like you're not even caring about us. You just looking at something like paying attention to something else
Look at my hair I say
Look at my sexy hair
What do you want sir? You're gonna say hi to everybody? You want my food, huh?
Go you want my food?
You ain't gettin' it fucker
You gonna say hi?
Yeah, I know
You're so bad. Good job
Why did I get them then I just take a hit of crack
What I just did sucky I did man. Sorry about that guys. I think I'm my own crack now
I'm summer I got the Bible tattooed on my asshole. No, I have the black I have the black widow tattooed on my
Okay, fair enough that I thought that's I thought you had the fucking Bible first that's it on your nipples
No, I like summer actually I have a black little tattoo on my toe. I'm broke and trolled Kim
What are you doing my TV? Yeah? No
Get out get out watch that is down
I'm not gonna play it. I'll meet myself first. He ever named his name is sir
Our family the guy from fucking dexter or not dexter the guy from Lincoln Park. She fucking loves it
Chester not dexter
What about psych you don't love him look at his hair
Okay, I
Mean I'm not saying I'm gay, but if I was I'd be like at least this guy has nice fucking hair
Look at it real what it's like get on camera real quick
Look at him came
Back up look at her hair back up psych. Let her see your hair. What do you want?
You look good, so you look handsome brother you look handsome out here gorgeous person
If I was on family pewed and the question was like, what would you do with that hair? I'm like, I'll fuck it
but it's family feud summer
family feud
it's a funny show
remember family matters
I do
it's a rare condition
this day and age
to read any good news
newspaper
love and tradition
a grand design
Some whores say it's even harder to find.
Sucky, there must be some magic glue inside this tattoo.
Because all I see, a tower of glee.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Thank you. So I love you, man, but let me do that. I know it's gay that I just sang that but to me it means a lot to me
I love fucking family matters and it's saying that song. That's that's why it's like
Yeah, I fucking love him because he fucking cares about us. He cares about his fucking followers
Summer you got any cheese
No
I know you do summer. I know you do baby. Oh she left. Bye. Sorry about that psych
Let me get a beer one last beer. I'll drink with second and I'll leave. I know I'm annoying you psyche, but look
Last full beer and I'll crack it. I'll crack it right now
Hear that
What it's on like
Okay, I'm give me a minute sucks about the end it or you don't got to end it, but I'm gonna end it psych
It's such a pleasure
No, fuck you. Don't say good night yet. Are you banning me right now? You're banned. He's banning me. I think it is banning me. Hello?
It's a pleasure to be on your panel site. It really is. I know I'm joking, but it's a pleasure big dog and your hair
Looking handsome big dog. You're looking like fucking um
What's that guy?
Kenny Springfield. I wish I had Jesse's
I never find a woman like that.
I wish that I had suckies.
Turn it off when I'm talking to my friend.
Turn it off!
It is, Joe. Joe, it is.
Now what I'm saying goodbye, Suggie.
I'll end it. I'll end it, brother.
I love you, man. Sorry she was fucking playing shit.
I wasn't playing nothing.
I was literally-
Thank you, Suggie.
TV was giving me instructions.
Sorry about her, man. Sorry about her.
His TV was giving me instructions for captions.
Sorry about her, bud. Sorry about this.
We could end on a good note and camera with the sorry about that psyche you always be a friend to me you always be a brother to me psyche and as long as you keep shampooing your hair like the way you are you'll always be Jesse's care I wish that I just see so.
What's this? This is new you just made it. Who's that? Yeah
That's sick, man. Look into her eyes, buddy. Fuck stop man. I'm getting fucking hypnotized shit
Holy fuck. Okay. Well, I mean the page is not here so I can't really show the page video, but it was a beautiful video
I'll show it later of what a song
Yeah, oh the one with Alex. Yeah. Yeah, that was good here. I made a video to it
That was pretty good see the video. I saw it. Was it a nice? Yeah, it was pretty good
You know the two of them together into your fantasy creature
Well, that's me. I'm there
I'm cheap at hiding in the bushes like making fall
Yeah, oh that was you watching them. Yeah, that was me
That was you from the future you went back to see your mom and dad. Okay, I get it
I wrote that into the script, especially right here, here we have summer, here we have summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer, summer,
I
So what's everybody up to today? I went out for a little bit came back
Yeah, it didn't really do much
I had enough bent this morning and then came back and crashed for a minute
the
other came in the
Okay, this one's called the alien tarot. They're all kind of covered in tarot. Then I have the monsters
Monsters, that'll be cool monsters. I got the rainbow tarot. There's a rainbow tarot, and then there's the
It's called the a pause pause tarot. It's a cat tarot
And it's like 20 bucks for like five decks. 20 bucks for a five deck. Oh, that's sick. Yeah
Four bucks a deck. That's great. They suck if you just throw them out
You welcome Marcy
Oh you live like a fucking king
Got to live it up while I can you know. Hey, man. How much time left? I don't know how long how long life lasts, right?
We've got about 25 years. Enjoy it. I
Don't even know that 25. I thought I'd look to 30. Gay people live like usually less than regular people, you know
We say it's in first people say it after my coffee, but here we go
That's the devil
This is like this is like this is like home improvement because this is like Wilson's wife. Hi. Hi neighbor. She's peeking over the fence
I like that so
This is a
Oh delicious, how are we doing guys and I'm having a great couple days. It's a weekend
the
Yeah, you guys go on great. Yeah, I was I was I'd like to listen to him
I was really cool. I don't I don't know her but it was called it
I just wonder how she like who like who like told her about the show because it's like I know she knew about it
But it's just like everybody in this everybody knows about you psyche
You're YouTube famous baby. I know I know that I know she knew about me a couple months ago
I've heard about it for months, but it's just came because I saw her this morning on
I don't know, Kate's, she was at Kate's channel for a little bit, and I was like, oh my gosh.
And I've always wanted to talk to her, but yeah, I guess she didn't get along with Surya Diamond.
Because I thought if Surya Diamond was talking about Alex one day, and she's like, oh, you know, Alex is a porn star, did this, and that's it.
I was like, Alex is a porn star? I was like, and I was like, okay, porn star for a little bit, and she explained.
She explained it was a female Alex. So that's what happened.
Yeah, she's been around for a while, I guess.
She really reminds me of Omarosa. She got the BGM. Have you heard of BGM?
Yeah, but pretty. Black girl magic. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, she's in school. I don't know her like I said, but
she has like a vibe of like someone that works with the white guy.
That was a good, that was some good vibes.
Yeah. Yeah, it's good to get new people up here.
So I'm getting these new, I'm getting the Jeffrey Dahmarn glasses tomorrow. These are going back
get your jeffrey digger you got a jeffrey dover that's it well it's by
focus these are just there's rears that it's rears oh for like reading books
yeah like just for like 25 years and now I take my vision so I'm not
Who is that piece? Yeah, I like the season and the season. Yeah, the season fries are great. Yeah, it's delicious
Put some ranch on it, it's even better I
Don't eat a lot of salad dressing like I usually like I try not to eat a whole lot
I'll eat a little bit of salad use a little bit, but I don't eat a lot of salad dressing
I feel like if still like a steak if the steak's good you don't have to put a one-sauce on it
But a salad's really good. You don't necessarily have to put
Just not
I have a photo shoot Thursday, so I gotta tighten it up a little bit. Oh, yeah. Yeah, you gotta split it out there
Yeah, so that's what I'm doing
And then the protein
greens and water
Fucking boring water. Yeah, but the pictures will look good. So that's all that matters
Okay, I'm a little bit and streamed is like psyches, huh like MLI by just you just like me. Oh fuck yourself, Joe
Kick off the show
There's actually some guy named Fred Alastair if I mentioned Emma any kind of day or night
Anytime me I mentioned her name. He's there. He's always in the chat. He's here right now. He's gonna probably mention
He's always says I'm chilly
I remember when we very first met like you guys having a fallout or something and
But I remember the name but oh, she is no I don't really care sounds
You don't like me Joe you never have to be here again. Bye. Oh
At least you know you always got one of your it's probably is Emma is you bitch? I know
I don't know what to say.
Okay, we're all good guys, okay, let's see.
Hi, Marcy, hi, Ninja with the pencil.
I'm sorry if I missed anybody's comment,
I was very unwrapped within that last conversation.
I almost like, I can't besides it.
And uh-
No, good, yes, we're having a good conversation.
He clipped and shared it, Emma's Discord.
Well, good, she'll finally like,
you're not allowed to say my name or she'll get mad at you.
You're in trouble. Hopefully get kicked out of there. Okay. Yeah, he'll just refuse to read any more messages
because he was like, I'm gonna kick you out of the discord if you say his name again, so.
You peeing? What's going on? No, I'm done. I'm done. I'm done.
You don't have to prove it, Summer, we believe you would.
I would say it on the internet, you got to be careful.
I don't believe it.
That was being fucking psychic, yeah.
Yeah, I could hear it now.
Like, no, no, I was just stepping a pop can out.
It's all over Discord now.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
Discord is known for being
I don't go in discord
I just don't I did I had a discord and I had people come in a long time ago, and I was like, yeah
No, I'm you motherfuckers aren't having me crazy
Well, they can only come if you let them right it's all about it fight isn't it? Well, yeah, I just
I mean, I have a discord like if people private message me and shit like that, I guess but like yeah, I don't so do
I don't do anybody's groups. I don't do that
My panel panel versus enough cake out for me. I got enough shit. I don't yeah, no
Yeah, I'm too busy like
You don't talk and you're not you're not talking to us and like I got a fucking life
This is an attainment of a burger when I'm busy. I'm not gonna talk to anybody
Plus I don't like typing. I'm like my nails and just I just don't like typing so
I like just being able to jump on a panel and talk about shit. Yeah, I didn't know
Why don't you run a stream? I don't have time to run a stream. That's why I appreciate you guys
Thank you, I really wanted to get that all my jazz. Thank you, brother
Doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-doos-do
Man, I'm a really good guest panelist over here.
Really bringing up the writings with this kind of voice.
Joe, get off the fucking internet, dude.
Your voice sounds like trash, bro.
What the fuck are you doing?
You suck.
Why am I listening to this?
I hate myself.
See ya.
He comes in, he doesn't drive by, and he out.
I said, Joey, did you better than you do?
I'm dumb.
I don't think random guy cares for me, and that's okay, but I think he's quite funny,
actually.
the
Sank me and psyche was laying in a bed and just drowned together and we just played together. I
Love you psyche. I always will brother
No matter what no matter what psyche is like a fucking
He's like a fucking lover to me. What do you want to tell you guys? I
Gotta tell you the truth man
We already know Joe you confess this many times
I
Didn't have no content as far as my life
these gay guys didn't even notice summer turned the camera on they're all so busy jerking themselves off
they didn't even notice a sexy woman you losers losers she's my team my team making it all hang out
Remember when Kim comes back act like I was telling like a lie like Joe said. He loved you Kim like that whole time
Yeah, she took all your money and left. Yeah
Me be like you cheated on Joe and I'm like, yeah, you did I'll be whatever you guys say I'll just agree with
She left you for a woman.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
First of all, hey, psyche.
Who's there?
I'm real light.
We'll fucking try.
Hey, gorgeous.
How are you doing, beautiful?
I'm doing fine.
Hi, baby.
Guys, I don't read any vibes.
You piece of shit.
Hold on.
Who is this person?
That's Joe.
It's like Reddit monkey eyes.
Who the hell is this psyche? Who the fuck is this man?
If he ever ever talks about somewhere like that again, I'll find him and I'll kill him
Joe
Can't read people's live. He's done it like every fucking time on the show. Stop it. You understand threatening. It's like
I
You know, I love me some summer. So I really can't disagree
I don't know who's trying to go away, but I'm saying if anybody can get the smoke if they can I talk about my summertime fun
period
Today when I was doing both of us up here, I love you summer
Love you Gord just how you been. Oh
girl
Lord, I've been sitting on going on into these motherfucking tick-tock streets and oh sweet baby giblets
That you know
I'm not big I do a lot of like post all my activism shit over there, but I don't really do anything over there
Girl look, okay
So we had a live the other night and it was about the Cory whatever the fuck his name is
I, I really don't know who the person is. All I know is that he was in Five Nights at Freddy, and he was like a cab driver, and whenever I watched it with my kids, my kids knew who this motherfucker was.
I don't, right? And I guess, um...
You know, we were talking about
It was pretty much something along with misogyny and how men pretty much don't hold men accountable
But they'll sit there and protect men even if it means, you know, it's pretty much against their own interest
If they're sitting there and talking about you know making jokes about as saying a woman or something like that
And then these people sit there and protect them, but then, you know, we'll sit there and try to be all up in arms whenever
Somebody else that you feel don't have status want to sit there and make the same type of comment
Supposedly it's wrong this that and a third but whenever somebody says it like that that is just a bit more wider well-known and
Somebody that has some form of status usually in a form of fiat currency
Everybody all of a sudden forget how to fucking speak and they get real motherfucking quiet
And they're right baby. So we were talking about that and oh Lord just
the level of Corey's supporters that came in that were sitting there and trying to excuse all this shit and
Initially what we were saying is that the accusation that the girlfriend or the ex-girlfriend or whoever the fuck the bitch is
And when I say that I don't mean to respectfully I just mean I can't remember this woman name
Whenever it comes to the accusation the accusation it was that you know, he was verbally abusive. He was emotionally
Well, thank you random guy, thank you, I'm cheered up
Thank you.
Sorry Styles wife.
Go ahead.
You're good. You're good.
I'm happy y'all watching the chat because I couldn't even see it on the phone.
His phone is raggedy.
Anywho.
You know.
Pretty much they were sitting there talking about oh, he didn't say her and I'm saying you're like
Did anybody say anything about it saying what what it was is that there was a video clip of him
He was saying that while she was sleeping did something to her and
Then she starts laughing everybody's like oh, she's laughing boy. I can't tell that was a nervous laugh
She was uncomfortable as fucking she was on camera. So she was trying to say face
Like if y'all don't know what the fuck that looked like that just tells me I ain't been around pussy
I mean like bro like women will sit there and nervous
Yeah, exactly. And then they're like, Oh, well, she's lying. How is she lying when literally she showed exactly what the fuck she was talking about in the fucking video.
When I sit there and tell you all these people sat there and got they panties and I twist and it was clenching they pearls, but here was the worst part of it for me.
This live was supposed to be 18 and over when I sit there and tell you there were so many 13 year olds in here
And I'm like, dude
No, no, no, honey, there there is it depends on where the fuck you go and what would kind of shit
Because over there in my sector, baby ain't not one kid in that motherfucker
891 because all I do is just over. That's why I never fuck with a tiktok
But if you did it to me should I
Yes
You're gonna have to send Excel your your tiktok name so I can sit there and find you and shit say less I got you
Um, we have conversation with adults because baby look kids don't have the intellect to really try to have a debate
And when I say kids I am referring to ones that are over the age of 18 that are just fucking dumb
I said what the fuck I said
um, I
Still refer to them kids because if you're mentally a child
And then you sat there and stop growing due to whatever fucking trauma whenever you're trying to communicate
You're not gonna be but have skill set that you need so
Like but when I'm in this live, there was like 13 to 16 year olds and I mean we had to boot so many people
It this was the first time I had to literally boot over a thousand people because they were on page
That shit was fucking wild to me. Now mine. This is the same type of live where we've actually had
conversations on
You know male misogyny
you know, we we've had conversations on
deep-receded rooted topics and
Once again, nobody that's under the age comes in there all of a sudden we sit there talking about this quarry person
They feel like they have to come out and supposed to be his army that that should be weird to me. It's cultish, but I
Love your boobs I
Love your boobs
Mine aren't as nice as yours
I mean
He would we will bet to different but his opinion isn't necessary in this I like yours though
Well, thank you
Now's wife has nice moves I've seen
No, yeah, she's gorgeous
Very very very beautiful. That's what I'll do respect by the way, and now you're okay. Thank you. I mean
I am I am I'm look I'm worse about my feet though
Or is as fast
I will see I'm a I'm a size 5. I'm a size 6. I know that's why I'm not
showing them on the internet. Okay I am not showing them on beyond-phrase web
interwebs.
I I have an issue with my feet even though hubby doesn't think there's anything wrong with them kids
So I know what regular feet versus feet that have been in toe shoes for years look like I don't have any bunions or anything like that
It's just I feel like
Because I've had to wear toe shoes for so long like other people can see that
Even if they can't it's just like something they can't I can't get back in my room
So, everything on me is small, pretty, but see, that's not saying a lot.
It is, because it's better than the opposite.
Hello.
Got even giggling. Did I make it giggle? No, no, somebody says spooky. So
I said spooky because once again ex health bone is shitty, but that's a
Hey spunky gorgeous. How you doing?
What's going on duck
Oh, not much. We just got home from dinner.
Oh, nice. Where'd you guys go?
Very nice oceanfront restaurants where I took Justin out for a celebration for his new job.
Sweet, he got it. Oh, good.
Congrats!
Even though he was a dick yesterday. Tell him I said congratulations. Yeah, I heard he was a huge dick to you
I know I want to let you know someone I told him off about that
What he did and I was like, what the fuck is your problem? I think he was talking about BLM. I
Don't care about the BLM stuff. It's the Brianna stuff. He was trying to go and I'm like yeah, we're not doing that
Yeah
So
They always come back
That's what psyche says
Yeah, it's been a really funny
Yeah
Everybody's like, but didn't did she sponsor the channel? It was like yeah, she didn't want to send the stupid shot
I didn't sponsor the stupidity
Okay, sorry
Sorry, you had a good night. I'm glad you guys had a dinner and I'm glad he got a new job. So hopefully he'll start you know
It'll make a break
I
Have to have to agree unanimously. I was just saying is his boss black. Oh, we'll find out
Hey, you know what now you have a black man or a black woman that's writing your paycheck she better be nice
But I can't see him being married to somebody like her and being racist.
I think that he's just probably was trolling me a little bit and it just
was not he's not he's not he's just black women.
Yeah, he was black women.
He's trolling.
He just acts like an asshole on the Internet.
Well, I don't think it was necessarily him like he's a racist
I wouldn't put up in that box, but I just he was trolling and it was just not the thing
Because we heard your fucking voice
Whether you like it or not you were here tonight
Mongos in you're out
Hey, just like I sat there and said look they always come back. I'm never coming back. Yeah, they'll be here tomorrow at four
Yeah, he found that would probably irritate me and he told me so I worried about it. It's all great
I mean
He's really good at picking out someone's weak it says like what bothers them and then and then harp in on it
I would love him to sit there and try to pick out what bothers me
Because baby my level I don't give a fuck be a little too strong that sometimes even
You heard him. He's in the kitchen. He's out. Oh, I will. Oh, that's okay. You have to find something that I give a fuck about first and look, we gonna have to find that shit together.
Yeah. And usually it wouldn't like bother me that much, but it's just because we have court Monday and it's just like, you know, it was just kind of fresh again, I guess you could say so I was just like, you know what, fuck you, I'm not doing this with you today, buddy.
Like I said, I don't see him being a racist or anything like that. I think he was just trolling
He found something that was like this bitch. Let me see if I can shut her up
Yeah, whatever he says is a scab. He loves to pick at it. He loves it
He's in the races box for a week so he gets to see how races get treated
Thank you
It's about pages. I could be wrong though. Wait, wait, wait, hold on. If I was trying to get a bj, hold on
Well, no, I sat there and I offered that as a as a contingency offering point and I'm waiting for his response to Justin
No, I tried that on Justin last night. He shot me down and I just went to bed
Yeah, we heard yeah, yeah, I told I told to kick you out of the bed. Oh
Like literally like like literally just kick your ass off the bed
And then you say like not in front of the dog the dogs not the dog doesn't care
She can't get down the bed when she's the one that offered to be right
No, I heard you said no
No, yes, he said he said no. Oh, no, he's he told me that you said no you were too drunk
No, no, I absolutely came in drunk offered a BJ in the kitchen and he said not in front of the dog and I said I
Said all right. I'm going to bed then
Oh shit boy, what are you doing with the dog?
Probably a little Pomeranian to Justin's house this weekend
All I'm saying is I am so happy that my dogs are in their kennels and they're sleeping they give not one fuck about
Like normal people do just like kick him out of the room
Who's that one?
That's Malibu.
Malibu.
She goes by Boo Boo.
She's a good girl.
She's my closest dog.
Does she smell good?
She does.
Like baby shampoo right now.
Oh nice.
Actually speaking of that y'all, I gotta go. I'm gonna go ahead and get the phone back to exile. It was good to go ahead and talk to you guys
Take
I'll do that
Mrs. X
Elijah
Yeah, she's really cool
It's gonna be jam panel right now. What's wrong man? You sound depressed
No, she's probably gonna get on TikTok. No, I'm high as shit, bro. Oh, that's what it's okay. I'll let another one up
Spunk you guys get dessert
They had like 12 things to choose from.
That's great.
I would have had the shits, but I totally eat that.
I've already given you the shits.
Yeah, blueberries go right through me.
Oh my god.
Right through me, right.
I'll let you know how it works on Justin.
Put some.
Take a pic.
Don't roast berries, baby, I mean, you know.
Don't roast berries, baby?
I never saw it.
Oh, see it. I know it's about. I just never saw it. Maybe see it. It's from it's a mere me a hero. Oh
That was like when I was still and I think that's when the Manson thing happened and he flew it
And I have some bomb ass
French onion soup
Onion soup. Yeah, never heard anyone say that about onion soup
French and soup done right is amazing, and then I had scallops some fresh sea scallops that were like
pan seared and like garlic and butter sauce
and then I have french fries and that's a lame side, but
That's what I wanted and just think yeah, Justin got a
crab cake
It was made as like a
Like a souffle
fancy that was good and then some pecan rice oh yeah and that type place I'm
kind of spinach yeah I took a nice place and he got something else too sweet
potato cream spinach and sweet potato I'm surprised you didn't want to go to
Denny's
yeah he did try to go to some like hole-in-the-wall like smoked pork place
on the way there and I was like no we're going to the nice place like we're
doing a nice dinner that's what I had tonight smoke or smoke for it what was
I
Good break up from this damn email
J1, what up, man?
Gawdy, when's the last time you had a woman?
What do you mean, when's the last time?
Like, what, do you have a girlfriend?
Of course.
You do?
Yes.
Who is she at?
We're not fucking like Arm and Arm, like you and him.
Oh.
She's a woman.
Yes.
This morning, last time you had a woman.
This is Gawdy.
Don't miss this. I mean miss Gotti
Yeah, you're reading cuz you remember you're gonna you said oh you said it's when I forget you the second
Give me your first reading with it, but you did give me the deck and so I'm gonna do it
Oh my god, 15th it's coming. Okay. Well you get a reading from this
Okay, there's a monsters. I just got this one. Oh, I like
Is it universal monsters or just once it looks like universals
It might be you know, I think it's like, you know, just like probably all over. I don't know
I don't think it might be enough. I'm not sure. Can I give it a good shuffle for someone using it?
So there's actually it's a good feel to these cards
They are probably like, you know a copy of like to all of these all of these five decks are the same size
They're all like three or four bucks and they're all like
But they look pretty good. Okay, so your car from here is going to be
Okay, okay, it is the eight of grips
Maybe the eight of cups eight of Crips. I have to check those do it eight of Crips. Oh, okay
They changed the names too. Let me look at the the Crips
Yep, the Crips, but let me see. Let's see. They have the four suits are the
Claws this is kind of hard castles
Crips and okay, I have to look it up in the thing you candles. Okay, so that's candles or wands. Okay, Crips are
No idea I have to look it up
Yeah, the eight of cups is you know, it's about you he has these eight cups and he's gonna go look for some more like
There's a lot of emotional fulfillment hold on
And that's a cuffs, but I'm not sure if you have to check
Somehow they changed the names of the cars. I didn't know that I got to find a morbid deck a
Morbid deck, okay, there's like well
Like what if we're kind of any morbid
He's playing contra. Hey, you're not at the drive-thru. It's okay
It appears that it's it appears that it's eight of pentacles so the eight of pentacles without that
So that would mean that you've been working really hard on something you're stacking up some
Some my results and you still have work to do you're in the middle of it
But it's like you're you're like really like have been
Perfecting your craft whatever craft that is there. I'm sure I know I know you do but I'm sure sure it's perfected
But yeah, you just don't working really hard it should the regular card is this guy right here
So he's always
He's just stacking up the pentacles right there and he's working on one. He has one finish at his feet, right?
And so it's like you're you're something in progress something good
And it's gonna really pay off for you because it's almost all done. It's almost all already. So okay, so I can pull a couple more
Well, look at another deck
The 80 until I learn these don't come with instruction manuals of course because they're like knock-off sticks, right?
And so they don't have the instruction manual probably can get along on the PDF
They have them on, if you go to, if you go to, what is it, Temu, they have on the Temu
page where they sell the deck to have a little link to a document with the, with the, stay
on it.
That kind of, yeah, it's a good, what is it called, like a French document file or something.
Okay.
You're the car from this rainbow deck is going to be whoo
King of Pensacles King of Pensacles, which is a very good thing the King of Pensacles is going to be
Someone that will be able to manifest manifest your dreams will be able to like not really have to like run around so
Because he makes everything come to him. He's very magnetic. Of course. He has the Queen and so that makes you probably the Queen
Are you gonna earn a sign? No, you're signing it. We were Leah
Okay, yeah, and what is his time?
He isn't at Aquarius Aquarius. Okay, so he's like an air sign. Okay, air and water. Yeah
Air and water. I think that's like waves. It makes waves
You know the air makes the waves over the water and it's like but I just make your waves, baby
There's the key is the city
Looks like Ziggie
Not him Viggy. Okay. I'm gonna take it that big God
Okay, they're back, okay, oh
There we go. We're back. I'll pull a couple more cards for a couple more cards
You were not crazy. How would you full-screen them?
I'm saying
It's right here speak to me boy
I'm suspecting
the
Hey, what my big lips looks like princess Leia up there. Come on. Okay. All right. Yep. Okay. Hey, how you doing gotty?
You guys
You got rid of summer
We can't we had to go nobody can be perverted here. Okay, all right
Smunkie put her makeup on that's good. That's a good one
You get laid
she's dead in their full
They fucked her on the tip
He was drinking so he's like okay. Let's do it before the date. Oh
You banged him before the date before the date. Oh fuck. Yeah, okay. All right
We got a we got a player in here. That's why he had the crab cakes
Yeah
Psyche, what's up? What are you doing?
What'd you say?
No, it's like it's like you're running around or something like yeah, because I'm doing taxes
No, I know it looked like you were doing like taxes or something. I don't know
Uh, Gadi, Justin says he found a crystal ball for $350 on eBay.
Should he buy it?
The original?
No.
Fuck that.
Mint condition.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
She said condition.
No way.
Fuck it.
I don't know what the hell you guys were talking about, how much he said.
You get 10 figures for that price, fuck that.
So one from the 80s, so one from the 80s doesn't matter man. It's not worth it
Spunky spunky is now conditioned and that's why she used that word
Conditioned
She's looking at her man
Condition the mind you can just in the mind with the shampoo and
Oh, yes. What does that mean? That means you're talking about shampoo. If the ass needs shampooing you just use the shampoos. Yeah, like bleaching her ass holes.
You got shampoo. Are we talking about bleaching my asshole? I thought we were doing another card. Yeah, we're doing another card. Thank you. This got awkward. Where's the card? Yeah.
I have I have cars. I mean, I have cars. This is a cat sex. You guys want a cat cat cars? Yeah
Yeah, this is for everybody
This is called the six of Cubs and this is like some rumminess in about your
Back to the past maybe just remembering some happier happy times not happier times. It's happy times
Maybe your childhood or something looks like a calming book
Yeah, it's like that. It's like the first feeling of first love. Well, it's a cat's dick. It's a cat's dick
It's like the cats reaching over to the neighbor's cat to be like, hey, yeah
What's it?
I
Look like the the the lower cat was reaching up to the other cat neighbor to be like hey, can I have some of the food too?
Okay, I don't know it looks like
No, you're saying no you can't okay anyway, okay, so that's who this deck
Don't waste the shot. Hold on. It's almost. Oh my god. It's almost eight o'clock guys. What does that mean?
What what's that mean, you know what that means you guys to go off. Oh, yeah leaving. Yeah, what do you mean?
You're not leaving. I said I was I told summer. I'd go into eight o'clock with the panels
Okay, I'll be back later tonight. You guys want to do more panels. I'll do another panel, but you're not leaving dude
It's eight. Well do it to 830. How about that?
They're cool because they even wants to come up. He's not in your chat
He does well, yeah
Is that okay? Yeah. Well, I guess so, but I would knock it
It was just a joke guys
Anyway, hey, do you wanna see how it tricks? Oh
Sponky got spunked
I
Maybe I think you like he's giving me some appetizers backstage. I'm sure I'm back
Yeah, we have some appetizer we have a stripper back there. I just want people to be comfortable everywhere. You know
Diggy have some back there. Okay. It's not like purgatory. It really is like a green room
with strippers and cold cuts
Hello, okay, I'm back here. Yeah. Are you gonna make those jokes again, Steve?
No, I didn't know that was offensive. She was laughing. I didn't know
She's smiling right now
She's laughing right now!
She's laughing!
She's not even my joke, not yours!
Come on!
I'm
She's sitting there with a seat full of you know, whatever, okay
I see a seat full of what that's not a joke people
Sonja full of laughter. Oh, those are nice. You don't get a good a good idea of what they look like
Yeah, they're good a pearly pink, right? Yeah, it's like a pearly pink
But they're like also cat eyes, so you can't really see them on the internet. Yeah, you know, I can see it
I it's nice. They're really cool. Those are sick
pretty yeah
No, hey, baby does Boyle tell you to dig those in
Oh, he doesn't back. He never likes when I get nails
Scratch the neck so fun. Those are way back. I know totally wasted and he always feels it means to like get them like shorter
No, no, no, you don't want them sure that's good. That's pretty look at my hand tattoos. You just rub them down the back
Look, I'm so reckless. My heart is not on my sleeve. It's on my pink. How do you got to use pictures? I got it
You're using which one?
You know what your avatar photo still sir. That's me. That's you. Yeah
You're running danger field. Oh my god
You're such an old beer like an old man. Oh, yeah, I told you I was 71
No, no, that man's like a hundred years old. No, he doesn't have any teeth. Come on man. I thought you guys
I was a num. I was a num. Oh, no, no
God he's 45
45 oh boy, what would I do? Got a will you ever tell how old you are?
No, you guys know how old I am maybe he's the head vampire million years old. I was born in 86
Okay, that's it. I make you exist. You're 30 years or 39 or something like that. You're 39. I'm 39
I just you are not 39 your voice is that of a 63 year old
Jesus really?
No, you're so bad. I'm just saying you have a distinguished voice. That's all. Oh, I'm sorry. Oh, maybe is this better for you. I
Think she looks more like 61 or 61
She likes a younger voice. Oh, sorry about that spunky, I'll try real harder to sound younger for you
Boy oh boy has that young boy voice you like
Oh come on God don't don't don't put anything on spanky like that I don't want to say that Spanky Spanky Spanky
I didn't know my face was so offensive shit
Ah fuck it. Oh, thank you so much. Thank you so much. I don't like I don't like you're that old man on the screen
It's scary
You have Dougie Doug up here all the time. What do you mean? You don't want an old man up here to scare people
No, that's not him. Oh, that's that's that's that's not a damn art. I thought that was Dan Marger's uncle
I didn't know it's like it does. Oh
The one who fucking right? Oh, no, I won't say it. Oh, no, no, no, no. I'll go beat him. I'll be though. Yeah
I don't know I'll go be though. He died right
I'm not sure but I think he
My friend right now is dating a guy who used to help produce jackass
Oh
Take it easy man
Dayton who?
Someone who used to help produce jackass like he was on some of the episodes and stuff. Oh
the idiot
We man, I think it was we man. He's not a midget
The door
He's actually really handsome.
He used to like Jackass.
Yeah, it's really cool.
He, Mongo loves him because he came over for dinner one time
and he was telling all these Jackass stories and stuff
and Mongo was just like, no way, dude.
Yeah, I love a good Jackass story.
Boyle, tell us the story.
No.
Tells the story jackass
He's there he's playing Nintendo. He doesn't want to talk to you. Oh, he's playing Mario Kart
The original
Contra I think he was playing contra and then he was playing Pac-Man now. He's going into Tetris. It looks like
Tetris King
Those are Tetris after you beat it. It turns into the space shuttle. What was that all about?
You thought you unlocked some kind of secret code. I've never beaten anything. So no too bad for you Boyle
Sorry Boyle, maybe tonight. He just had my cock only. Haha. Yeah, I figured
He has to pick his handicap level on Tetris, that's so rude with me on the panel
My love was always very hard. Oh, of course. Oh, this is some ghetto Tetris.
Hologram tarot cards. Oh, that's pretty. My eyes actually kind of look blue tonight.
Isn't that weird? They look nice. What are they, hazel? They're like a weird color. Look at them.
My hair is all they're like a grayish thing. They're like gray. I think gray is the color
But they're super rare to say you have gray eyes. They won't let me say I have gray eyes at the DMV
Glad you stye cleared up
Stye, yeah, you had a stye about a week or two ago. I did not have a stye. What the hell are you talking about?
Oh, I thought you had a stye
You're a mess
Yeah, depending on what I wear my eyes look great or green sometimes, but they're really not
I know
Yeah, I would like if I could say my eyes were hazel
But they're also not too because they're they're gray with yellow in them, which is like a weird combination
Amber is like amber. It's pretty pretty. Yeah, they're weird like one of them. Let me see it
See yellow in the middle. Oh retro guy said are you sponsoring the channel until 12 o'clock is time? Oh
Read that earlier that was way up on the thing. Okay. Let me see sponsoring the channel. Let me see. Oh, yeah, okay
Yeah, that's yeah, thank you. I don't know where he lives, but uh, okay
It's eight o'clock, so I'd say I'm still like probably like 1030. Yeah, so whatever. Yeah, whenever
Whenever I'll say until you guys you guys even empties out. Oh, so you're fine. Yeah, thank you
I think you random guy. Thank you for sponsoring the rest of the show
I'm gonna put your name in the banner if you'd like to have anything else put in the banner like a business
Website or anything. I don't know anything else in the banner. I put it for you. So panel is open
No, I can put doze notes.
Doze notes, not these.
Not only doze.
10.30.
PFC.
Subscribe to you.
I tried, Gotti.
It would have been funny.
Next time.
I'm going to pay them a doze note.
Let me see.
Got him.
That's my ringtone. It's like a, like it rings like the normal iPhone noise and then it says
D's nuts in the background and it says Goddy instead of Goddiem. I think of you, Goddy.
I'd love that to be one of your patients in that. That makes sense.
Now you know I don't remember my phone in the room. Oh shit, that'd be it gets the hypocritical so wouldn't you that boy?
Oh, it doesn't say Justin
There we go
There you go, random guy. Let me know if you want anything
That is the benefit you should call my phone Goddy and then
Do you have tunnel rat? What the hell? I do have tunnel rat. Yeah, the new the new tunnel rat
What is that dude? It's ten bucks on walmart.com right now
Yeah
A mole rat like
Okay, I also don't know mole rat is so what the fuck are we talking about many that's many mansons
It seems more that Billy the guy that seems to be on word sign
He sings like this on like oh, I've my house next door has been sold to you know
Yeah, but then if you've been trolled by I think so by many we were at tonight
I don't know why it made me think of this, but there were the serving sizes
You could either order a mountain or a molehill. Oh
You can you make a mountain out of the molehill? Can you do that?
That'd be interesting. I thought that was cute. It was like cute. Yeah, I just changed it
I just changed. Yeah, I'm taking some of the emojis. Okay guys. I can go like a better. Okay
Yeah, look, I'm at the school. I just changed people like a better
I love a little clip for her.
Hey, Ziggy, when my, I earned,
like I learned or earned one,
my membership for the first month,
will it alert me when it's over
so I can subscribe myself?
Yeah, it will say, yeah, it will say
like your membership's about to expire
and then you can renew it if you would like to.
I'm going to do that.
Thank you, sweetie.
Like Ziggy's still backstage in case you didn't see it.
Okay, well.
We put Ziggy in the corner.
Yeah, he's gonna stay in the corner for another three minutes until 8 15
Just because you know me twice you're not supposed to do that within two seconds
Supposed to like you know kind of like it out a little bit Ziggy
Why don't you do you're a bad boy? I kind of like it? Oh
Okay, well I'll keep them off the rest of the night then I'll then I'll be there really bad
God
Really, okay, okay, so oh yeah, okay, so the LOL will look like
I can put OMG too. I
Like it. I like the OMG. I like this one. It's lol
Guys, I got some good stuff coming for us. It says the panel sponsored until 10 30
Can you explain what's going on now? Because I thought it was just a guy. Who the fuck is that?
What what now who's the girl to be in care? I like to look at
That's a beautiful woman, that's why I was asking you about it.
That's good.
Stop, Goddy, Goddy.
Stop doing that.
What's wrong with that?
I don't know who these people are.
It's a random stranger.
It's nobody.
But what if it's, I mean, it's like, what if it's a person, like, what if it's Alexander's?
It's nobody we know.
Trust me.
It's nobody we know here.
Nobody on YouTube. I'll take it down. Take it down. Can I show you something funny guys?
I did one of those things on the internet that was like, let me draw your soulmate.
And I'm gonna put it as my avatar here. Look, does this look like boil?
Hold on. Yes. Oh, wait, wait, let me, let me turn my camera off.
Kind of no, I don't see it. It looks like it looks like it looks like the guy Edward Norton looks like a gay Edward Norton
Yeah, okay Edward Norton. Actually, you know, it looks like Epstein a younger Epstein. Oh my god
Yeah, hopefully. Oh, yeah, it is okay. Is that him?
No fishes of Epstein. It's way back in the day
For the island. I think it looks like Boyle back in the day. You've never seen him
I've seen Boyle Boyle when he was like 30. He was hot with hair. No, I never saw this. Oh my god
I saw the pictures and I was like, I've got the discount Boyle version. I think he's always looked the same
No, no, you should see him back in the day. Justin send me that picture. I'm gonna send it my fit
Go find it send me the hot hot boil version
I know you said it to me, but I don't know where it's at
You guys got to see what boy you stole a bike got it you're gonna die
I'm gonna faint I'm gonna faint you are gonna faint
You're he said he's gonna you're gonna lube your tube
That's me that's that's like 20 something year old spunky I thought that was doors day. Holy shit
It's like put on the big screen for a second. Let me guess. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Wow, so innocent
Baby, thank you. There he is. Welcome back. Hi, Ziggy
Told you I'd be in back. Ziggy tell me I still look beautiful
He's mad mad man. Oh, no, I didn't even know I was up here. What the hell psyche keep you doing this to me
It's 20 it's been 20 minutes. We've been waiting for you. Where have you been 20 minutes? That was 20 minutes
Listen, he got really mad when I said I kind of liked you acting up
He said he was in the banyou for the night and I said just just kidding
Yeah, oh
Somebody a really good picture. I forgot who it was somebody said sponk you got a the sexiest voice they ever heard
That was me as I said that I said wasn't you? Yeah, and then he bans me. Yeah
Somebody said that
All right, thanks. Oh
Say she called your baby. Yeah. Oh no, I just hiccuped. Oh my god
Here it is the beginning of the end of the night at the brown bag. Yeah, but no, no, I won't throw up. I never
Fuck I had three martinis at dinner and I'm on my second white clawed apparently. I'm gone
What did you eat it? What did you eat at dinner? French onion soup?
Some amazing bread, some scallops, sea scallops from where were they from in the region, sea scallops, and some french fries.
And blueberry cobbler.
The french fries we could have laid off.
That blueberry cobbler would have been great.
Well I only had like a few, you know, Justin really had the rest.
I got some ice cream.
Ice cream.
Ice cream?
Yeah, it's some ice cream kind what what's the flavor chocolate swirl and it has these little chocolate cups in it
Like that. Oh, yeah
with the
Yeah, got it fancy shmancy shit. I came and enjoyed it for my phone because I
Don't have it on my iPad and I don't know how to get it to my iPad because I'm messaging turn on
I will hurry up. I'm doing I'm doing it. You gotta see boy. Oh, you're gonna die like you're gonna you're gonna die
He was so
That's fucked up he's there and you're saying he was
Stop
Those niggie who's that you're showing who who's that picture now? Oh
That and oh me. Yeah, you oh
No, that's me. Oh
It's okay
Yeah
What the hell? Why did you do that?
I thought it was Doc. I thought it was Doc through the crow. I thought it was Doc through the crow or something.
That's the crow. It is the crow.
No, it's me.
Yes.
Brand movie.
I love it.
Dude, that's actually, whenever I did stage work, I fucking actually took that from the crow.
Yeah, that smile thing. Yeah.
It's creepy
What the crow I never saw the crow I never saw the movie you never watch the car never
And it came out of the night
Yeah, we see you still no wait, let's let's second Spongebob
Second Spongebob
Holy shit
Isn't that crazy? Oh, wow. He looks like one of those greasy. I well, I mean, I can't really
Yes, one of those two afro things going on wait look it kind of looks like it, right?
Yeah, can you expand spunky psyche? What are you doing? Are you playing a game or something?
You want him to look like that?
Look at him with hair
Does he not have hair
He's doing the you know what
The Patriot the Patriot
Oh
Whatever happened to those guys with the suspenders, they're not around anymore
The big in Europe still
No, I don't believe in the back
I just took it it's gone
I didn't I'll rewind the stream. Hold on. I can get it from there. Okay
I'm right here. I have a pretty story to tell you guys. Okay. Let me get off my second
There it is off. Okay. Yeah, I got it. I love that skull face right there, dude
The stage the year is like 1994 Jesus. Yeah, I was five
I was what I was nine. I was nine years old. No, I was nice. You're right. I was nice
So I was in yeah, 85 to 90. Yeah, I was in like third or fourth grade at the time and
My parents were not the greatest parents and we were constantly moving and moving and moving and we'd finally found some place that they had like
Promised us that we were gonna stay here for a while, which they did they did fall through they they did go through on the promise
But we moved in and we were in Greenfield, Indiana. Have you guys ever heard of that place? Yeah, of course
Do you have okay?
Heard of it. I've never been there
Yeah, I will even tell you the address if you'd like to Google it. No, this is the first
We were renting so there's nothing you can find me on but we lived at
579 North 150 West
Greenfield, Indiana 46140
First address I ever memorized it was great, but um, yeah, we moved in
and it was a we lived on probably an acre but like around us there was just like complete
cornfields nothing middle of nowhere great area beautiful my dad is the most racist
effort you could ever meet in your life okay i mean like just just a jerk he was really a jerk
i don't have many great things to say about him he's he's passed now but we moved in
And it was really cute, it was such a small town,
a literal welcome wagon came around.
Like it was a truck with like an ox wagon,
like that was pulled around and came through
and visited us and brought my mom like cookies
and they invited her to the knitting group
and it was the craziest thing I'd ever seen in my life.
The sun went down and
About six pickup trucks pulled up came up with a full of I know exactly where she's going with this
You know, you know where this is going, right? So I because I was born in West Virginia. So
uh-huh
So, um, I'm not sure I can say all this sticky stuff. I say something to tell me
I'm gonna try to censor it as much as I can, but so I'm nine years old, okay, and
All these guys showed up it was dark and they wanted to hang out with my dad
They invited him out and they all like we're sitting on there
They made like a little circle in my front yard with their trucks
And they're out there cracking their like course lights or whatever the fuck they're drinking
and I was
curious, so I'm kind of like listening all of our windows are up in the house because it's the summertime and like
That's just what you do. You don't run the AC because you're saving the screens. Yeah. Yeah, so I'm listening underneath the
Living room window and all of a sudden I hear my dad say
The letter K three times. I'm not gonna fucking join you
Bad f-word like the the word we don't use on this panel
Dressing up like a bunch of pansies and dancing around a fire together
I hate n words the much as the next person
But you guys are really the gayest ones I've ever met in my life if you want to hang out and touch each other's penises and
Hey, I'm like use that as an excuse to really highly doubt that he said that to them
He did
Shots were fired shots were my mom
My mom came out and like was like what is going on?
You know it was there was just cuss words and all this craziness and like long story short they left
but my dad was someone that
Was running from he had like been exiled from the mafia in Chicago and like we were like hiding and like
moving every three months in constant places and
He was a plumber and he would open up these fake like my dad was also literate
So my mom ran all the business, but he would basically like open these businesses and like
Duck tape and like spit together all these jobs and then as soon as things started falling apart
We were getting in trouble like we'd run up and leave, but he would take all the money and let go
it was a terrible childhood and
But yeah, he like told off the triple K and like left and I was kind of like
I don't know in a way. He didn't do it in the right way, but it's kind of proud of him. I was like, that's really
Like, good. Good.
He hates ends and he hates K's.
Yes, he hates that.
And he thinks anyone who's getting together and like, you know, circle jerking around the fire pit
and mutual hatred is still gay and he was done with it.
So, yeah.
He hates gay too. Okay.
So he hates everybody basically.
Okay. What? Scotty, sorry.
He hates everyone equally. That's good.
Yeah, he really does.
He is someone who was, like,
didn't want anything to fucking do with anyone.
It was crazy.
I'm so surprised that I turned out as normal as I did,
being raised with so much chaos and hatred and bullshit.
Like, I can't believe I turned out where I wanted to, like,
help people and, like, do nice things and...
That's what I think.
You can't judge your parents for that.
It was a different time, you know what I mean?
Yeah. You don't know what he went through.
You don't have no idea what he didn't tell you.
You know, there's probably many things that you don't even know about your dad.
I'm sure, and I'm sure he got like hurt and stuff too.
And I get it, I get it, I do.
But I try constantly to get it.
But I think I never will you could you could know somebody that says that shit about people
24-7 for years, but you have no idea how they really are in real life because they might be doing things that you have no idea what they're doing
My dad didn't really do much of anything good. I mean I watched him for a long time. He lived until I was 24
I didn't really see anything to be proud of he did something good right there. Maybe did some secretly
Yeah
Maybe he was taking care of like a family in Africa
Signed up for Facebook and immediately it was like bombarded with like his prior family he had
He was married like numerous times and his other family
Yeah, but wait, wait, what was his name? What's his name like mark?
You know Thompson, you know, that's like a frequent name. No, I'm gonna tell you his name was Vince
But like even at that like my my birth name is not the name that I have right now like he had to buy
Identity from the Hells Angels and when I became a god you went from KKK to Hells Angels
But I was like shitting my pants when I sat for my boards and applied for my license and said like my name is such-and-such
Stephanie such-and-such here's my search security number
I knew that was not what I came into the world with, so I was like losing my mind that I
wouldn't be able to create a life with everything I had worked hard for because my dad had fucked
me up.
I don't know what happened, somehow went through.
Is your last name Defazio?
It is, how'd you know?
had a good feeling but at the same time I had already been married twice when I
went in and did that so I don't know if like things crossed wires and it just
like her boy her boyfriend's ready to go into the car and fucking leave right
Oh my god, what did I what did I just do? I
Like when I when I date somebody and I really like them and I feel like I'm falling in love with them
I like tell them all the bullshit, and then I'm like, hey, do you still want to stick around you love me? Oh
My god, do I love boy? Oh, well, it's yeah
Well, I love you. There you go
see that was easy yeah that's it on stormfront right now boy don't stay back don't stay back
he did not say it back he never does and he said to tell ziggy that he's on stormfront right now
whatever the fuck that means that's how we get power he doesn't say i don't even know what stormfront
is what kind of gay shit are you trying to have me communicate right now it's the radical website
I'm just teasing you by the way.
What's up with that Athens? What up, man? Yo, hey guys, how's everybody doing?
I like this guy man. He's okay
You're okay, too. Yeah, man
He voted for Trump, you know how funny you wrote you know, I wrote that though, right?
He's like I voted for Trump over Biden in the primaries
No, no, no, no, it's like he this guy loves
Bants for sure
Mm-hmm
Yeah, he calls him Bansie pants
I don't think anybody do
I know you don't want to talk politics, but just a random question
What do you guys think is gonna happen after Trump like post Trump?
Like the next little guys thing without him
Do you think the MAGA moves to Vance or you think no elon's gonna be up next tea?
No, it's gonna be elon's like whatever elon can't run. He's a fucking foreigner
But whatever his little pawn is he will you think he's gonna try to get somebody put money behind him. Yeah, absolutely
No, hopefully it's somebody normal
There's nothing there. That's not that doesn't exist. There's nothing. I think we should put Jara Wigan up for
Me and I told you I have a bunch of back. You know story like stuff. You want to be the president spots
I mean, let me hear you
You don't you don't want Jara Wigan up there
Uh, no, I kind of want to be the president despite drawing in that makes Boyle the first lady
Oh, that doesn't sound like a typical woman. Of course you would this fight
I don't think his ego could handle it
Oh my god, dude, he'd be okay. My my my I still have my
Kingdom, you know fucking lose his mind. He'd eat absolutely leave me
Look at he's sighing right now really hard. Oh my god. He should have heard it
Yeah, we ran into a congressman who at dinner we did somebody that
and so close that he ran into me and was like oh oh spunky i'm sorry i ran into you like
you're gonna try to bribe them like fuck it with me you're way what you're gonna try to bribe them
no no i'm so close with him like i don't need to bribe him how close how close that i see all of
It's not
Sanchez
Yeah
Cackling witch
They can do it like on spot you and your little dog, dude. I do that during sex
Dude, no do what he do do what he just said see in your little dog to do it
Yeah, but it's so funny that I'm like such a fucker and like you guys know the real me, so I
Don't I don't know you what no no no
I mean like you have my personality of like the real me of like hello
So real you like a chill bitch and like I such like a prestigious job and
the shit that I do it's so hilarious like
That I have such a professional side of me and then just such a fucker side of me like
Uh, dude, I grew up in the same way, man.
Everything that you were talking about, not everything.
I wasn't in the, you know, realm.
Yeah.
By the way, Ziggy, they did catch up to him.
They did catch up to him.
When I came home from high school at about 16 or 17,
I rolled up to the FBI raiding my house.
And I literally, it was a dead end street.
I literally saw what was happening.
I knew what was going on.
I just backed up and left and never came back.
Yeah, I'd already dealt with foster care and stuff and I was like not doing it again
I had a 21 year old boyfriend, and I was like hey, you're gonna rent us an apartment and
He was talking about like the Hell's Angels
over in West Virginia was
Fucking the Pagans and then it was fucking the triple K, you know that kind of stuff when I was growing up
Can you fuckers like appreciate what I've done for myself like yeah, we're sure you sure yeah
I feel real proud of myself. I may not be like the perfect person, I've made a bunch of mistakes, but
I know I'm drunk and in my feels, but I'm like, dude, that's I'm pretty good for myself.
You know, haven't-
Where's Psyche, yo? What the hell is this?
Psyche just left. Psyche's like, I'm done with this.
He's out.
This therapy session, I'm done with this.
That happened the other night too, Psyche. You're just gone.
What?
Psyche, come back. Tell me you're proud of me. That's what I really wanted. You're my new daddy.
What do you say? I love a girl with daddy issues
And daddy issues and mommy issues. What do you say? No, what do you say?
Call me daddy while you be my mommy I love that
Me oh gringo
How do you play Paperboy?
No, I grew up the same way, man.
If you want to, look up a place where I grew up.
It was Arden, West Virginia.
And fucking
No, not Maine West West Virginia it was
We're talking about the football player from right from West Virginia
No, no, no, no, no where I grew up was Arden
Ardee in West Virginia
It's along the river and a lot of dead bodies
I thought you were talking about the Buffalo Bill that was from the town near you and no, no, no, no, no
Megatory
And you need to answer your question earlier. I'm 40. Yes. I've been married a bunch of times. I'm an idiot
I've never been married. I'm not in I've been an idiot, but I'm not
Justin buh buh buh. No, what do you say?
Don't do it. You want me to marry you? What am I an idiot? Yeah
No, it's easy, right whenever fucking dude. Can you put the phone up put the no put the
Put the speaker up next to him real quick. He can hear you. He's not
It's real easy whenever you're fucking your I
Gotta be light here where I'm gonna get kicked
When you're connecting and then fucking it's like yeah, you want to get married. Yeah, no fuck that
Hey boy, don't worry about spunky here. Dominer is about to turn over. Oh
She's been rode hard
She's a roadster
Gotty honestly, I know
Gotty you and I between you and I
You know you die for a woman like me. I don't think you can handle me honestly
Honestly, I don't think you handle a woman like me. I don't honestly. I'm gonna be for real
I don't think you could handle gotty to be honest
Oh, you were talking about your Italian stuff? Whoa?
That might be the audience I are cut from the same fucking clock. I got his number
He knows we've talked on the phone. How many people can handle me Spunk?
No, no, I wouldn't handle you but I'm grown enough that I wouldn't handle you
Is that the light way to say it?
No, she's basically she's basically saying I
Couldn't handle you. You know if I ask Boil to give me three months with you
Boyle would never do that
No way
Whatever I ask people do
Yes
Tell him I'll give him his I'll give him my GI Joe collection
Said you can have his GI Joe collection
He laughed
Dude, I do for real. I actually have a fucking GI Joe collection. I don't know why
They do
I haven't looked at them in forever, man. They're in storage. Pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew, pew
I'm not ever I'm never again going to say I'm a veteran because then people will be like proving
Who could be what?
Are you guys trading geodges right now?
Like at 40
I was watching a 1a or a video the other day and
the auditor was talking to the cop and he was like oh you served and the auditor was like yeah yeah
and then the cop was talking about officer safety because the veteran you know had a gun on his
side and he was like you know imagine I was you know overseas and I was like excuse me so soldier
safety can you move to the side please and I was left with so fucking hard because the cop has no
clue what the you know the veteran went through like at all you know and he's like he's like I don't
That's what the cop said to the, uh, to the guy, to the veteran, but it is
the veteran. Yeah. Yeah.
He made a good point
Man, I still I still have fucking like like I have small tics for me, but not nothing major
But like I'll still like wipe my fingerprints off my keypad
fucking from my door and like look under the
Yeah, it's weird sit like in the back of the room like when you walk into like a restaurant or something
You like sit with you. Oh, dude. I sit dude. I go and sit by myself. Yes
Do you look for exits and all that shit like I got no I mean you're no I don't look for it
I'm already self-aware of it. You know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Stupid stupid man and like everybody's like dude quit freaking out man
You're not I'm not freaking out though. Like I'm just like nope. I'm self-aware close friend of mine lost his
Extremity and
Yeah, it was good guy man, and he wrapped lunch and he is like like what you're talking about
He's hard-wired, you know, and I was like well you really look at exits and he's like three over there boom boom
He like threw it out really quick at me. Okay, and then it was like a movie scene
He's like the guy over there. I was like, what color hat did that guy? He's like red. I was like, holy shit
You're like fucking Jack Ryan right same. Yeah, my AR man my fucking one of my brothers man
Like fucking had my AR shifted a certain way
and fucking I came home it's moved and fucking I knew I know it's you and he
went God damn man you fucking know that fucking it was because it was shifted
left you know what I mean yeah fuck yeah
Fuck me up
He was in Felucia. He's in Felucia. It was in the
Zool, yeah, I was in the Marine. I was
Yeah, I'm gonna tell
Did look up that place though that you were talking about with all the last names that were the same that guy that was drafted by the bills
And I was doing research on yeah, I was looking at that
I told you I go down like a rabbit hole with some of that shit and yeah, man
Yeah, a lot of history man. It's interesting really interesting. Yeah. Yeah, that place is
pretty crazy the Nine N'Wah
province Nine N'Wah
I sent an email to the guy that has a YouTube channel. He's called the civil rights lawyer. He's got over a million subscribers
Yeah, I watch him all the time. Yeah. Oh cool. Yeah, cuz he's from West Virginia. That's that's what it was
Oh, yeah
He did it dude that civil rights guy he did a fucking video in a town that was
Where I was growing up
Fucking what was it called?
Fucking bill bill Billington Billington first out of trash at block
Yeah, I'm always there. What was it about?
The guy was just like the cop was just a fucking dick man to the to the people and fucking the civil rights
Guy was like man. I'm taking up on you know, he he took the case basically. Yep. Hell. Yeah
Hell, yeah. Yeah, he's good. I like the way he breaks down the videos like from a psychological point of view and shit
Yeah
I met him actually. I met him at a is that a phoenix?
That's my phoenix tattoo. I'm going to show you some shit. I just figured out how to operate my Google Drive.
That's nice. Yeah, show me.
It was red because it's new, but let me show you.
Yeah, you look a little red there.
Yeah, it's brand new.
Summer has a phoenix too.
Yeah, let's see the after.
Why does everybody get in Phoenix is the next tattoo I want to get it's a good bird. Goddy. What do you think? Let me see
The high priestess. Oh
No, like it make it a tramp stamp make it where
Yeah, show some cleavage and have the ball in between the cleavage. That's that'd be perfect
Okay, the last I heard Justin back there talking
Justin is getting beers for me and he said tell him that he's telling me he's being my bitch
He's being he's being what he's getting my bitch
Yeah, he got me. Oh, he's beer bitch. Okay. Yeah beer bitch
Yeah, I thought I thought you said ribbed. Oh my gosh. No, he's being my bitch. Sorry. I'm sorry
Yeah, God, he I love like just like five minutes away from him. You asked me for about long on audit
Yeah
Yeah, I went to one of his protests not to like walk around with a sign or nothing
But the protest was like two to five and I got there at like 515 and
You know all the people are trying to get on the camera like hey, this is my channel
This is you know, and he's doing like a live thing
So when I got there everybody was gone and I got to like have like a 20-minute conversation with the guy
Because I just you know, I wasn't gonna just blindly support him
I wanted to like size him up and see like who the guy was and he's
He's pretty chill
He got arrested the other day, I don't know if you saw that video.
Yeah, the fucking, uh, state trooper spit in his face.
That's what he saw it.
Like Justin then yeah, so so like wait wait so in real life you size them up
And then you realize that like he's a lot larger than you
But yeah
Yeah, he went he's got a history with that that guy that Justin's talking about and this guy's nuts
And he went to his house with the fucking billboard truck. He bought a billboard truck
You know like it was like writing shit like you know, he should lose his job
And this and that he parks in front of the guy's house
And then he goes up to the door and knocks on the door
And then the guy comes out of his house his name is brian v and he's got he's brandishing a gun and he's like get off my property
and showed poor races like
and he walks all day to golf his property and then to stay trooper
Like and makes him turn around so he's like now backstepping off of his property and then he spit in his face
That's crazy
Like that I don't like to attend things like that man
I guess he's asleep and Alex, sorry, you're gonna have to wait.
Psyche is sleeping?
You're gonna have to wait, Alex.
You're just gonna have to wait.
Alex, you're gonna have to fucking wait.
Come on, Psyche.
Wait, Psyche.
Fuck it, Psyche.
No, you guys, I wish everybody would use like a distorted voice like, Psyche, you have
to fucking wait.
I
Give me the keys I have to get a 7-eleven motherfucker hurry
Me and mongo
Which one's mongo with the glasses
The great mongo trick that definitely has a foe
Oh boy, how could I tell?
He's convinced the world he didn't exist
He knew, he knew
Alex knows, Alex knows
Who's this?
See
Oh, he's still
fucking alive
He's still around
That's funky
Is that yeah, that's me. No
Fucking way
Let me turn it upside down. Oh, shit. It is you
Her head hanging off the edge of the bed, bro, that's what yeah that one
Kill them all summer kill them all and ball that's how I'm gonna leave you a spunky upside down
I'm saying
Please stop. Yeah. Yeah, look, this is that's us tonight
if it'll load
Digital load you said if it'll load. I'm trying to put a picture of us tonight. Let's see
It's being weird
Who's what's your mom's hand? I hope so
My mom's a freak
I pray lover
You would
She looks just like my pic right now, yeah, she probably does yeah ten years
What's that a nipple oh
It's my nipple
I wonder why Google Drive is being so stupid it like won't load these things I've uploaded what the fuck
What'd you say you discovered? Your Google what?
Google Drive to upload this shit on here. All right. Looks like it there. You can do it from your your pics
Yeah, but I'm on my iPad. They're not what I've like taken from my pictures. You know what I mean?
Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah, it doesn't work the same. Okay. Yeah
I was gonna show you Mongo's new car
Oh, yeah, I want to see this. Yeah, you know that 106 miles you said it's uh, yeah, yeah, and it's it was a 2004 and
But this is someone who I trained his wife to be a nurse practitioner. So he's super super like
You know, yeah, right ball. So he's like, thank you for letting him her do your her clinical hours with you and
So he was like fuck. Yeah, like
That's awesome. I'll give you a deal. Yeah, it was four grand. It was listed on the website. You probably might need an alternator soon
But other than that, that's great. Mm-hmm
The brakes were good the I didn't have them looked at yeah, but like we're going to the
you know to the mechanic my mom knows to
Look at have everything looked at we put in a new battery the battery was dead the tire stop
My best friend's son works at his hair place. So he's gonna put them in
Yeah, don't spend a whole bunch of money, but tires breaks and battery tires breaks battery, you know, just like, you know
Normal shit. Yeah to get him around because like all that's gonna add up to probably like four grand
Which I would have paid for the car anyway, so
Tell him to change the tire by himself just to practice so he's not stuck anywhere. Yeah, when I came up to
My friend son shop, I'm gonna have him interact. My friend son is 21
And Corbin is almost 17
They've grown up together, so I'm gonna have him like give him a little like man-to-man talk
About how to change tires and all that shit because Boyle can't do it. No boy won't talk to Corbin
Boyle do it man. Teach him how to change a tie. He'll love you. I know that's what he said
Like this is the opportunity for Boyle to like bond with him
Two things will happen either he'll bond with Boyle or he'll turn into the incredible Hulk if the shit falls
Yeah
Have fucking lose the mind of a you did this to me on purpose
Mr. Boyle don't make me angry you wouldn't like me when I'm angry
And you know it's funny
Mongo is absolutely me just like a little boy version
Mongo is gonna grow up to be a nice gentleman
He's gonna get all this out of his system.
He's a good boy.
He just needs a little guidance.
Like I said, he needs a big brother.
He does. He does.
He has a dad.
He has a dad and his dad is very active in his life too.
Nothing's wrong with that, you know?
We act like he doesn't have a dad.
His dad's not far from him either.
No, he's not. Not at all.
He's in high school, right? He's a junior?
He's gonna be a junior next year. It's up coming year. Okay
In what August?
I think him and Boyle would bond over cyber security
My son was a lot about cyber security if they were just talk about it, you know, I told you all that shit, you know
Yeah, that shit he did. That's crazy
What are you doing? Yeah, you hacked into the files or something tell him you can tell him
He started selling pictures of girls to other other kids
So my son's like Rico Suave, and he obtained all these like nudies in middle school of other girls and he created a discord server and then started selling these nudie pictures of these girls for Fortnite cash or whatever.
Oh my god.
When I discovered I fucking beat his ass.
And yeah, it didn't go well.
He was especially pretty popular though, right?
I bet you they were lining up.
Yeah, he's handsome and I mean, he's not amazing or anything,
but he looks just like me, but a man, a young man.
And yeah, he holds his own, you know what I'm saying?
Hell yeah.
It's pretty wild that black women black women are his thing like
Mix women black women any any any of that? Yeah, what was he like seven great smoke?
He was like seventh grade. What do you think he was in like seventh grade when he did this shit?
And yeah, he mirrored his hard drive so I couldn't see it outright
And then like I when I got deep into it. I figured it out told us that is that a fucking piss
And that yeah
That's what happened and like it and by the way the equivalent of money would have been about $5,000
He wanted for that cash. That's crazy. I mean it makes sense. You know that age. I did just so fun
Well, he was real smart. He made an entire server on
discord of a mirror of
Disney and
Then people were subscribing to that that he built
Having monthly memberships to see that, but I shut it all down how old is he now?
17 almost gonna be an entrepreneur. It sounds like I know he's smart
So then his newest thing is he told me he's like mom. You're a doctor
I know I don't really want to be a doctor, but I'm kind of thinking about becoming a radiologist
So that I can sit at home and read everybody's images and I can have like, you know, two three monitors
I can play my games. I can do whatever the fuck I want to do
I can still help people by telling them what's up, but I just pull up their image read it whatever
Write off the transcription and like send it off and I'm done. It's really a good idea
Sounds like a million man in the making school paid for he'd be so smart to do that, but will he do it? I don't know
Yeah, we talked about that before like big when like the writers go on strikes for like the shows and movies and stuff
They just they had the AI writing and shit like I'm waiting for an AI to win an Oscar, you know
They'll probably end up hacking the Pentagon.
What?
That's what I was gonna say before.
Remember Wargames?
Oh, I love that movie
And he goes to that island that goose island and yeah, so find the dude. Yeah
He's and he's flying a plane right he's flying that our RC plane and shit in the yeah, yeah
That was a girl was what was the what was it called again? What was the name of the?
Computer it was like for oh
acronym whopper whopper that's right. Yeah
Yeah, W.O.P.R. Hell yeah, the Whopper.
Good old days, that giant fucking computer.
Now that thing can, you can hold it in your hand, that fucking computer.
I know, I know.
Amazing.
I had the first iPhone and I think it was like two gigs of memory.
I think it was, at most it was two gigs, I think.
And maybe one gig, you know, now it's, they got terabytes of shit.
It's crazy.
Yeah, they could fit that shit on a pinhead now.
And you're absolutely right though that that computer in that movie is like in our hands. It's in our hands
Those are good movies back then. Oh, you don't get shit like that anymore
Tic-tac-toe. You want to play a game? It's so good
So good. He's changing all the grades memories changing his grades and shit in the yeah
I was gonna say he was like the original hacker. He was hacking into everybody's fucking system
You remember how he gets the passcode? You remember how he gets the passcode?
Yeah, he got called to the principal's office. He went and he looked at the file. Yeah
Yeah, you looked on the need like the desk or whatever. It's all crossed out. That's that was great
They remember how we hacked the phone the payphone
Oh, yeah, that's actually like my favorite scene where I tried to do that so much
He puts that thing he he unscrews the receiver right on the bottom and then yeah, yeah, I tried to do that so many times
Don't you have it to it it probably worked until that movie came out. Yeah, absolutely. That's usually what happens
And it's probably in the movie because somebody did this shit, you know, like somebody did it on set a producer or something
They're like hold on little let's change it first before you put the movie out. Okay
Hell yeah, he was he was a good, you know, he was like one of those kid actors that transitioned to like adulthood
Good, you know, they didn't get all awkward and like, you know, you know what happened with him
He was doing good
Until apparently he was driving one day. I forget where in Europe or some shit or maybe here. He killed somebody
Did he really? Yeah, apparently he killed somebody and got off I guess
But after that fell off. You really didn't see anything from him after a certain year
Was he drunk? I don't really I don't remember the full story, but I know it was some vehicular homicide shit
Yeah, I forget what year exactly you'd have to look it up Matthew Broderick. Yeah, he lives by me, too
He lives out here. I mean, I live in the Hamptons, but
Yeah, him and his wife that chick that's on
Parker whatever fuck yeah, sorry Jessica. Yep. Yeah, nothing special there
Oh
Horse face
Are you friends, uh, sorry spongebob, I know that was a front of yours
I know you run with the highfalutin crowd over there in hollywood. It is
Hi, so did they do?
You'd be surprised by the people I know I wouldn't be surprised. I can imagine you you would be real surprised
I will one day. I'll figure it out. Yeah, they run shit out there. They do what the fuck they want. I hope it's somebody cool
I hope it's not somebody shitty
I was the finance man
You know an amour, you know, it's not just my looks. Oh
It's who you know
I blow you you heard that story too, right? The story about Jose can say girl. Yes. I did. That's a great ridiculous
It's a great fucking story
He was like everybody's favorite baseball play as a kid. I used to fucking pretend I was him the play
He shouldn't literally
My dad was in the federal penicenturer with him at the same time
For my dad's bullshit with the mafia and whatever the only thing they could get him on was the fake identity
And they, when I rolled up at home, when I was in high school in like, uh, this was like 2002, 2004, I came home and my, my FBI was running my house and anyway, my dad went to jail and he went to, um, I lived in Cocoa Beach at the time, so he went to Miami Federal Pen for that and he was put, he was acted up, he was being an asshole, so he got put into solitary.
And, you know, protected housing or whatever, and that's exactly where Jose was.
So my dad was like neighbors in the same jail as Jose Canseco, and they were slipping letters
to each other through the air vents or whatever, and my dad's a fucking retard, so we couldn't
but he was able to like talk to him through there
and they became friends.
And afterwards, my dad got out before he did
and came home and he was writing him letters at my house
and my mom got fucking pissed when she caught wind
that someone from jail was writing my dad.
So she shut it down and wouldn't let him talk to him anymore
and wouldn't let him respond.
But when I found out I was fucking Jose Canseco,
I was dying laughing.
I thought I was crazy and I-
the like even wrote him and said like you know hey my dad can't really write my mom's mad that
he's got a friend from jail he doesn't let him like associating with anybody from there my mom
doesn't have any idea who you are or whatever but like thank you and my dad ended up dying shortly
after he had a heart attack and unexpectedly it just just passed yeah it sucked but uh it was uh
It was fucking crazy.
I had all these letters from Jose Canseco.
He made friends with my dad.
And my dad didn't really know who he was either because he was a sports guy.
And I tried to tell my dad like the magnitude of like how cool it was
that he was talking to Jose Canseco.
And he to him was just a friend he made in the jail.
And it was a good friend.
And like, is my nuts.
Yeah.
You know, it's looking crazy
He was like
My dad when my my dad name fucking know who Madonna was he was just some you know old
curmudgeon like he had no idea
Looking crazy
That's cool. Apparently like
The mother of them had a bond that like got them through the day and they like, you know, figure their shit out and
Made it through but life is so funny, isn't it?
Now you can take it off.
Got it, you taking a dump?
What?
What is all that, you taking a dump?
I'm washing my hands, do you mind?
Well I mean afterwards you can, but like, what started that?
I finished up, you told that story, I finished up.
Oh you were jerking off during that.
Yes, it was a great story, what do you mind?
Oh my god, it was a great story.
I loved it, thank you.
You're welcome. Put a little lotion on afterwards. Fuck me. Thank you, honey.
Just someone's enough of a Nigerian nurse got you off. No, no, it's tomorrow.
She'll be here at three.
Don't mind the noise. It's just a wheelchair
You drink a mountain explosion
What the drinking mountain explosion. No, no, no my coke zero on ice
Dude got it. You know I love coke zero, but I love cherry coke zero. Yeah, that's not too much flavor. I don't need all that
I need all of that like the pure
All of that
So good, so fucking good.
So I'm uploading so much shit, I hope it comes up.
What happened, you're losing weight?
I'm uploading some shit, Gotti,
I'm gonna show you some pictures.
They better be good.
Are you serious, Justin,
or are you just fucking around right now?
No, I don't know.
You don't know if Gotti likes Iron Maiden, really?
What?
What do you out of your mind?
He's fucking around. Okay, good. Oh, there we go. What a thing to say. I
Know right? It's so gay. I would kill half the earth just so Iron Maiden can live forever
Thank you
Job you would have loved me when we were younger when you were like 40 and I was like 16
My first job was at Spencer gifts in the mall
I was there the other day
Fucking iron-mated figures and bullshit and whatever. Yeah, I bought them just fresh off the truck
I know you would have loved me would have loved the hookup. Oh, that would have been great the 40% discount. Yeah. Yeah, all that too. Yep
Still have all that shit
Yeah, I don't I don't think it's published but
You know, you know, so, you know, I heard that shit. I rolled up to my house. My house is being raided
I had to figure my shit out Katrina. You're awesome. Yeah, I had my my 21-year-old boyfriend
get us an apartment in Cocoa Village and
I lived there like you know under the under the thing anyway, so I went to through this program called an
OJT program where you could be a I was in 10th grade at the time and
I worked
Full-time on this on-the-job training program and used all my elective credits to work full-time at work and earn money
Well, I was in high school
So my job was at Spencer Gifts.
And and I'll tell you I'll have you know it Gotti my boss at the time is now my secretary and my job currently
Wow
Yeah, she's crazy. She is she's a cool. She's a cool lady. She's older now and like life is great
And when I needed a secretary she was like, oh babe, I'll come do it for you
but uh, you know back then she was in her 30s and
She loved me. She thought I was just
The fucking best supporting me taught me how to be a woman taught me how to be like a lady and
Take care of my shit. This was my mother. This woman is an amazing woman an absolute force in my life
But yeah, so I used to get all this these like action figures and bullshit
But I would buy them, you know, I'd get them in I'd Google on you know
What was like the thing to get and then I'd sell them on eBay of course your scalper. Yeah, you scalp. Yeah
I scalped on and make a lot of extra money doing that shit. We hate people like you. Yeah
You're the reason I can't find time I won't go walk into a fucking wall
you were paying for my insulin
because I'm a type one diabetic and I didn't have insurance.
So until I turned 18 and I was able to obtain insurance,
I was like, well, I think I got at 17.
Anyway, when I got promoted to being a manager,
I was the first person in Spencer's history
to be promoted under the age of 18
to become a manager of Spencer's
and then I got insurance, so.
Did they pay you in dildos?
They paid me in dildos and all I wanted was my fucking insulin, that's all I cared about, but...
I haven't been in a Spencer gift in, I'd say, six, seven years. I went into one about a week or two ago
just to run through to see what's up because I happened to pass by one.
I'm like, let me see what's up in there. I'm like, you know, made in shirts or something like that,
but I made the mistake of walking to the back.
Of course, what do you see in the back? First thing you fucking see is a purple dildo staring at you in the face
A purple dildo, yeah, why not everybody should have one. It's like the generic color purple is the fucking generic dildo color
Purple dildo it was in the um clearance a bit and apparently nobody wanted it
Did you take him home?
I should have, yeah, but no, I left it there.
You should have. That poor little dill.
Yeah, poor thing.
Yeah.
I should have sent him to the psyche. Yeah, he would have been upset.
He would have been excited. He would have put that right in his butthole.
No, I think psyche's a top.
Not to pick on psyche. I think he's a top, but...
Just saying.
What's back?
So the Vader clone, I can see it up here.
It was a Vader clone.
Dude, why is Google Drive being such an asshole? I've uploaded all these pictures
I got so much shit to show you Goddy, and it won't it won't lady lady lady
I don't see pictures. I want to see fucking video put your fucking camera
Show me the goods. I don't want to see pictures. I don't want to see old there. We go. Come on. Yeah, why?
That's all right
What is going on there goes it caught up
Go upside down again, that was great. Yeah, that was great. Great. We can do 69 hold on
You had a lot of tasks see that ass do you know see that ass when she got up? Whoa
Like a jungle booty she had a no wonder boils with you
No, I actually don't have a big booty. Yeah, is he writing crutches? I was being nice. No, I didn't see it
I don't have a big motorboat and son of a bitch
That was like God he'd be nice be nice. I'm being nice
They built this speed
Are you gonna lift it up a little more lift it up? Oh my god. Oh my god. He did it, but it's not I can't oh
I got it
It's so juicy
It's not it's very muscular like when you hit it doesn't move. Oh like a dude's ass. Yeah
Sorry.
That's what boils into that.
Apparently.
He always said he wanted a girl that looked like a Phoebe Kate's in the face
Bruce Jenner in the body
She's a great storyteller I've been listening that's a great story great story. I'm good to see you man
You have an interesting life, right?
Right, if you spread it in your legs for it.
You see that?
Holy shit.
You say random, you say random.
I don't know who your boyfriend is,
but like, it's like, he like put you to work.
He's like, hey, go stream for me
because I'm getting bored.
And so he can go play Nintendo with his legs crossed.
Is he autistic?
I like this guy, he's funny.
He's totally ugly.
I'm just making up stories in my head.
I gotta go see.
Holy shit.
Hey random, thanks for uh, thanks for sponsoring the panel, man
Here's a quick message from
A little lower Marce a little lower just a little bit
I
Doesn't
Double trouble. It's like 3d night
Right in front of their husbands too, I love it. I love it
It would be all set
School that's my husband's like wait am I missing something?
I'll be right back that's what happened to random guy, right Katie said smokey is getting smoky
I'm a straight man. I could do that
Marcy's
You got drunk you right now
Drunkie not
Telling stories or what?
My my other thing gaudy that I should tell you is that I had a best friend
So I win it
All right
So
How I ended up in Cocoa Beach was that my parents were like in distress when they lived in Greenfield and
They were they were doing the shit when they were like fixing stuff
But like not really fix it at the right way and do what they needed to do
So they knew they were hot on their ass the heat was there that had to get out. So they said Stephanie
Stephanie recently got diagnosed with type 1 diabetes. She wasn't feeling good. She wasn't having a good time
They were like, baby, we know you don't feel good. Where do you want to move?
I was like, well shit, Disney World. Take me to Disney.
If I could be dying,
This could be the end of my life. I'm nine. Take me to Disney World. So...
These fuckers sold their business and you know, they were renting a house and they had whatever
so they sold their business and they came up with like I want to say at the time was like $26,000
from this business and they bought an RV for 18 grand and took the rest of the cash and pocketed it and
Took it sold everything from the house. We had a massive garage sale and said get in the RV. We're going we're going to Disney World
Fuck I was so excited. This is great. This is a
like summer of
And we move to
I just want to talk to Marcy when we get a chance
I'm sorry
What up God got my boy excellent one in school
My boy Marcy you're the only one that has contact with easy out of all of us right?
So you have to let him know that's not me
They made a hole
They are Alexander McQueen roast
They made a panel you saw that
All right, so the cagaga and her mom they're going crazy. He starts attacking easy with their own
Oh, I'm the evil one and all that shit. I don't want to get in between that
But now they went as far as making a panel called Alexander McQueen a channel
With my picture and now they're pulling up old videos when I had beef with easy
Trying to make it look like it's now, but you know, they're trying to manipulate
So I, you know, because he's a fragile mind, my friend, he could take it first and I don't want the kid back in my neighborhood.
Oh, please mercy. No, I know God you're loving it
But they know at least Wanda and DJ Paco know because they they commented and they were like, yo
You think we're that stupid to think it's Alex like we know you're using it shit. I was like, thank you. Thank you Dorothy Boyd
The only bitch that got up and left the office room?
You know that, right?
You don't need to know the bitch.
No, I'm sorry.
She was talking about the money.
You fucking, you're burst right in with this bullshit.
Who's coming with us?
I am, man.
Come on, play.
from maple country he's got a badge of dream and a thing for a laugh called a glimpse of her smile
now he's doing the math from the Bronx to the bush oh he's thinking real deep page are you the one
i've been missing in my sleep hey
Paige, will you fall in love with me?
He dreams of her boots in his uptown bed
Laughing at the dumb ass jokes he said
She's gutting trout, he's eating steak
Somewhere in the middle they both take a break
He'd trade his knife stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his patrol
Oh Paige, don't you know you're the catch of the day
And this cop's got one hell of a line to say
Fucking beautiful
Until I saw some fucking tranny
Why is paging the bushes with a beard
Best song I ever heard until I saw page with a beard crying like what the fuck is wrong with site
He's crazy
And bro, that's on purpose by the way, there's no way he
Reviewed that radio 10 times before he dropped it. So that was on purpose because he's an asshole
No, they don't know yeah, no Marcy AI does not fuck shit up. That's what you're wrong
That's why it's AI together and had a baby you dumb bitch
You know what it means Marcy's article you dumb bitch that just flies out of my mouth it rolls off the tongue
You know what it is? He's trying to mind fuck me in page. He was blending us together. Like look there
Anyone knows about blending if you've been with a person long enough
You start blending with them like you start becoming them and they become you in a way
I've had so many relationships. Oh, I know what that blend is shit. And that's what I thought about when he did that
Or maybe just a freak
You the way
No, you're gonna ask Alex come back cuz I'm out too
I know I wanted to hear the rest of your story though
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
So I'm moving to know this celebrity right here, Rick Worthy.
Who Rick Worthy, he played the head vampire in the show Supernatural.
He played. Yeah, I don't.
I'm blind. He played the Cleong in Battleship Galactica.
I've seen him before. Yeah.
I was an extra in a few movies.
living in Cocoa Beach when I ended up moving here.
I was an extra in,
fuck, things behind the sun.
And then it was like some movie,
was like something about going to space
that they recorded in our high school there too.
I'm gonna fuck it. I have to look it up. No, I can't fucking remember but you know, you can't really like see me in it, but
things by the Sun I ended up having a
Human see me in it
after you if you watch the movie, but I met Don Cheadle and
Rosanna
No, I actually know Don
Don's from Wyandotte County Kansas City, Kansas
From the 30s, I know that dude. Yeah
and they were they were really cool like I had a scene where I there was a scene where they're in
I know Eddie Griffin also Eddie Griffin is my older brother's best friend they went to high school
together yeah and I said I know a few celebrities I used to go to the Grammys every other year and
go to the after parties and shit never attended no Divi parties actually I've never really seen
That's because he was having his own diddy parties, ish?
That's what I was going to say.
Yeah, don't.
He's a small guy.
He's at the vanity fair parties, and then he goes there.
The way that Mary used to kick it, well, that's Mary J. Blige and Heavy D.
They used to kick me with us back in the day before we moved here.
But I don't know if you remember Candy, I knew her well.
I said I know a few people so I made friends with a gentleman who
Was in school with me in middle school, and he was an up-and-coming photographer, and he was great
So he became a junior photographer for transcontinental records
And then I got to go to all the up-and-coming like concerts and whatever he photographed all the concerts
There was great. He had a magazine online back then. They were zines. I don't know if you remember that and
He has his name was Wesley still friends with him this day very close friends
Um, I met Britney Spears, I met NSYNC, I met, uh, Take Five, uh, like, just, just, many more.
My, um, he dated a girl who, they, like, Wesley was gay.
I dated this girl as a beard and
She became really close with me and back in the day. I had a lot of trauma. So I was like, oh
I don't really like men
Her and I became super close and we had to come to him and say like hey by the way like you can't date her anymore because I'm dating her
So
Yeah, it was like a huge traumatic thing, but it was all worked out. Everything was fine. Her and I dated until I was in my 20s
um it was great and she she had a little group that she did too i will not mention it um
that she did with her her friend did not did not hit did not make anything and anyway we're all
we're all friends to this day it's crazy but i got to go to and meet all of these celebrities
I feel like I fucking like scored and I didn't even know what I was into until afterwards, you know
Yeah
And a ton of stuff man tons
On television he never really want to go into the big movies, bro
He's been offered hell of big movie
Bros, but he's turned them all down because he likes the flexibility of doing the television shows
Plus, you know, how they fly up
and and he worked constantly you know I was looking at his filmography and
every year he had work every year and once he gets once you get known you know
you could do like a episode or two on a television show like a arc they call it
and you know you paid for the whole year you know what I mean you do a couple
weeks worth of work yeah he's in a ton of stuff I heard you say he was a cling on
on Battlestar Galactica but
Klingons in Star Trek he was Simon on Battlestar Galactica. I watched that show. I remember him. I
Was a big role
Yeah, yeah, and then he also played a Klingon on Star Trek, but he was in City of Angels
He had a show not too long ago where he was the Dean and shit of that like a supernatural type college and shit
He was like the main yeah supernatural alpha vampire and then he was in the man in the high castle too. That show is good
I'm trying to think of that one that he was like he was a dean of some kind of fucking college for people that were kind of like
Supernatural abilities and shit. He was called super supernatural. It was his character
He was the main star he was the dean of the college you're talking about supernatural where he was the
Empires how about the vampire diaries?
He was in vampire diaries. That was it says main role. Could that have been it? Yeah. No, no
Fuck I had to look it up. Gotcha
He worked with some really famous people Nicholas Cage and Julia Roberts Clive Owen
Project that I'm talking about. He was just doing four or five years ago. Nice
Is the magicians it's called Dean Henry fog. That's what it's called. Okay
Gotcha one where he was the dean of the college and shit, bro. Yeah Dean five gotcha
Yeah, he's on like the main cast build and everything son. That's cool
Well around his character
Yeah, he was in the every every season he was reoccurring in season one and then main cast for the rest of the show two through five
I mean, I met a whole lot of people through music because my homeboy was fat tone and shit before fat tone died
Because they thought he killed Mac Dre
Yeah, this is cool
Do you watch that show that he was in Rick worthy the man in the high castle. Did you ever hear that one?
I've heard of it. I never got a chance to watch it, bro
It's an alternate history show where I didn't watch these in the Mount of the Magicians though because yes
Let's check that one out. Yeah, I'll check it on the man in the high castle is like an alternate history
So Hitler won the war and it's like they chopped up the United States the West Coast the Japanese have and
The East is the Germans and he's in that too
Yeah, and that photo, we had a funeral, though.
Please bear enough family member at that time.
I'm going to make some food real quick. I'm hungry.
Yeah, I probably need to eat but I've been fucking smoking like I'm not the realistic. I
Was just not to say knows what I'm gonna do
Wow, I hate on my last night
See now you're making me fucking hungry. They was talking about food earlier and shit was fucking now you're talking about eating
I'm fucking hungry now ever since I got the air fryer. Yeah, and you don't have to
This bitch when I start fasting again fuck that I
Be like five days into a fasting you motherfuckers gonna start mentioning food and shit
Sorry, I'm having to fucking write something really quick here
I'm gonna throw this stuff in I'll be back. Okay. I think you actually fly
Ah, good God, some people have no lives.
Anyway, so what you guys do today? Anything exciting, anything fun?
No, no, just go out and get that bag.
Plain old, plain old everyday shit, right?
Yeah, yeah.
Man came home trying to get blitzed this fuck
It's something to eat cuz eight things had to re-bring up food and shit. All right
I know probably hit those my daughter made like fucking ten burritos last night
And she's like I made a bunch for later, too
And she left if she went out with her boyfriend tonight. So I'm like, oh shit. I'm not going
Eat some of these little burritos man
That's a good thing about having a daughter that's old enough to like make food now like she can make food for me
Make food for the family
You know
Oh, yeah, I hate that my older daughter then got pregnant and moved out with her baby daddy
Because she
All the time if I was too tired to cook my baby
The wife was too tired to cook baby girl would be cooking
She made you a grandpa this young shit. She's 19
Pay attention, please. We're paying attention. We would pay in the attention. What are we not paying attention?
No one is backstage by the way
Yes, baby is trying to get up. I want to see them, too
And Evans was just gonna throw some food in and come back. Yeah
It's so weird that people like they are like they need to like harass me
I do not even get that
It's like an unfathomable to me that you would sit there and just pay attention to all this shit all day just
I see this shit is crazy
Right. I'm like the internet is crazy on its own
But I mean like when dealing with people that probably need mental care mental health care
It's a whole not sure, you know
Well, it'll be honest everybody here needs mental health care
I
Talk to a counselor. I used to be once a week, but it's now only after being my counselor once every two weeks
I'm a low priority
Yeah, you're right. I was like, I guess that's a good thing
I'm emotionally dead inside. So I'm just here as an observer. Yeah. Yeah, I'm a delusional optimist
So I'm like stupid about shit. I just
So happy
Don't it's awesome though. I like it
I don't even know who they are. I've only seen them just recently in the chat
Oh, New York native is in chat. What's up, New York native? Good to see you
Yeah, I'm all close on this view. Come on. Yes, baby. Hey, how's it going everybody?
Let's go, let's go. Get some people up here, y'all. Yes, yes, y'all. When you don't stop, it's like a new one's backstage.
Yeah, I just wrote this whole thing out and now it's gone
For some reason psyche is saying nope to that individual wonder why
For real sake you why can you tell me
Now
That's pretty much fucking foot go play with one of the other kids. It's when you play mates over here
You don't have to attack my feet, bro
All right, thank you. Oh
Good, baby, I can understand we don't want no poor bomber up here
Right God forbid that let me go to Tom flash and perform on them
Be right back
Yeah, be BRB psyche I'll get some revenge
Seemed I did twice and I was sick
Huh, my psyche, could you please find me?
Hey Grace, what's up?
Hi, do you hear me?
Yeah, yeah, we could see you in a minute.
Yeah, I don't know it was like it's like I someone said something about Tom flash earlier
I went and I checked his channel and he was like he's like on a show right now
And then like the BSPB is like oh, I'm sitting in the back row and I look at some Tom flash
And then it said like the name it was like some form bomber name
So he's like trying to like
I don't know it's not the same person. I don't think it's Tom Tom flash
But um, don't keys check you on though
Yeah, I have a bagel with locks. I have a. Oh, damn. I never got my fucking. Oh my god. I think I'm in. I never got my
more cigarettes, but I don't have any time to run to the store. So, oh well.
How's your bike doing? Have you been able to charge it or no?
They just the neighbors just moved and like she's like I let them use my garage to store their stuff in and she's like
Oh, we'll buy you your part what you need and then they but then they just moved it. I didn't like I don't know if they did but
Yeah, they just moved a few minutes away. So hopefully I think he'll come back in and fix it
But yeah, they're kind of busy, but I think you ordered for me. So I
Want to do it. Yeah, but I had my bike. I would fucking drive over there right now shit
I guess I'll just not do the macro to that.
This cat is being crazy and eating my feet.
One of my favorites, the black one, oh. Chill, golden eyes, chill.
Here, yeah. What was that? I'm not down for you.
I love that chacat. I love that cat. Real blacky.
Yeah, yep. It doesn't have a whisk like Lenore.
Oh, bye, Zeb.
Oh, wow, that's cute. That's really cute. Pause, Tarot. Future in your pause. You want to pull a card for me from that? Sure, yeah
Cool
Dude, just kidding. You're killing me, GoldenEye. You're killing me. You're gonna be the next one we give away if you keep it up
I'm just kidding. I like GoldenEye. He's a cute one
He's got these crazy like amber colored eyes
Hmm
You hear me now. Here we go. Oh, yeah, you hear me now. Okay good
Okay, yeah, these like they're pretty cute cards. Okay, so I'll give you some cards
Okay, let me just shuffle. Oh the back of them is really cute, too
Rats making videos about you online
Okay
Okay you
So we first out we I mean we have the death card, but the death card is always remember like really I always consider it like
There's some kind of like yeah, it's an end of something it's something something something's ending
But it's like it from but from there it goes to King of Swords and a wheel of fortune
Okay, so King of Swords is like this really really good communicator. I would say probably an airside. I don't know
For sure, but it's like it looks like this
It's like once you talk to this guy. It looks like it has something to do with like the mate this the wheel of fortune going really in
Your favor. I think this is like somebody good to do business
Maybe business or something with because we also have the Sun and the night of cups
Okay, so the Sun is like really one of the most positive cards in the deck
Yeah, it's a really little unicorn she was on the unicorn
it's like positive and so it's like and it kind of like is like a contrast it's like if there's
been like some kind of like even if there has been some kind of mourning or sadness in the past
it's like you know it's like it's just really like the sun coming out again and then it's like
somebody's coming towards you also with this like something that's going to make you really happy
it's like some kind of something fulfilling it's like a cup but this cup can like also grow into
It also is a night. And so this guy may be like, I don't know. Look at the nights. The nights are a little bit rowdy
The nights of the night of cups, maybe a bit of a drink or something like that
I'm going to a family reunion down in San Diego in about a week or so
a little over a week
That's and they're the Kelly. It's the Kelly side of the family. So there are a few drinkers over there
Well
Let's see, okay, I will do one there, but where advice is, oh shoot, the advice would be too, okay.
Okay, yeah, so then we have the emperor. Okay, and so this is like, you know
This could be this is all the kings in the deck baby
But it's like it looks like there's gonna be some really fast communication from this like from this like important person
It's like somebody it's an important person
I think maybe all the kings and stuff and the advice that came out for you
Hold on was there one more the matter cups not a cut this okay
Yeah, the last cut the glass card gonna be the advice. It says strength and the strength is is they do is a god
Forced through gentleness. It's not it's not like you it's like, you know
He's petting the lion very softly and then it will open the lion's mouth instead of like, you know, like going kind of forcing it
It's like just a way to approach things for the best reason best result
It's like it's like always better to like like strength is like not you happy to use for sometimes, right?
Cool. Yeah
Key little cards. Yeah, this is like a either from a
Timu there's like five. They're like pretty much I think four dollars a deck or three. I don't know
I got for 20 bucks. I bet next like 20 bucks. So
Isn't that crazy how Timu can just like do the prices like that? Like it's wild
Some of the stuff and it's a crapshoot though. It's kind of like wish.com. You know, remember wish
You order stuff and you get you'd either get really something really good or something that you're like they re-bottle this
They have like some decks that are like regular price and then they have like these decks which are like kind of also popular decks
But they're like really cheap and then I noticed like but all these decks that came today are all the same size
And they're also none of them have like the instruction manual in them or books
So they're like they're like I don't need either there. They're like either like knockoffs of the main cards or they're like an abridged
Keeper
Traditional cars yeah only done so like a nine of tabs or like you know the embers or whatever it's like those type of things
But yeah, that's probably that's probably why I didn't have a book with it because I noticed the ones that have a book with them
Are the ones that are like kind of?
Like a like not traditional. You know what I mean, right like the Oracle card like the Oracle card sometimes. Yeah, I mean yeah
these are very
these are very like the traditional kind of cards sometimes but they but there is on the
team website there's on the page where they buy them there's like a little pdf
like that you can download and it has like the instruction manual for some of them
there's some of them do like and so but i think these might be kind of knockoffs because they did
these are these came from china they take like some of the stuff comes from like local places
but these came from china and take a couple weeks to get here sometimes people things
But it's still a good deal.
That's cool.
Very happy.
And if you guys want to check out
just inexpensive decks to kind of play with,
if you're not 100% sure you want to invest
in an expensive deck, they're not bad.
They also shuffle really good and a nice size for handling.
So I recommend.
Yeah, yeah.
When I played that song, the music video I made,
I noticed finally like,
Yeah, I was like, what is it going on like when she has the five o'clock shadow?
Yeah, it's so funny. But that's what AI does, dude. AI does that.
You'll put in like something spell, like spell something a certain way and they'll change like one letter or like, you know, like
get it like transposed, you know, something. So I guess it just made it like, it's cheaper.
Like, if you and Paige had a baby, Alex, that's what it would look like.
It's fabulous.
I, uh, like, okay, so, like, I, you know, the AI music generator is, like, it's, like,
pretty much free unless you want to, like, you know, share the song.
It's like, I don't want to download them.
I have to, you know, I've got a membership.
And so then I thought, like, the music video generator would be the same thing.
You just put the music in and get a membership.
It was, like, kind of like $19 for the membership.
So I like I went got 19 dollars for the membership and started making the video and that like stopped halfway through
And it's like you're out of credits and it's like you have to buy it's like a lot of credits
I know the $15 so that's like $35 I spent on that and then this woman has a beard in the video page has a beer
I mean, it's like I can't redo it
That was like mean in drag trying to like you know
He's like, he's really shit-faced, he won't notice.
Oh my God, that is pretty good.
It's expensive, but it was pretty cool.
I just not going to make another one.
I think I tried to make another one,
and look, I'd have to buy another pack.
Yeah.
It's expensive.
It starts adding up, yeah, definitely.
I might want to do one more just for my introduction of the show, but
You're gonna make it like a new song a new interest on well
I have I think I have one I want to use I've made like 10 songs already. Yeah, okay, but
There was one place last night that was kind of like disco-y, like electronica-y, and it was not super long, so I think that might be a good one.
I can't remember. It was just kind of random. It had a bunch of people's names in it and a bunch of people on the panel.
This is one about Gotti. The Gotti one is so cute and then let's see how many have 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12.
I made 12 songs. I have a full album of music so far, you know.
Wow, right? Justine, good to see you in chat there. Justine says she has a Ziggy dick pic.
Uh-oh, you can share it on my discord, but we can't put dick pics in the chat, but in the discord, okay?
No dick pics in the chat, bro.
How do you withdraw it?
Are you Tom? Actually, I have like a, not ziggies, but I have a picture of a, I drew a picture of a JT's winner.
But it's not, I don't think it's a really big picture.
Have you seen it?
No, I just imagined it.
I was like, did they have you score it? Like, cause I know like some guys that do that. They like send dick pics for people to score.
He's like the wolf man. So I just like made a real Harry. Oh, you know, Barry
Barry the turtle sent me his dick picture and his butt picture and then uh, and who else? Um, this guy named Theo
You know, Theo Theo sent me a yeah, Theo gate. Yeah
I haven't seen him since then. I think he got embarrassed. I'm like, that's a pure
I think so too. I know he hasn't been around for a minute. Summer said she talks to him though and that you look really good
Yeah
Yeah, because it'd have been so long, you know
Long since we've seen him like you are no brand new. I know I saw him like come back once since then
He's like he's had he's been busy with something. So yeah, I guess
Yeah
Boo
Yeah, but the berries like what do you think I was like, oh my gosh
I was like I really can but it turned out was like a fake picture. Is this a porn star?
Yeah
So, let's see somebody else's penis. That's right. That's the whole thing
No, no face is in it not like Theo's picture
That was a full body, right?
That was a full body in the mirror.
There's one full body.
There's a full body in the mirror with the pants down.
And then there's one with this.
Like, you put a hairbrush next to his.
Oh
It was pretty big it was as big as the hairbrush
I mean
I saw a summer earlier and she did that and I was like oh my god she did the
Marcy Titty Shake. Oh you invented it huh? Yeah you know it's just the top of the
tits no nips nothing just the top just wiggling and brandy. She has a little
bouncy bouncy. She grabs them really hard and just thrusts them in.
40 diamonds
Minor natural and hers are are are not natural. So hers are gonna be harder than mine naturally
I know
40 diamond did that and chocolate milk started squirting out, you know
I
Was here one time when she flashed the camera and I've never seen nipples that dark honestly. Yeah. Oh, yeah
I don't know why it's great
I'm like, she's a light-skinned Mexican, so I didn't expect different apples to be so
I don't have you ever seen like a dark like sometimes
Hispanic guys or I don't know if it's like Puerto Rican or something
But some of that they you look they're like look light and then they have a black dick and you're like, oh my god
Why'd you take black?
Yeah, I've seen that it really it really is
We have a dark thick
I think I've seen guys that look black from the waist down, but it wasn't because the actual physical color
Oh
Well, even like the berry the picture the berry set me that there was like half
It was kind of like half pink and half black. It looks like it looked like a pudding pop that I'm dipped in a
Oh
Are you are you Tom flash PSB be are you Tom flash PSB be are you I'll try of letting you on but
You were using the name Tom flash then there's a porn bombers name. Okay, so I'm not sure who you are
Because he's on live right now. He's not calling me. Oh Jamie is saying she says Jamie Cowboys on the on the read psyche
Can you please read why I don't remember the wreck?
My guess is this is your body trying to protect you from the trauma. That's my guess
You don't think dramatic like that
Or if you got a concussion that could be part of it as well
Yeah
It would be too traumatic to remember some of these memories and so the mind will just kind of put you into like a
Okay, so he's back. My will kind of put kind of give you give you temporary amnesia. I think you might oh like six a sort, okay?
Okay, six of swords queen of sword. Okay, because you don't want to remember it's like you're like you want to cut them away
It's like, you know, you know, it feels like it's like too overwhelming like the six of swords. It's like a
Did I come at a wrong time or something? No, you're fine. I was just telling it's just telling Jamie's like it's like you
You're able to you're able to cut away things that are too traumatic and
It's because it's like there's a lot of there's a lot of
Bad it's it's not a it's not a pleasant memory. It was scary. Okay. I'll look at one more. What's scary wait? What is scary?
Cards for Jamie
Why she doesn't remember the accident
I think it's a star. It's a star. So I don't have brain trauma, right? No, I don't think it's she means she heard her teeth and stuff like that
But it's I don't think she has brain trauma. I mean
And then it says are you the star the star which always means like a wish and it seems like you made a wish not to remember it
It's like, you know, you're just like you're like
Just blocked it out. I just feel like you just blocked it out. You're able to cut it away because it's
Would be too painful to remember, right? Well, I think Marcy said yeah, I think so
I mean if your head bashes into a fucking windshield, I mean you're not blocking anything a lot of people block out when they're injured
Like a lot of people like you don't remember when they hit the list should wake up
They'll be like what happened and they don't remember the accident
Okay, I kind of know what you're saying like like for me like when I get an accident
It's kind of a like a maybe a trauma thing because I get in that
No, when I get an accident, it's like a laugh and that's stupid
People laugh sometimes when they get hurt like some people do. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, that's what I mean. That's what I mean. Yeah. Yeah, that's stupid
Yeah, I don't know why
I don't know why why maybe you're maybe you're funny bone in the axle
Yeah, I don't know hook or may or maybe it's like you're a masochist and you love the feel of pain and so you just smile
I do I fucking I think I do
Very useful
I was in the military
Yeah, but I like I like fires and I like fucking like mosh pits and shit
Oh mosh pits. I thought you said muskets. I was like what in the fucking revolutionary were you talking about?
Oh, no, no, no, I'm a hey, I'm a civil re-enactor though, too. Oh, you are
I do have I have a musket. Yeah
I have a bus I have a bus kit
What the hell's a bus a bus a bus kit? I don't know what it means
Oh, I thought you said a dusk it like
It's dusty down there or something
Are you do?
Yeah, sure, man, yeah, we'll see if it's accurate though, man, you've tried it before
it wasn't really that accurate I wasn't okay to tell me this is good okay or maybe it wasn't you it
might have been that uh that page girl yeah she learned very accurate oh come on it might have been
I post just blocking it from you what's your what's your sign by the way I post yeah the
fucking go away should be but you know I posted a divan he said he said he's a divination um
he's a divination demon he is um and so he deals oh you looked it up you finally looked it up
Okay, I looked it up weeks ago. Remember when you said you said oh, it's his real name is this and I was like
Oh, it seems like it's like you like
Yeah, oh yeah, man. Well, I appreciate that and I like whenever you look up stuff man
Well, I know I studied the Goetia like I mean, I've studied Solomon's the key of Solomon and stuff
I told you the first time I met you and you're like you told me it wasn't that and then I like
Found that very odd that you knew that. Yeah, that's right. Why would you find that odd?
Not many people knew
When I was 18, I joined it, and I felt like there's like 100, 100 question, questionnaire. It's like, that's how you do. Okay.
And a lot of that stuff, yeah, yes.
Well, that was, I mean, they did the Anokian calls in the Satanic Bible, but they didn't really go over the Goetia.
The Goetia, you read when you say Alistair Crowley and stuff like that.
The only reason they didn't is because they took those books out and it's in the Vatican Library. That's why.
No, she's talking about the holy you're talking about the holy bible it's on the satanic bible
Oh, that's the devil's bible made out of skin and that the picture of the devil in it. Have you seen that?
Yeah, um, that's that that was actually it's made of human skin and or I think or maybe
It was made it by a monk the mad monk, but I pulled some cards for his
Punish his punishment was to sit and write the Bible
I mean
Rasputin Rasputin was a mad monk too, but okay, so okay, so Ziggy at the wheel
Yeah
Okay, so I have the wheel fortune and so it's showing like luck is on your side right now
Things are going in your favor. Then we have the nine of pentacles nine of pentacles can be yeah, you have a lot
Oh, actually, it's like you're up. There's abundance around you. Yeah, it's like so this is like there's gonna be some abundance
You're also gonna be handed something that's gonna make you really happy and passionate
It's gonna can grow into more more more wands and stuff like that
um the more wands you kind of the crazier we'll get but uh because then we have the king of wands
you're really able to like handle all the wands like he has a bunch of wands right then that was
the wands too okay so it's like you're really going to go together it seems like you're really
really going to come into being able to manage your own
Emotions, passions better and it looks like it's because you're gonna spend a lot of time alone or something
Or you like you like spend a lot of time alone and meditation or something like that. Oh for sure. Yeah, you do
Yeah, so I think yeah, that's that's gonna be the key in like learning those wands
I think but it's like you're gonna you're gonna really yeah, that's that's okay. Can I interrupt that?
That is one of the main things. I love I love to be alone. I love to work
you know obviously you know the chicken farm and all that stuff
and then I like to subject myself into like city life
as I want if that makes sense yeah yeah I got it what's up man
what's up man
I'm getting red right now
Oh, yeah, you look at this comment. So Chester Bennington was actually from my city that I'm from pals movies
And he hung himself there, right? You conjure hate by ignoring and showing love to the person right beside you
Who hung himself pals birdies? Yeah, yeah, that's where I'm from your mom's
Three four twenty palisbury's drive west. Wow. I grew up. I grew up right off palisbury's drive
I think up right now. I don't know if you know Malaga Cove, but it's like palisbury's the states has a statue of Neptune and like
an old Italian style plaza
Peacocks, yeah, it's beautiful. Yeah, we talked about the neighborhood church. My grandma actually was
That's where I was when I went to church there. Yeah, yeah, my grandma is one of the people that she raised Peacocks there in Palisbury's and they
released some of them
Peacocks
They brought in
Yeah, when they went down to the city. Yeah, they did like this guy named Vanderbilt or you know, he was like or not a Vanderbilt
It was like a Vanderbend or something. He's really he was a developer and they made the city really special like yeah, Vanderbilt
Yeah, I'll I'll I'll I'll red tile all red tile roof buildings Peacock
They built all these buildings and he was like hey, I want to bring in birds
Yeah, and then they've done peacocks of the peacocks are now it's still there. They're like they're really like a little bit of a nuisance
But I loved them hold on
Yeah, they're like really colorful. Yeah, justine
Everybody know I have Ziggy's dick pics just given to me
Anybody wants them they can come and get them
What does it look like? What does it look like? What does it look like? What does it look like? How did it look? Can you describe it to me? How does it look?
She just came up and was like, yeah.
You know what they look for, right? You know what they look for, right?
You see that? So tell me what it looks like, Ziggy. I want to hear exactly.
You don't have to send me the picture. Just tell me what it looks like.
Your best description.
Does it look like an anteater or a mushroom?
Circum size and circum size.
It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut. It's cut
I really am very upset that you know this kind of stuff about me because really I'm the most nicest person in the world
until somebody crosses me and
He showed a nude picture of me
Backstage show backstage
No
Don't put it on your screen don't put it on your screen don't put it on your screen
So now I get to show a picture of him. It's in the one now
Now I get to show 16 pictures of her
And I got the fucking evidence and I saved it in two places because I'm the true woman
I can sweet talk men into doing fucking anything you can go and fuck yourself and the reason why you don't
Sexually as you, Gotti, is because I never felt sexual towards you.
Gotti?
What are you talking about?
I don't know what happened.
Jesse, can you just see?
I have never felt sexual towards you.
That's the reason why you don't call me.
You talking about me?
You can't even keep pet pieces for a second.
Go ahead, bitch, go ahead.
Come on, I love you.
You're an asshole.
Do you want to know why I don't like you so much as JT?
Because you treat me like shit and you don't like me.
Why would I be mad?
She always said that, Gotti.
She said that you guys would treat her right.
Come on, man.
I know y'all.
You know what?
You think you're so much better at relationships than me.
I'm almost done, baby. I have kept three men going for 30 years, and the men, the new men that I have now, I have kept for one for nine months.
and one for four months.
But when is your girls? Where's your boys? Where's your girlfriends? Where's your,
where's everything? Oh my god. Hold on.
Two more bites. Two more bites, Kong. Two more bites. Okay, I'm done.
Did you tell me to have to feed you?
Let's go Skunk.
What do you want to say?
When you exit the studio, you'll be backstage
and you can show me the picture on the backstage
and no one else will see it.
What do you want to say Skunk?
Skunk.
Skunkka, Skunkka, are you there?
Go ahead, I'm listening. Go ahead.
I'm just letting you know that you think that you're so much better than me, but you can't hold it together with a woman.
I can hold it together with two new men who is in their 40s.
What two? Two new men.
You can't even keep one person together. You can't even keep head piece
Your word you mean nothing to me
you take to me skunk you're just talking you're just fucking talking baby sweet
word I don't like anybody that says the n words I don't see you like I don't want to know
wait wait wait gaudy gaudy I want to know how this turned into gaudy you're from me
you're fucking skunk you come up here with this bullshit nobody gives a fuck about your
Why are you even here?
Just say much better than really.
Where's your marriage?
Where's your kids?
Where's your family?
You never talk about them.
Nobody cares about me.
Wait.
Can everybody chill out for a second?
Please.
I know people care about me, sweetie.
No one cares about you at all.
You're so poor, baby.
That's why you have two old fucking men in their 90s.
You can't even keep a woman your number friend.
You've got two old men in their 90s.
You can't even talk shit about me.
You don't know anything about my life, downtown.
Why is she talking about you?
Have you ever been engaged?
I don't tell you a fucking thing about my life. How many times have you been engaged?
How many times have you been engaged? How many times have you been engaged, Donkey Kong?
Oh, sure. Four times for face.
Tell us, tell us, tell us how many times.
Four times with rings.
Yeah, that weird.
And you're all alone in the shitty apartment.
You're all alone in the shitty apartment for ten, right?
Why don't you marry them?
So I never married him because I think it's for me to suck him, to just bribe, to just bribe, but never dare.
Justine, Justine.
So I never brought him here to the company, never had kids.
Justine, I'm gonna, I'm gonna send Gotti like all the other 16 naked pics you sent me.
Well, please do it, baby, because I can send.
I am.
I'll send everybody.
I don't want to see them.
I don't want to fuck them.
Wow.
I don't want to see this pig your people are forcing these pictures on me. I don't want to see shit about her
It's a weird time
Hi.
What do you think
Oh, poor baby.
Get me there.
Oh, let me not be there.
Oh
I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't see I can't
Oh, JT, you're the best. You helped me with my dad issues.
You did the best.
Are we done? Yes, we are.
Are we done? You're old dad issues.
You're old dad issues.
Why is that? Why is your father made? You're a psycho, you're a mother fucker, and he hates you, dude.
Whose own family hates him that much?
I'm laughing my ass off of you okay um we're psyche he needs to be here when I have this
to say psych please come back oh oh oh he's gonna get it oh no he comes psyche please come
back principal's office
Oh, thank you. Please come back. I don't have a boyfriend in high school.
There's a weird head. Peter, you fucking fucking dumb pig.
Who was next to you?
I don't know. I haven't even turned into you.
I'm like, wait a minute.
No, not you, Christine.
Thank you. Please come back.
I need some to address, please.
But how did that turn in from me to him?
That was weird.
I don't know how it went from you to Scotty.
Yeah.
Christine, Christine, shut this bitch up, please.
God, that was just the weirdest thing.
Hot off the presses, baby.
Huh?
It is kind of important KT and he man in my in my opinion. What happened?
Well, the suicide he comes back. I'll handle it
But I don't want to handle it without psyche
So gentlemen and ladies if you give me one moment, please psyche you have somebody up on this channel
That last night was saying shit about you
Okay, who's that bad shit? It doesn't belong up here. Okay. Who is it?
He knows who it is. Maybe you gotta go. Yeah, okay. Okay. No dry. Yeah about me
No, he was on another panel talking shit about psyche
Oh
Fuckin toilet. Fuckin nuts. Fuckin head. Fuckin flush in your pig.
See ya. By the way it was a fake dick bag that I sent you from the board.
Oh, right.
Ken is dry.
Ken is dry. Are you here right now?
Yeah, he's right there.
Well, his picture's here. Is he here?
Oh, yeah.
Why are you here tonight after talking shit about psyche last night? I was
Shit, I was telling the truth
You're telling the truth about what?
About how psyche was like eating
He was what I think he was like, I don't know he was eating some puke. Oh now you don't know
Wow, Canada dry you're the person the chat that was saying that to today the first thing for the day
No, I just got online now, but yesterday I was saying stupid shit like that
Why would you think that like so you know I wasn't doing that right so he was telling everybody you were throwing up and eating it
Well, it's true. Isn't it wasn't he?
Hey, I'm throwing up because I'm listening to your fucking stupid ass right now. Go away forever.
That's disgusting, dude. Why would you say that?
What? Thank you.
That's weird.
That was only the- that was only one thing he was saying.
Well, hey, you know what? Hey, I gotta say this to Christine. Yes. That's cool. No, she fucking
Called it out women. Oh shit anymore. Well, but here's the thing
I like site site doesn't deserve this psyche. He's a very nice man
I think he's getting a little bit more strength with people around him
And the only way he knows about this
is when the bullshit starts in other panels and then this person comes up here and pretends like
nothing's wrong that's bullshit eating your puke that's where does that
happen Benny's talking about Benny's talking about the cat litter box and the cat poop and all kinds of
shit psyche
Thank you for letting me know Christina. I had the feeling like he was doing that anyway. I kind of know you have the links
So whatever you don't have to your band from the studio. So nice. Good luck with that
But anyway, wow. Wow. Sorry. I just felt it was disgusting that he acted that way last night
And then it's fucking weird and then come up here like there's nothing wrong. Why?
You don't use people that way
So she tells you these things yeah, that's cool, but one thing one thing I from earlier
I'm bringing up some that came that happened earlier today with uh, what was her name Janet remember Janet was up here
Yeah, I thought no I thought everything was
Interesting it's me. Oh, it's me until everybody porn on Janet
You know, I thought everything was good psyche in general having a good time until everybody I know but here's the thing
It's great psyche and Janet's having a good time. But this is he's has a panel
There were other people involved
And then she started and then she started talking about people and when she started talking about people that were in the chat
That's when it exploded
Christine. Yes, sir
Can you close like you to play my song because he keeps playing all these AI songs, but he's never played my song
Is it the game?
No, not the game one. My song connected me. I don't have your song Alex
Shit
I will pay
And we all get to use it we all use it
Yeah, it's good. So Christine, you trust them.
I played it before.
It's the second one.
Yeah, I played it before, remember?
And then I have another request after that.
But let's do this first.
Yeah, don't you don't you put to push you at your request? I'm not getting pushing. No Christine. You don't love the second one
Why are you gonna bury me, baby? I'm gonna bury you not you
She's mad at me and now she's mad at you
Summons in back
Don't worry
Cigarone Cigarone hold on this you lose up here if you give psyche ten bucks your name gets like on the banner
You get three hours. What do you mean three hours of the pink scrolling? Is that why?
You get a whole chat to yourself
you know
I sponsored the panel last night and this afternoon
Okay, so the link in the back
Hold on. What does that mean?
A virtual reality game those fucking things are fun
I knew it.
Oh, yeah.
It makes me dizzy.
I was in Dubai.
I guess I can book.
It's going to say Alex and the Queen for three hours.
Yeah.
Alex and you can have a whole panel to yourself for three hours.
I don't want that at all.
Alex, is that the game here?
Alex, I thought this was open the panel.
Alex, this is open the panel.
Three hours.
It opens the panel.
It opens the open panel.
Or otherwise, I just do one on one.
Oh, no.
I thought you meant the black Alex.
Oh, no black Alex. What do you mean that beautiful woman? No, there's a girl. There's a yeah
What's your corner name?
I'm like working on I'm so I'm doing I'm working with
I'm working. I'm making a deck. I just want to show you guys the first card of the deck
Okay
Oh, that's that's
You know what he hates that I come up here make it about me, but it is about me
Just play the shit. Hello J. Are you there? Yeah? Oh my camera. Okay. You'll be okay
J1 don't even ask me about crime and corruption and I want to be because I know what you're
gonna say. So how do you know? Because I know you because you're FBI. So and I told you
and that is corrupted. So you don't know shit that you can't be a problem with this and that
i run the show asos now you get it
we're getting on an organized crime family called the NYPD
so suck my dick and you'll die clean my song
let's be nice clean my fucking song bro somewhere tell them
Please
Thank you
Anyway, I was gonna do bad just a little bit ago virtual and it was the bomb I was jumping building
I was climbing walls. It was sick. What you had the goggles on
Yeah, my friend just bought the the new VR one that just came out or whatever for PlayStation 5. Dude, it is fucking
Like it's like you really people like you're doing some shit. It was pretty well
Psychic you can put names back up man like I can never
We're gonna drop the banner because it takes the names out one second. Once again, I'm weird there
Yeah, cuz I remember talking to her she was cool
Right
Yeah, oh got it. I wanted you guys to see that
He's threatening everybody in the chat.
He's like, I'd stop coming up there if I were you.
Or something like that.
He's saying, tell him to get me.
Oh, tell him to suck my ass.
And he said, he mentioned Mark.
Who's threatening everybody?
Oh, Mark.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
What the fuck are you doing to everybody?
No one gives a fuck.
He's saying you're on Allied Master Computer's channel
and IM2 or something.
And he said, I'd stop coming it up if you were out.
If you hang out here, he said, I'd stop coming out.
He said, what?
I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't know what's going on, but I don't
You seem like a bad case
Yeah
I know psyche does play my song
and i'll give you ten dollars okay it's a 50 second song where is it give him ten dollars
and then go to youtube i was going to tell you what it is you go to the youtube search box
and you type in alexander mcqueen nypd and it's the first thing the brock's off play
Yeah, Psyche. Psyche, I put the link in his thong in the back.
You have summer and Christine.
Fuck you for not even telling him about this.
Thank you.
You guys.
It's in the back chat.
Play it.
You got $10 for 50 seconds.
Oh.
It's gone.
Play it.
OK.
Do you want $10, 17?
I got it.
You can have my thong right now.
Alice.
Oh, he's done it.
Pay him the money first.
Yeah.
No, I can't even vote. That's weak. No, no, louder
Not happening
Nope, I'm not paying for that
I want that shit
Understand I want you to pull us all on the side and play it
And you get $10, you understand
I'm not paying for this garbage, fuck you!
Shut up!
What the fuck up?
Yo, it's true that Alexander McQueen and YPD
Pull it up and play it full blast!
Stikey, you play it full blast, I'll give you $15!
Stikey, no one gets the fuck what you're talking about either!
I want everybody and play a 50-second song
No, you didn't I didn't hear shit all I was Christine in the summer
You want
Kick everyone off the panel
You're gonna play my song full blast and I'll tell you $20 and you know I'm good for it
Okay, but can everybody just mute voluntarily so I don't have to keep people
I just everyone you know you fuck you have to kick them off take them all
It's okay. It's okay. No one's gonna mute. They can talk in between and ruin the song. I'll do it later
I don't even want to hear the song. I want you
You're gonna mute all these fat
Pissed out ten kids
Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck
Right now that's how we hear the song. So I want that bitch
And you
Shut summer up and you everyone and play a 50 second song. I will sell you $50
Tell you
Play the song
$100 if you take every one of the panel and play my song
I want that shit
Uninterrupted you understand I want no one on the panel
And
Guys, I'm gonna take everyone out just okay guys by the way that panel did expire
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
you say pretty sure maybe this is not negotiable bro and if you don't trust me
my mouth fuck you okay at least i don't have a hundred dollars for fifty
second okay okay listening to old broke bitches
Well, oh well
Changing the rule who's changing the rules around and not be honest like if you want me to do it's another time
Yeah
Summer's a cute one, sorry
And he said that he was gonna give you a hundred then he's like
I know I know he was
Wait, you know, wait, I'd be like on like a loan, you know, summer like you know, some of you
Thank you, you're welcome. You're welcome. Well, you can't share with the rest of us with the fuck
You are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you are you
Hey, what's up, dude
By the way, look at those guys. Look at those Q. Very
Cat it's like as soon as you die it's gonna eat your face. That's like one of those emojis. Oh, yeah, I hope
Oh
Now I'm gonna start taking everyone off the panel
Pick someone
Also
I got you
I want to see what you got tonight
I'm gonna pay for you on my channel
She's my type of woman
Yes
Hey, Paige, you'll get some tattoos
Pat, Pat, you're gonna need cues
You're gonna need three for two
Can I kick?
I'll give you $60 for three people right now
Right now
like you you got a damn show here
guys guys and make an answer then guys guys christina sponsored the open panel for another like
You know what I would do yes
I don't have a relationship that you don't know about he trusts me
I don't have any first he knows I paid bitch so pick summer and kick Christine
no I'll send you 50 right now but you gotta do a birthday to kick anybody
And if I don't do it, you bring them right up and call me a liar
And if I don't sell you 50 you bring them back up and you call me a piece of shit liar
I
Sponsored the panel you can't kick me
Yeah
Yeah, I can't kick anybody, bitch
As the sponsor of the panel cannot be kicked up there, up the panel they sponsor
Haha, and I sponsored the next panel, so you can't kick me either, bitch
Well, I'm gonna fuck a man
It's like, so are you insane? You like sending money, but you can't kick nobody?
What, are you like a, you're a rat with a speed?
This figure's like, you can't kick nobody, but send me the money first
What, are you crazy, bro?
What happened is yesterday like crucible ghost was the first panel sponsor and I was like hey crucible
Like I was like he's like he's like I promise I said you promise you'll pay and he's like I promise
And then he just took off to the middle of the thing and then never came back
He knows I pay right
He knows summer pays, right?
I said you pay I pay
I'm talking someone's talking that's Christine
Summer was talking
Dude, you know what that means like look at that. She did regardless of her beautiful tattoos summer is loyal
Yeah, I'll give you I mean that deal yeah, all right
Okay
Thank you
No problem, but I'm gonna put Christine is sponsoring this panel, so I will put Christine's name on the banner and
Okay, okay, thank you people that already paid a good for it
Hey, hey, hey, hey, he's like he can you do me a favor?
I'm going nowhere by the fucker. I'll summer. I'll pay you some or two summer down
Everyone's doing everyone's good. I'll gladly pay you Tuesdays like
I'm tripping out
I need I need summer to summer down a little that's what I need
Oh, we have fun
Yeah
Alize over us, but we like roasting him
What was this fucking song you wanted to play?
What was that all about?
I played it anyway, and he couldn't hear anything. And so I might as well not even play it
Yeah, he's making the man's I mean we're making the man's and I don't like to be ordered around on my show like he
Like I'm not gonna be like oh look, you know mine. It's like I'm gonna like you know
I'd like to have a respectful deals not just be yelled at like if there's money thrown at me like that
You get yelled at all the times like you some like you're some fucking whore. He's just yeah. Yeah
Yeah, that's weird, that's where he wants to take up, you know, and Christina and like, you know, and summer and stuff like that. And who I like summer summer. Are you listening?
Yeah, I'm here. Hey, I can't I can't request the song because like, you won't play it. But if you want to, you can listen to nine inch nails. We're into
We're in this together. Yes. Okay.
Guys, guys, has everyone heard everyone heard the
I
Hello everybody
Brace um page mic up just a little bit. Yeah
Yeah, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there, right there
Oh, you have a tattoo on your fucking chest man. That's cool. Yeah, there she goes. Oh
Well ending summer ending that's a
Let's take a little musical break for the I want to show page this video. Yeah, can you yeah, please?
I'm gonna show page page. Watch this. Have you seen this page?
Walks a beat in the city life
Flashin' blues under New York nights
But his heart's up north
Where the rivers run free
With a blonde haired beauty from April Country
He's got a badge of dream and a thing for a laugh
Caught a glimpse of her smile
Now he's doin' the math
From the Bronx to the Bush
Oh, he's thinkin' real deep
Page are you the one I've been missin' in my sleep
You're falling in love with me
Paige, will you fall in love with me?
Is that you?
I'm cute
He dreams of her boots in his uptown bed
Laughing at the dumbass jokes he says
She's gutting the trout
He's eating steak somewhere in the middle
They both take a break
He'd trade his night stick for a fishing pole
Chase her laughter like it's his
to say
around the alley.
Do you go with your partners and your partner?
That beard though
All I'd have to do is play cemetery gates with
Everything would be okay
Yeah
I'm talking to someone not you
Who's that there's like Peter Pan was in that video and one of the seat all of a sudden there's like some guy like some
Yeah, who's that guy
Yeah, it's like pages twin
I don't know it's weird. It's a mystery. It looked like a page transformed into a man or something. I don't know
Ziggy
I was like summer and I would like her to listen to Panterra Cemetery Gates
She has gray hair remember that one time you just gray hair
Well, hey, she has he asked me to say
No, someone's trying to get in the studio, so I'm gonna kick Ziggy out and
I was just counting my money. I was just talking to my pocket change
So I'm gonna try to enter the studios I'm gonna kick the out of the U.S. Let's look at it for a second
Summer the little pain
For you can't see it. It's fucking it's meaningless if you don't send it to him
It's not digital.
You can't send that.
What are you going to do?
I'm just showing you my hand right now, Ted.
He's trying to show off.
What are you going to put that in the envelope
and send it, Ted?
If you come to it, what does he do?
No, he's not going to do anything.
He's just going to show off.
He's just trying to, he's trying to show off flaws.
It looks like ridiculous.
Come on, Alex.
Look at all the money I'm going to send you.
Look at it all.
Woo.
Yeah.
Nice, Alex.
Go like, I don't want to see it unless it's in my account.
I don't want to see it, because it's in my account, okay?
Okay, we're out.
Hello?
Hi, Gaudi.
How are you doing?
What's up, Peggy?
How you been?
Hi, everybody.
Hello.
Did you yell four?
I did, by the fucking yell all day.
Yes.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Yeah, I know.
I'm not a girl who has to be told twice.
I'm really not.
Good, good, good, good.
It's not official unless you yell that.
You know, the girl that has to resell twice, I have to be told multiple times.
Hey, Paige, do you have on some ear buds?
That means you have two black eyes? Do you have two black eyes?
I don't have two black eyes! I don't have one!
Did you get to walk guys when you got your nose?
Because they didn't they didn't break the nose like usually they break the bridge of the nose like when they do a
But they just they didn't do that. They just did the tip of it. And so they didn't
I had Jane Fonda's uh Jane Fonda's the guy that did the Jane Fonda's facelifts that is the her the doctor I got
I went to a few consultations
I went to a few consultations and one the first doctor said it was too complicated
The second doctor wanted to break or like give me a chin implant and I
I got something on my trying to even it all out somehow. Yeah
And break my nose she was gonna break my nose too and then with the third doctor
He's like you don't have to break your nose. We're just gonna make you a tip and it was like real easy. It was like
It was very, it was just, I had a hook, I had a hook for, my nose was very hooked. Now it's like, perfect.
Yeah.
Well, forever.
I'm on my channel.
Lately, too. Coffee.
I should probably have worked them out and made one, too.
Cheers, like.
Yeah.
I think if anything, I get fillers in my lips because I do age to get thinner, you know,
so I might get a little bit of filler in my lips and then a little bit of my, uh,
because I have the, like, smoker's lines in my softest form.
Yeah.
It's pretty cool.
I'm sorry.
I'm showing the kitty cat.
Summer, why the fuck are you so goddamn beautiful, baby?
Are you so beautiful?
She is.
Christine's still up here.
No, I don't think so.
All of you girls are fucking 12.
Fucking 12.
Well, thank you.
I pissed off Boyle up here.
I think I had the most probably one of the best-looking panels
on all of YouTube, I'm sure I did.
Let's piss off Boyle.
Oh, my god.
Whoa.
Did he leave?
No, he's here.
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
We don't we don't discriminate
I told I told my husband right now. I was like everybody's like showing their fucking cleavage on camera. He's like, I want to see
My husband's like I want to see I was like we're live on YouTube, bro
It really is the best show on YouTube
Notifications
You got a bunch of fun
Oh son, let's talk off of that
That's panel 11
Whoa, it feels like Mardi Gras
Is it Mardi Gras? Look at Joe
Feed the needy
Joe!
You're live on TV
You're muted
I'll mute this boob up here
Yeah
Joe and I can be the boobs
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my
god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
Oh
Look at the cherries.
Oh, OK.
OK.
Hi.
I have to re-show the screen.
I'll be right back.
I just, I'll be right back.
I'll have to restart.
Really?
Sorry, guys.
Yeah.
OK.
I'll have to re-show the screen.
I'll be right back.
I've been on I've been on for 11 hours anyway, so I'm gonna end the stream. I'll be right back, okay?